I pull you into this world...
A machine that can think... and feel...
that's it...come,come...
Come in here...buddy~
That's a watch~(echo...)
W-A-T-C-H?
It's like a child,it has to learn.
Your name...Chappie
CHA-PPIE
Anything you wanna do in your life you can do
why poetry have original ideas
W-O-W~
People are always fearful of something they don't understand
A problem without a fissional intelligence, it is why too unpredictable
You know what's a black-sheep?
NO
It's like we knew different to everyone else...
You told about us so much more!
and I could ever if imagine
It gonna make you cool and tough...don't laugh at us being cool
This robot is gonna be removed
It's just a kid!
It could be the next step in evolution
I'm conciousness...
I am alive...
I am Chappie!