I know you.
You killed one of our people.
You've got another DNA record.
Oh, the other one was just a sample.
Did you know the authorities would
attack here?
Actually, we were just passing by.
They weren't attacking us anyway.
They don't give a shit
about human beings.
Their thoughts are too complex for us.
Silicon Creatures to understand anyway.
Don't get hit by his gun.
Did you uncover the records?
My name is Cibo.
The information located at the tip of a hard disk...
If  processing speed is 8 to the power of 23 GPS...
If processing speed is 8 to the power of 23 GPS...
If processing speed is 8to the power of 23 GPS...
If processing speed is 8 to the ppoower of 23 GPS...
If processing speed is 8 to the power of 23 GPS...
...it is 824,654,282 hours later.
...it is 824,654,282hours later.
You should remember me.
Head Scientist Cibo.
A son of the President?
Something like that.
A fourth generation clone, to be precise.
Well, you've certainly showed
up at a good time.
We're about to start an experiment.
Connecting to the net sphere?
I'm glad I made it in time!
I asked my father for a big favor and
he gave me this special promotion.
Is that the complete net gene carrier?
Pretty huge, isn't it?
All of this equipment acts something
like a brain for the subject.
Even with all that,
it's nowhere near as good as the original.
What's that floating in the water tank?
An emergency power plant for the city.
It was discovered in
one of the sedimentary layers...
When it was removed from the pressure
machine, a chemical reaction occurred.
Right now we're managing to suppress
an explosion...
Explosion?
Have you really given up on breaking
through the mega-structure?
No, we haven't really given up,
the council just gave us an order to stop.
So, you're going to use that...
Is it really okay to tell
me this kind of thing?
The President should know
about it by now.
He can stop us at any time if he wants.
You must be desperate to get out of here.
So, what is up there?
It's getting started.
My name is Cibo.
The information located at the tip of a hard disk...
Who are you?
Administration Bureau...
From Net-Sphere Control Level.
In order to convey a message to the
explorer Killy...
...we have downloaded a proxy organism.
Due to the current status of chaotic
infection, we are incapable of making...
...direct contact with you.
We know that you humans have made an
enormous effort...
To emerge from isolation.
However, even with all that effort,
you have never succeeded.
Because, no matter what your methods,
if you have contact with humans...
...who do not carry network genes, you
will invoke Safeguard counter-measures.
This function is totally independent
within the net sphere...
...and thus, even at the control level,
we cannot interfere.
Even now, we send a stream of
interference to the current Safeguards...
However, its effects wouldn't last long.
So what do you want?
The city keeps expanding randomly.
This expansion has been continuing for
a long time, and we can no longer...
...determine the actual size of the city.
All hardware for the net sphere is
contained in the mega-structure.
Insecure construction between levels
causes problems for the structure of...
...the net sphere, and
accelerates the chaos.
Network genes must be discovered
to stop the expansion of the city.
There is no one who can initiate perfect
access to the current net.
However, there must be a human
with network genes in this city, and...
...we believe that you will find this
person.
The Safeguard download will soon
be completed.
We advise that you head to the top
immediately and accomplish the plan.
It's great to see a living
human being at last.
I detected a strong magnetic
disturbance, so I came to have a look.
Those Silicon Creatures were just doing
the same thing.
My name is Cibo.
And your name is?
It's him.
The latest model of Silicon Creature.
My equipment is useless.
Gotta get away...
New model...
That's a Graviton Radiation Projector?
I'm here to rescue you, Killy!
Ok, I got it from Killy.
I'll be back soon.
Uh-huh.
Nothing irregular except chromosome #10 and #11.
Get ready for the recording.
Above the 3,000thº floor, we found a
community where the system is alive.
We don't know if anyone is there, but go
check it out.
It's getting dark.
We've met before.
My name is...
My name is Cibo.
...Cibo.
OVERFLOW
RESTORATION
OUTPUT THE RESULT
Data on the 45,724th particle
- Lost
Data on the 32,134th particle
Data on the 721,311 st particle
- Lost
Serial number: KM24358447
Manufacturer: YUJIN
Security scan start.
Voice output disabled
|
This is a Silicon Creature.
Voice output disabled
|
Continues... from the ancient...
Voice output disabled
|
Continues... from the ancient...
Voice output disabled
|
Continues... from the ancient...
Independence... power... on... the net
We've ...come
to destroy
The...
Net... Terminal... Gene
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with theNet Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
To block... the
human beings...
with the Net Terminal...
Geneto...
recover...  the
Net... Sphere
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
Gene... to...
recover... the
Net... Sphere...
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
This...
is the purpose...
of... the entire
... Silicon Creatures.
For...
our ...race
to survive...
net...
the Net...
must
always be...
...in... chaos.
This...
chaos...
...was...
...not...
...created...
...by...
...us.
Once...
This... w... orld
was... united...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
by...
...the...
Net... Sphere...
How...e...ver
There...  is no
documentationtation ... of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
There... is no
documentation...of ...it
that... exists...
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
It's... also...
the... Governor's...
...
.....
old...ish...
memory...
Besides... we've always
Besides... we've always...
...hated you.
Do you remember now?
Killy...