It Hurts!
Enough!
Caesar!
I'm sorry, Caesar.
You're too late. She's already
sucking my big juicy cock!
Alector...
Die!
Father...
- Yes! We got him!
- We killed Caesar!
I'll kill you!
How dare you touch my Alector!?
For this you pay with your lives!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 4
Journey to an Unknown World
Do not be afraid! He's just a big piece of shit!
What the hell...?!
He will kill all of us! We can't do any harm to him...
Unworthy mortals!
Did you really think you could mess with me?
One more step asshole
and your daughter will die!
We will tear her apart in front of you...
Alector!
What's wrong...? Stop it!
Stop it! Stop crying Himi!
Now tell me, why do you cry?
Himi!
Withdraw!
Give us back our town!
Kill them! Don't leave anyone alive!
How could they have become so strong?
Pedro! Our last hope is the Genocydroid D-9.
If we can reach the R&D sector...
We will even still have a chance to win the battle.
D-9...
Go to hell!
Pedro!
Ruddle! We waited for you!
What's going there outside?
Everything worked smoothly.
Tell us!
Meanwhile already more than a
hundred of us must be in the palace!
Do you still want to take more fighters in?
Yet we still have to find Caesar!
I think it's enough to storm the palace!
We shouldn't over do it.
Never! Not before we find Caesar!
He treated us Makemonos always as scum!
He killed many of us!
This all ends only when Caesar pays for that.
Let's go!
Idaten what do you want to do?
Enko!
Forget it, I stay here!
D-9... on the day your body became metal...
was the last time I cried...
Now we meet again...
yet nothing is like it used to be.
Please... use your powers to help us
in this time of need.
D-9...!
Hello soldier bitch! What does
a pretty girl like you do...
in a place like this?
You...?
Fetch her!
Well, up to now all you and your troops
ever did was always fuck us...
But now...
No! Leave me! Be gone with you!
What the...!
What the hell is that?
D-9...
Your regeneration isn't finished yet...
P...e...d...r...o...
Make him harmless, now!
Leave him to me!
D-9...!
P...e...d...r...o...
This thing wasn't even worth a clothes rack!
D-9...
Hey, you act like that scrap pile was your lover!
At least now, no one will disturb us from...
having fun with the girl...
Ready for a small party, soldier bitch?
Let's go...
We sure will have a lot of fun with her...
You girls belong to the troops
only to amuse the guys...
I want to taste her first!
Hey it seems you like it, bitch...
Your nipples are already hard!
I will put in mine first...
Prepare yourself for something
real good, soldier bitch!
My cock will make you happy...!
No! Please, stop it!
Yeah... this is nice!
I think I'm in heaven!
Please stop!
And how does it feel?
She... she is great!
I could fuck her forever!
I'll take care of one of her other holes!
How does it feel for you?
Better than in my most beautiful dreams!
The girlie isn't bad!
But now I want something special...!
No... not that...!
Alector!
Was everything for nothing, Alector?!
Good...!
We got him!
Caesar is ours now! We defeated him!
Long live Enko!
Soon also Caesar's country
will belong to us again!
That means finally, freedom!
At last the bastard had to pay!
We made it, Enko!
Yes...
And now since he can't help
his daughter anyway...
should we take care of her...
No wait! If you do that then you
aren't any better than Caesar!
What's this bullshit?
It's none of your business, small one.
What the...?!
This bastard!
Damn! He is the only obstacle in our way.
Enko...!
Oh... my Alector!
Caesar!
Now it's your turn!
Enko!
Enko...
What is this...?
Megumi...! What is this?
Kyo-O... Kyo-O... His light fills the palace!
What's his intention...?
What's going on?!
Why do they fight each other?!
The weak will be kissed by the light of justice!
Light of justice...?
From the voices of people hatred rings...
The child will be the messenger of destruction...
Unless it's released before...
Hey... man...
She is damn good to fuck!
Idiot!
She is mine! Don't touch her!
What...?!
Help!
Stop! Stop it!
D-9...
Pedro...
I... I feel...
I will die...
Release me...
from the pain... please!
I have never forgotten you...
Please... the pain... kill me!
Kill me!
You are the only woman I ever loved...
Thanks...
Please stop it...
Don't be afraid...
I'm here with you...
Everything will be good. Trust me, Himi.
Buju...
Who's work is that...?
Incredible! The city is completely ravaged!
Everything will be good again... Himi!
Osaka... we must go to Osaka.
Buju, let us go there.
Osaka, you say?
I must meet Chojin in Osaka.
Chojin? In Osaka?
Damn Chojin! He is probably
responsible for that destruction.
Either he or this damn Kyo-O!
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey, old man! What do you mean by that?
You know well what I mean.
I thought much about that lately.
Chojin must be in direct connection
with the origin...
of us Makemonos.
What did you say...? That's a joke, isn't it?!
I am what I am!
No one created me!
And no one can tell me what I have to do!
Are you sure?
How is it then that we arise after...
destruction of the three worlds?
Couldn't it be that we are part of Chojin's legend?
A new race born to create a new better world?
If we want an answer for that
we should go to Osaka...
Only why has Kyo-O not shown himself yet?
Megumi! Where were you? Did you help me?
Amano, I am not that which you think of me...
Megumi?! What's the meaning of this...?
Through the annihilation of the 3
worlds my work isn't finished yet...
Chojin! You are him!
What the hell did you do?!
Up to now I ignored Kyo-O's existence...
however now Megumi will be my messenger...
Once more I will bring annihilation to the world...
That's my destiny.
You mustn't! Your time didn't come yet!
Forget it, Amano.
The world which you desire becomes
faster reality than you think!
You can't be serious!
Brother!
Megumi...!
So that's what you want, Chojin...
However, what do you plan to do against Kyo-O?
And what the hell did you do with Megumi?!
Fine! Let's go to Osaka!
Really, Buju?
Yes, just for you...
However before we go I would
like to take along someone...
Ruddle! It is dreadful!
Enko! it's Enko!
Enko? What's with him?
Caesar killed him...
Caesar...!
That all was unnecessary after all...!
Alector... my graceful Alector...
Just how can I use my powers to help you?
You shouldn't live on in this cruel world...
For you there is only one way left to go...
Wait!
Caesar, I came to fetch your daughter!
Buju...! You are really still alive?
So you want my daughter...?
So it's like that...
But my daughter is too graceful so I
wouldn't give her to a beast like you.
She is the most valuable treasure
which I ever owned...
Alector was always my everything for me.
Yet you took her away from me...
and brought her death!
You...! And now you dare meeting me again...
Do you think that I simply accept
the fall of my empire?
Do you really think that...?
Well, Buju.
The time of pay back came.
If you can defeat me Alector will be yours.
You will die, Caesar!
What!?
Buju...!
Don't approach...!
Don't approach!
Buju...!
Buju, now the fight really starts!
Not bad!
Don't talk so much and come here now!
Did if finally kill him?
Not so fast...!
Don't just think that you...
can beat me that easy!
Alector!
Buju...
Alector...
Finally... I found you...
I never imagined that a Makemono
could love a human.
I think that's a good sign...
I think so too... It's better than killing each other.
Father...?
Father! Buju, where is my father?
He... he is...
Father...?
Buju, you defeated me...
Since you were able to do that
Alector should be yours now...
Father!
I... I give you my daughter...
Because I... I'm defeated...
Father... Father!
Oh, Father...
Please don't say something like that...
Forgive me... Buju...
You must understand me...
I can't leave my father alone... father...!
Alector...
I'm the one who lost... Caesar...
For me...?
Thanks... the time of destruction
is past. Sorry that we...
treated you so bad...
Why did we fight that long?
Why did we fight anyway?
Everything for nothing... senseless...
Please don't die! Please no!
Stay up, please!
Let's go... you look like you're ready...
You too, Buju...
Oh really?
Then let's go!
Father... look. Everything looks so
beautiful and peaceful from here...
Do you really think that it was
the right decision, Alector?
Yes... I would only restrict Buju...
Buju, the father of your child...?!
You knew it?
Yes... it's his child...
It will be very strong as he is.
Yes.
Alector, do you remember my last wish...?
Yes, father.
OK! Still a long trip awaits us.
What the hell do you want here?!
We accompany you. Also we want to
find out the reason of our existence.
It might be that we won't return alive.
We know what dangers there
are in the outside in the world...
it awaits us.
That's right!
You can use the aid of a few friends well.
Since we have to protect the child...
the key to everything...
Who are you?
I'm the Genocydroid D-9.
The woman I loved is dead.
There is nothing that holds me still here.
Take me with you!
You too...?
I'm D-9. I'm strong...
Do what you like!
Good it's settled!
I'm already excited about what will happen...
After all the great adventures..
more still awaits.
What will happen when Kyo-O and
Chojin meet each other in Osaka?
That will be very thrilling, won't it Chojin?
Alector...
Buju, I wish you luck for your trip.
Sometime we will meet...
again...
Buju...
We will meet again for sure.
OK people... let's go!