What's going on here?
What is that?!
It's Nagumo! Why does he return?
He wants that child!
Then... Then this baby must be...
The Kyo-O!
Nagumo is still alive?
I thought, he was dead...
Faust!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O!
Your powers will serve me well.
What is this? What happened?
What is this?!
That's our chance to escape!
What are you doing?
I asked you what you were doing!
Long time no see, Amano.
Münchhausen...!
Now you become witness of my power!
What?
You will see it...
Finally it's time!
Nagumo, try it! Try to kill that baby!
You know that it's your enemy...
No!
Kyo-O, what will you do now?
What the hell is going on?
Now we have the Kyo-O!
The Chojin will meet his end!
No, you would not dare!
Alector.
Most beautiful of women,
what will I do now?
I can not imagine life without you.
But why?
Buju!
Why did she sacrifice her life
for the sake of some monster?
When I created your soul
I asked only for love in return
What happened?
Was this all because of the  Kyo-O?
The Caesar! The Caesar!
Indulge! Indulge your pleasures!
Indulge in the pleasures
granted you by God.
You can cleanse your
lost evil souls.
Only then will your souls
be eternally happy.
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
0h great Caesar!
Today, the three of them were chosen.
Please grant them
your boundless love.
You will be entering the world of
pleasure and enjoyment forever!
Great Caesar!
Great...
Remain here...
No... please...
Afraid...?
Almost half of my body is metal.
The body is only the wrapper of the soul.
Such a sensitive body!
Soon intelligent machines will rule the world.
Come here...
It's your turn.
I'll give you an ecstasy of pain...
No...!
Now Tagushi, how do you feel as a Japanese prime minister?
Fine, thanks... without your help I
would never have reached this goal...
I owe you a lot...
You moved any of my opponents
out of the way without hesitation.
This was only the beginning. Soon
I will control the whole world.
I will succeed with what failed Hitler.
What?
Hitler's obsession became his doom.
Yet I'm realist.
I studied the history of mankind.
My research lead me here to Tokyo.
I'm sure that civilization has it's origin here.
At no other place of the world
are you closer to the Gods.
The ruins, I found, are the key...
to domination of the whole world!
8th FEBRUARY 1982
HOTEL AKASAKA, TOKYO.
It's a great honor for us to
be allowed to greet you.
Father!
Alector, my daughter, are you alright?
Yes of course, father. Do we
dine together today father?
I'm afraid not. I still have much work
to do. You will have to eat alone.
Alector, your father is a very busy man.
You must understand that.
I'm sorry, Alector. But tomorrow
will be only for you, I promise.
Oh father...!
How tall she became...
Unfortunately I have only too little...
time for her since her mother died...
This is the most important
excavation in the world.
It's as old as mankind itself.
These hieroglyphs tell the history of mankind.
They tell about emergence, past, present...
and even about future of the world!
The future?
Yes it sounds unbelievable but everything fits.
According to the records our end awaits shortly.
It's said that besides our world
two other parallel worlds exist...
one of the Demons and one of the Human-Beasts.
Every 3000 years...
a being called Chojin unites the three worlds.
More can not be made out. From
here the boards are damaged.
It doesn't matter I will continue
history from here myself anyway.
I will summon Chojin and then I will kill him.
Then I will rule as God.
I will determine the future...
Caesar, we made it. We have a direct access...
to NASA's computer system.
Now finally we will receive the last answers.
Which time do these ruins come from?
17.000 before Christ...
+/- 2000 years.
How reliable is this answer?
80%. Max. deviation +/- 5%.
What does this information base on?
On all entered information.
With who is Chojin to be equated?
With God... God... God...
Why did Chojin appear on earth
17000 years before Christ?
In order to release the earth
and to unite the worlds.
Was the old God MU involved?
No, Chojin and MU are not like-minded
They used their powers against each other.
Can you summon Chojin?
Only if I manage getting into contact with him.
Initiate all capacities...
Establishing of contact runs.
Are you the one who called me?
Are you Chojin?
So I am called.
Then die!
Now I will unite the three worlds!
Never underestimate the power of a God!
Father!
Alector!
Run away, fast!
You won't be able to stop the apocalypse.
Alector! Alector!
Chojin! Who ever you are you will pay for that.
Alector!
Alector, come back to me...
I miss your laughter...
Alector!
What? That baby?!
Yes, Himi was kidnapped by Faust.
Before however, he still
managed to revive you.
Nonsense!
Only Chojin has power to revive dead.
Maybe Himi has the power to kill Chojin.
So what?
That isn't a reason for me to free the baby.
Nevertheless there must be
a reason why it revived you.
I guess it chose you to protect it.
That's your fate.
Fate...
Even the most insignificant being has its fate.
If insect, half-human, demon or human...
everyone has a fate which he can't escape.
On my search for Chojin I became
acquainted with many people...
They all were guided by strengths also
against the power of their love...
They all couldn't escape their fate
exactly as you and I.
I don't know what fate expects of us...
however, I know that my fate
will be fulfilled.
What will be will be.
Don't you think the same... Buju?
In fact I came here in order to
annihilate Kyo-O, the evil.
However now I know that Himi,
the baby, is Kyo-O.
No!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Sorry but I can't promise that.
Yet I don't see any danger which
starts from Himi at the moment.
And you, Buju? Which role will you play?
Which role...?
Caesar plans something with Kyo-O.
As I know him he will try to kill Chojin.
However I will not allow that.
I will annihilate Caesar and
if necessary also Kyo-O.
Unless...
somebody would destroy Caesar's plan
and free Himi. You for example...
That's none of my business...
Think of that, it's a question of Himi.
I go now to Caesar.
Think again about everything, Buju!
Amano! Don't hurt Himi!
Forget Alector, Buju. You must be strong now.
What?!
Just shut up!
Let's see what Caesar and
Münchhausen plan to do...
Are these all?
Yes. I did my best to bring people.
Doesn't matter. Perhaps more will come.
Now to our plan...
We are at this place.
Here is Caesar's palace.
And here is the mine in which we had to work.
Some of us couldn't escape and are still there.
We have no information about the monster.
Nevertheless, I fear that a lot of us were hurt.
Therefore we should act as fast as possible.
Ruddle, are we really
doing the right thing?
We can't go back now.
And we don't want to either. We
have to pay back much to Caesar.
It won't be easy.
I feel something...
Evil powers concentrate around Caesar's palace.
Something incredible will come up.
We must save our friends fast.
God gave every Makemono
specific abilities and strengths.
Now it's time to use them.
Yeah, let's do it!
We will creep tomorrow morning
into Caesar's palace.
You know what to do when we give you the sign.
Yes!
Caesar, all preparations are done.
We wait only for the awakening of Kyo-O.
Faust, I'm worried.
All events arrive as prophesied
by the hieroglyphs.
I ask myself if we really can change history...
No worry, Caesar.
We have Kyo-O, the key to ultimate power.
When Kyo-O awakes and
combines himself with Faburil...
even Chojin himself can't stop us.
Faburil? I thought he was
destroyed by Nagumo?!
No, only a part of him.
However he regenerated.
He is now even more powerful
and he wants revenge.
Tomorrow morning the union
with Kyo-O will occur.
Really?
Caesar!
What?
The restoration of princess Alector is completed.
Ah, finally!
Alector!
Oh, Alector!
Show me your face, daughter!
What's wrong Alector?
Where is Buju?
He isn't here.
He is dead.
Father!
Have you killed him, father! Did you do it?!
No!
Alector...
Buju...
Alector... why...?
What happened to you...?
Father, do we eat this evening together?
Alector, I will revenge your death...
Kyo-O, Faburil...
With the nuclear missiles...
Chojin will soon be dead.
Alector, I will create a new world only for you.
Caesar, we register changes
on the psychowave monitor.
Faburil reacts to the power of Kyo-O!
What?!
Who are you? Why were you born?
If you oppose me I must annihilate you!
So you are nevertheless my enemy?
So it starts! Very good, Faust!
You are supposed to suffer, Kyo-O! That
is the key to the union with Faburil.
Faburil approaches to the palace, Caesar.
He claims many sacrifices
also among our people.
Don't worry about that.
Caesar... the nuclear missiles are ready.
Destination: Osaka.
The launch occurs tomorrow morning.
Start the countdown.
Starting the countdown.
Watch, there below!
What's that? What's going on here?!
Nothing good I fear. Come, run away from here!
Why does this monster appear here?
Disaster is breaking out!.
Father, I have a good news.
Soon your project will be complete.
and our family will control the whole world.
Alector, forgive me.
I just wanted you back.
Soon you could be the ruler of the new world.
Everyone would obey you.
Please, Alector, laugh again...
What, Kyo-O?! You refuse Faburil?!
What are you afraid of?
You are still a baby. You can't already know...
what power you have.
Open yourself and allow Faburil to enter!
That's enough, Faust! Leave the baby alone!
Too late, Amano! Kyo-O is already under my spell.
To release Kyo-O you have to kill me!
Are you able to kill me?
Be ready for it!
Hold, wait, Münchhausen!
Oh, Faust...!
You don't want to kill Faust, do you?
You again! We have still a fight pending!
I'm ready!
Damn!
Buju... Buju...
Himi...
Buju, Help! Help me!
Are... Are you Himi?
You are very beautiful...
Buju...!
How warm you are...
What the hell...
Himi!
No fear!
What a sword!
Caesar...!
Caesar, Kyo-O was kidnapped by Buju!
What?!
They just escape from the palace!
Catch him! He mustn't escape!
Kill them!
Yes!
This dirty bastard! So he is still alive!
Is Kyo-O responsible for that...?
Buju is alive?!
Buju!
Alector!
No, please! No father, no!
You aren't my daughter...
Just an useless android!
You are mine!
No!
That hurts!
Forgive me, father!
No father, please!
Buju...
You will forget him now.
No!
How do you like that, Alector?
I do give it to you better
than this Makemono, don't I?
I'll take you to ecstasy...
An idea just came to me!
You want to see Buju, don't you?
I'll show him to you... one last time.
I will tear him apart in front of your eyes!
WARNING! WARNING!
Only 300 seconds till launch.
All employees into the safety zones.
I should have take insect spray with me!
That was only a small taste, small one!
Go to hell, bitch!
Somehow, I suddenly
feel unwelcome here!
Caesar, you bastard show yourself!
Alector!
So we meet again, Buju...
for the last time!
Alector, say goodbye to your lover!
It's your last chance!
Buju...!
Buju...
You can't kill me...!
Sorry but you can't help me.
I can't move.
Buju...
No...!
Makemono scum... Faburil will
engulf you together with Kyo-O!
Buju!
Alector! Alector!
Alector...
Only 30 seconds till the launch!
Münchhausen! Now I will destroy you!
Too late!
Amano, you lost!
Hold, wait!