The Overfiend entered Akemi's womb one hundred
years ago so that he could return to this world.
I knew it!
He's being born!
It's the Overfiend!
Looks like my patience paid off!
Wh-What the...
Wh-Why does everything look so strange here?
Everything looks the way it did the night that
Nagumo turned into the Demon of Destruction!
I'm sure a hundred years have passed.
Have I been dreaming?
No, it can't be.
I saw it with my own eyes!
I saw the battle between the
Overfiend and the Princess of Chaos!
That happened thirty years after the
Overfiend was implanted in Akemi's womb.
Where there's a god, there's a demon.
And where there's an Overfiend, there's Chaos.
Just as the legend states, the Princess
of Chaos was born in Japan.
Unable to wait, the Overfiend has come to be reborn.
I was almost fooled.
That was merely a false Overfiend
sent from the Demon Realm!
By having sex with her,
he became far more powerful.
He tried to take all her powers for himself.
But the Princess of Chaos was
not to be underestimated.
Not only was she beautiful, she was cunning as well!
She used his metamorphosis against
him to increase her own powers!
It was a fabulous fight.
I was proud to have seen it.
The Princess of Chaos was able to protect
the barrier around Osaka Castle...
while warding off the false Overfiend.
I see.
It was during that fight!
That power she demonstrated during that fight.
The shock of that power surge...
shortened the hundred-year delay
in the Overfiend's reincarnation!
That must be so!
Nagumo...
Nagumo!
That bastard!
Nothing's changed!
That's right.
The present time is a continuation of that evening!
Nagumo!
How does it feel to be the Demon of Destruction!?
What?
What's that for?
It's me, it's me!
Don't you recognize me!?
So the Overfiend has been born!
Time to show everyone what this
"new world" of yours looks like!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Birth of the Overfiend
The Pool of Life
Days later   Osaka
This sure is yummy.
Aw, lemme eat it!
You mustn't fight.
Sorry, Mommy.
You're always so whiny.
Hey! She said we shouldn't fight!
Daddy? What's wrong?
Daddy?
Fucking hell!
Darling!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan...
I was...
What was... What was I doing?
How did it end up like that?
I don't understand at all!
All I know is that my body lost
control, like it was exploding.
Same here.
And not just with us beasts.
Humans and demons as well as beasts...
are killing each other every day.
It seems as though the birth of the Overfiend
has actually made the world worse.
That's for sure!
Wh-What the hell's that?
Not sure.
It appeared when the Overfiend was born.
Maybe it's the Overfiend's castle.
Possibly.
In that case, we'd better pop in for a visit.
Akemi...
She's sleeping so peacefully.
Sure is.
She worked hard these past hundred years.
Let's get her out of this barrier and let her live
as a normal woman in the outside world.
Behind you!
Who do you think you are?
I've never seen you guys around here.
Where are you from?
I don't think much of ya.
You think you're a match for the great Amano?
You wait here, Akemi.
I'll go crush 'em for ya.
Okay! I'm here to give ya some attention!
But I won't go easy!
Piece of cake!
What the fuck are these guys?
They all have the same face?
Have you seen anything like this before?
No, I haven't.
Huh? They don't have dicks or pussies!
Looks like they're not from the Three Realms.
Who the hell are you!?
I am the Messenger of Imagination...
Nizushi.
The Messenger of Imagination?
You mean the Overfiend?
We are a new race. The Overfiend has given us life.
The Overfiend created a new race?
We possess a power that is absent in the three
archaic races: humans, beasts, and demons.
We are a new race.
You have a power we don't have?
We can make real what we imagine.
We have the powers of conception.
The powers of conception?
We use these powers to
manipulate the three greedy races.
If we wish them to rape, they rape.
If we wish them to kill, they kill.
W-Wait!
So you're saying that when we lose our minds,
it's because you're controlling us?
Correct.
By the powers of conception,
we can accomplish anything.
What's that?
I don't know.
That thing must've come from her imagination!
Vanish, Amano.
Stay back, Megumi!
Shit!
Onii-chan!
Megu... mi...
What are you doing!
No!
Let me go!
Why you... you!
Do not resist me...
female who possesses the strongest
powers in the Three Realms.
What's happening?
My body... is hot.
Look well, strongest female of the Three Realms.
Amazing!
Not so fast.
I want it!
Do you want it?
Yes, please!
Very well.
Wh-What's happening?
Am I dying?
A-Am I gonna die?
Touch it.
strongest female of the Three Realms.
– Show me the mark of our new world.
– What?
Why?
No...
It can't be!
Are you a man?
Or a woman?
If you wish, I am a man.
If you wish, I am a woman.
It is as your will.
Allow me to show you...
to show you what you desire most.
No!
No, no!
Th-That's incredible!
You become a man again!
No, no, no!
I'm cum... I'm cumming!
Oh no, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
The strongest female of the Three Realms...
is not so strong.
The Field of Conception
Come to me, my children.
By powers of conception, you shall be born.
The Field of Birth
The Field of Growth
The Underground
His heart has stopped.
Captain!
How's that one?
Her pulse has stabilized.
What should we do?
It's a long shot, but I think we
should try electroshock.
Yes, sir.
She's regained consciousness!
Good.
So for now, we can relax.
Ready?
Yes.
Where am I?
The Underground in Osaka.
In the secret base of a certain organization.
A certain organization...
Osaka?
Nagumo-kun...
One more time?
Yes.
Captain! Captain!
Amano-kun...
Is that you, Chaos?
The Cemetery of Time
Amano Jack...
Th-That voice!
You're... the Queen, aren't you!?
Look well.
This is the place you feared:
the Cemetery of Time.
This is how the Earth's surface looked eons ago.
Those who live here are very ancient.
Not human, nor beast, nor demon.
They hover ambiguously between the Three Realms.
They sorta look familiar.
What they're doing is the same
as what we're doing right now.
The Overfiend resurrected these ancient creatures,
and he made them fight to their own destruction.
Then he separated them into the Three
Realms: Human, Beast, and Demon.
Is that true?
And that's why the Three Realms
are killing each other right now?
The Overfiend is tired of us, so he's
forcing us to destroy ourselves?
Exactly.
And he's attempting to open the path for a new race,
similar to, yet different from, the current three.
He can't!
He can't! He can't!
Our lives are not toys for some god!
You think I'm gonna fucking let him play with us?
Captain!
I knew you wouldn't let me down!
I knew you wouldn't die so easily!
It's a miracle!
Where am I?
Th-This place is...
Amano-kun!
Akemi!
So you came back to life!
What a relief.
What about you? You've been
out for a hundred years.
You look pretty good, considering.
Yes. I feel great!
Like I just woke up from a great sleep.
Well, that's nice, but...
Amano-kun!
We've been through a lot.
Amano-kun, please tell me.
Where is... Nagumo-kun?
Do you know where he is?
Akemi...
I'm sorry, but I don't know where he is right now.
A few days ago, we saw each
other outside Osaka Castle.
But at the time, he was still
the Demon of Destruction,
under the control of the unborn Overfiend.
Seems like you're awake, Amano Jack.
Who the hell are you guys?
A special anti-government task force.
A special anti-government task force?
The military has been crushed, but we're still intact.
We also have weapons.
In violent times like this, we believe we have
to take matters into our own hands.
For that reason, we saved your lives.
Demons have invaded the main entrance.
I repeat...
All units, hurry!
Akemi, don't!
It's dangerous out there!
Don't stop me!
I'm going to find Nagumo-kun.
Damn it, you're so stubborn.
Finding him is nice and all, but
where will you start looking?
That voice...
That guy!
Is he still the Demon of Destruction, even
though the Overfiend has been born?
Nagumo-kun...
Onii-chan!
Megumi-san!
Hey, Megumi!
So you're all right!
Why?
Why won't Nagumo return back to normal?
Nagumo-kun!
Please stop this!
Just stop this already!
A-Akemi...
Nagumo-kun!
Let's be alone together!
Look only at me!
It's Akemi!
Nagumo-kun!
Nagumo-kun...
Nagumo-kun.
You saved me.
Nagumo-kun!
Somewhere deep in your heart,
you still remember me, right?
Then, please remember that time we shared.
The time when you changed into that form,
and the Overfiend was inside my womb.
But back then, I was...
Nagumo-kun.
It's me. You recognize me, don't you?
Can you really kill me with your power?
I still love you even now.
End my life while I still feel this way.
I don't want to live by order of the Overfiend.
I don't want to be his tool anymore.
I won't have it!
If you kill me, the Overfiend will also die.
And you'll die, too.
Let's die!
Nagumo-kun, let's die together!
I don't mind dying if I'm with you!
Please? Nagumo-kun?
Nagumo-kun...
Nagumo...
Nagumo-kun!
Please kill me!
Back then, you weren't able to kill me.
But even when the Overfiend took over your mind,
your heart still belonged to me.
It's Akemi, Nagumo-kun.
It's Akemi!
No matter how you look, no matter what you do,
I'll still be there for you.
So come with me.
Let's return to the way we were.
I'll do anything for you!
But if that's not good enough,
then I'll die together with you.
Nagumo-kun... Nagumo-kun!
Akemi!
No! Let me go, Amano-kun!
Don't do something stupid like that!
Nagumo-kun!
Akemi!
Talking to the Demon of Destruction is useless.
Nagumo can't hear you!
Nagumo-kun...
Wait until the time is right.
Akemi!
Nagumo-kun...
Megumi, take care of Akemi.
I'm gonna go face the Overfiend.
I won't let him get away with this.
Let's settle the score, Overfiend!
Wh-Who the hell are you!?
So you've returned from the Land of the Dead.
I expected that much, Amano Jack.
What the hell is going on!?
How do you know my name!?
Because we have...
met once before, Amano Jack.
Once before?
I don't know who you are,
but you've got shitty manners.
I wanna see the Overfiend!
Oh, fine, I guess I'll have to kill you!
Wh-What's that?
What's that shining thing?
I see!
So the Overfiend is down there.
Hold still!
Those who resist us...
will pay for their sin with death.
Is that... Is that the best you can do?
Lemme show ya the power a
hundred year's grudge can have!
This is the power of Chaos!
How amusing.
So that is the power of Chaos.
Destroy!
Yes, very nice.
Resist if you wish.
Show me a glimpse of brilliant light before you die.
Resist me, Amano Jack.
Wh-What happened?
She disappeared?
This group of guys sure are difficult to understand.
I still can't exactly call this "complete".
Overfiend!
Where are you!?
Answer me!
What's happening?
Wh-What the hell's going on?
Long time no see, Amano Jack.
O-Overfiend?
You came from Akemi's womb.
Don't you have the power to turn
Nagumo back to normal?
Akemi has returned to normal.
So why hasn't Nagumo?
Return him right now!
But I still have use for the Demon of Destruction.
What the hell?
I need to create a new, superior race,
so until the current Three Realms
are completely destroyed,
I cannot return Nagumo to his original form.
Overfiend...
That's just way too harsh!
I know that to a god, the
Three Realms might seem insignificant!
But still,
can't you just give us more time to prove ourselves?
The weak will die by the hand of the strong.
That is the law of nature.
By the power of this law, lifeforms have evolved.
Oh, I see.
So this new race is supposed to kill
us all, and that is god's will, huh?
Sounds pretty rad.
I laid low when you were inside Akemi
and I still had the Queen to consider,
but now you're my enemy!
You're gonna kill us off?
Heh, I'd like to see ya try!
Before you're able to kill us...
we're gonna kill you instead!
Hear me, Overfiend!
The one who they call Amano Jack...
declares war on you!
Overfiend!
Choujin Densetsu Urotsukidouji
The Final Chapter: Part 1