What the hell is this?
It looks like a gigantic cocoon.
Is Kyo-O inside there...?
The missiles... they're headed for Osaka!
Finally the day of pay back has come...
Just wait, Chojin!
You sick bastard!
These missiles will never reach their destination!
Cursed scum! I don't have the time...
to see to you!
Help!
Caesar's palace! Storm Caesar's palace!
Finally the hour of the Makemonos
has come! Down with Caesar!
Let the world know that a new age began!
They reached the palace!
Caesar is still busy with his missiles...
But what if he notes the attack?
Will we still have a chance then?
We can think about that later!
Do you hear that?
The baby cries for help.
I wonder how it wound up in there?
We can clarify that later...
Let's go, we have to conquer the palace.
If we fail to overthrow Caesar
his revenge will be terrible.
What?!
What should we do?
Just wait!
These bastards!
Caesar, the Makemonos revolt.
They already have the prisoner camp under their control.
Doesn't matter we have more important things to do!
But Sir!
Shut up! Pedro, forget about that!
Yes!
Situation report!
What is the status of
Faust and the missiles?
Everything is going according to the plan.
They reached in a minute and 35
seconds the Fuji-sound.
Our fleet is 100 miles before the
Ise-Bucht, on course to Osaka.
The air wing is ready.
Fine... there should be nothing left of Osaka.
And now, Faburil... your time has come.
Do you still think that you can save Chojin?
Münchhausen! What do you plan?
Now you will find out the power of evil!
It's stronger than all your powers.
Missile number 1 is off course!
It's losing altitude...
What?!
With best wishes!
Brother!
Damn...!
My brother is in danger!
Akemi...? Chojin!
What... What happens to me?
It's getting hot inside me...
I'm burning!
The situation demands that I
use also your powers...
Aren't you Amano's sister, are you?
I... how can I help you...?
My powers...?
You are so powerful...
Give it to me, please! I can't stand it! I need it...
Fuck me... fuck me! Please do it!
I'm coming! Oh, I'm coming...!
I'm coming...!
I'm still hot...
Fuck me... now fuck me!
So be it...
I will raise your Chojin-powers!
No! No, please... no!
[Dark magical incantation]
Finally! He is born!
Where did you hide yourself, Faust?
Fool!
I don't fall for the same trick twice.
Give up, Amano!
Death waits for your Chojin!
What do you want to do about that?
Don't you prefer to serve me?
You would like that,
wouldn't you? You bastard!
What...?!
Another missile descended! Another missile descended!
What!? What is Faust doing?!
Münchhausen! You will never be able to realize your plan!
There are only 4 missiles left! And I will get them too!
Didn't you forget something, Amano?
What...?
The time of truth has come! Now
you can prove your strengths!
Damn! This monster is really giant!
Münchhausen! That is only the beginning!
What the hell is he doing there?!
Shit! A dead-end street again!
The sectors A4, B3 and C5 are again under control.
Good! No one is allowed
to reach Caesar's palace.
Shit!
You poor devils...! I will revenge you!
Enko! If it goes on like that we are lost!
What should we do now.
What is the secret of  these people?!
What happened?
Energy falling in turbine 2...
We did it!
That wasn't hard...
What the... What's going on here?
Malfunction in reactor room 3. Turbine
2 destroyed no control anymore!
What?!
The Makemonos must have penetrated there!
Energy falling in turbine 1 and 3.
In this state we can't hold the balance anymore.
The palace is in danger!
Therefore increase the energy in turbine 1 and 3!
The Makemonos keep on penetrating.
They keep getting closer and closer...
Intruders in sector A4 and B5.
They're moving into the palace!
Now do something about that! Am I only surrounded by idiots?!
The palace! They're storming the palace!
Don't panic!
Attack! Don't show any mercy! Our time has come!
You are still alive?!
How you see!
You worm!
What?!
Now only one is left!
We lost contact with the fleet!
What?! To hell with that! What's with the missiles?
Four are destroyed, one still on course.
What about Faburil?
We still get his signal but it's very weak.
Caesar, the signal is
getting stronger again!
I knew it... this creature is unbeatable!
I... I'm coming! I'm coming...!
I'm coming...
Now my power will show itself...
Münchhausen, admit your defeat! You lost! Give up!
Amano! Do you still think you can defeat me?
This beast is still alive...?
Faburil is the personified hatred! Try to destroy him...
and you create even more hate!
Brother...!
Megumi...
Last missile destroyed!
Faburil changed his direction!
That is all done by Chojin! We are lost!
Even Faburil and Kyo-O together aren't strong enough...
to defeat him.
The palace's balance is reconstructed to 89%.
Status is held. State of the supporting-system is still critical.
Find Caesar! Destroy him!
They are in the palace! They're
moving into the headquarters.
Caesar! Caesar!
Caesar, where are you?
Show yourself, Kyo-O!
Kyo-O, who gave you your power?
I can't remember to have testified you.
What...?!
No... that can't be...!
It's like this...! I wait for you in Osaka!
Stop it... Stop it...
Stop it!
We can't obtain a signal
from Faburil anymore!
Part of the palace is collapsing!
Withdraw!
Where are you, Caesar? Show yourself!
Alector... Farewell!
Alector!
Forgive me!
I couldn't avenge you...
It seems I lost everything  even though
everything was well planned...
Till this bastard appeared!
These cursed Makemonos should pay for that!
I congratulate you, Caesar.
Don't be so disappointed...
Since you did manage to create a new world.
Over 20 years have passed
since the great destruction...
and a new being arose like you wanted.
What do you mean by that?!
The Alector-module which you
constructed was a perfect Android.
It's impossible to distinguish her from a human being.
That's right! But I still failed!
Tell me, what will Chojin's realm
look like now?
What will happen to the world as we know it?
Caesar, your task I have analyzed...
every corner of these ruins created by Chojin.
But about the Makemonos
and the Alector-module...
nothing was recorded here.
The world moves in a direction...
which even Chojin couldn't predict.
And more strange is that the
Alector-module carries...
new life in it.
The Makemonos and this new life...
will determine the fate of the mankind...
because they are beyond
the Chojin's imagination.
And because it is Kyo-O who will lead them.
When Chojin and Kyo-O will meet each other in Osaka...
then there will be an answer for everything.
However I won't have this concurrence anymore.
The Makemonos have already
caused too much damage.
This also is fate...
Farewell... Caesar...
Fresh meat!
Buju! Buju!
Buju!
Hey! That bitch is Caesar's daughter!
This small one will make us
heroes among the Makemonos!
Catch her!
Alector!
Himi! Himi!
What happened? What's wrong?
Buju!
What the hell...?
Damn Makemonos! I will never forgive them!
Anything might happen but I
will take them with me into hell!
No...!
Caesar, do you hear me?
No... please, stop it...!
Come out and show yourself!
Show yourself or we kill her!
But first we will have a bit
of fun with your daughter...!
Father, don't come! They will kill you!
It doesn't matter what they do to
me but stay where you are father!
Alector, are you OK?
Daddy's small daughter, eh?
No! Please...!
Stop...! Stop it... please!
Maybe she really wants it...!
Ouch! No, no! Please don't...!
Where are you, Caesar?!
Your small bitch is afraid!
Stop!
We still want to have fun till Caesar appears...
Do you like that?
An iron-hard steel penis, just for you!
When he starts you will be just dead meat!
But we won't kill you yet.
Say that you need it!
I need it...
You need it? You really need it...?
We help you!
Then go...
I want it...
Look at that!
That bitch is already as wet as a whole lake!
Come on let's give it to her!
I... I'll do everything
you want. Everything...
That sounds well!
Then let's take a look at
your juicy, randy pussy!
Come on spread your legs!
Very good...
Hey, what's this?!
Spread your legs if you want to live on!
Yes...!
Hey, she is already very horny!
Hold on, stop it! You hurt me!
Me first! Yes... this is good!
Spread your legs more!
And how does my cock feel?
Do you like it?
Oh... she is so warm... so wet...!
I'm coming...!
Yeah the perfect cock massage!
I want to be next!
No me!
Ouch no! Stop, it hurts!
That hurts... it hurts...!
Stop it!
Caesar!
Too late Caesar! Your daughter is already sucking our cocks!
Alector...!
To hell with you!
Father...
We got him!
We killed Caesar!
Alector was everything what I ever had!
For that I will tear your heads apart!