Current coordinates: 7-12.
Recording runs...
Destination was destroyed,
no survivors.
It is time, Sir.
The hot line...
Indeed!
Hello?
Mr. President...
The rest of our wing arrived
in the target area.
We are ready for the attack.
Which destination?
Osaka, Japan.
Osaka... Japan?
There we located the inferno's origin.
As you command, Sir. Destination: Osaka, Japan.
Good luck.
My mission is completed.
John, what the...
There is not any going back anymore.
He rose and will destroy everything.
Let's do it... a last time!
Destination: Osaka. Program
all rockets on the destination.
Do we really save mankind with this...?
Captain!
An unidentified object approaches!
Speed... 250 Knots!
What?!
It disappeared...
What happened?
It's HE, Nagumo!
To hell with him!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 1
20 years after the destruction a new
order forms out of the ruins.
The apocalypse produced a new race.
Neither human nor animal nor demon...
They are called Makemonos and
are disfigured by the inferno.
What's wrong boy?
Your time hasn't come yet.
I come... Mom,
I don't want wait any longer.
Chojin...
The Chojin! It's the birth of Chojin!
What...?
Amano, what happened?
Why now already...	?
What's the meaning of this?!
What the...! Akemi...?
What happened Akemi?
I have waited for you, Amano.
Are you... Chojin?
How do you do, Amano?
I dreamed of you...
I know.
Why now? Prophecy says
you should be born in 100 years.
Was it a lie? What happened?
That, which had to happen.
In the east the evil was born
It will try to kill me.
Why does it want to kill you?
Aren't you immortal...?
Everyone can die... I'm not an exception...
Currently my enemies are very strong...
Maybe there can't arise
a better world in this generation.
Amano! You must protect
me from the evil!
I beg you, Amano!
But... how do I recognize the evil?
Chojin!
Brother!
Seems a Bastard hunts the Chojin...
The Chojin...?
Where always there is a God...
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is...
is also "Kyo-O" not far.
Where am I supposed to search for the evil...
I will try it in the east...
There it will have to meet me...
and then I will destroy it...!
Human women have a deliciously tender skin...
That feels heavenly...
Now you will pay for
your superciliousness...!
Buju...! That is our booty...!
In this realm all
women belong to me.
Evil of the east!
Disappear!
It has been a long time since
I fucked a human woman...
We will have much fun together!
I can hardly await it.
No! Stop it!
Already again... what the hell
is the meaning of this...?
Caesar's troops!
Caesar! Caesar!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O.
Now you are mine.
Don't let him flee or you will
pay for it with your lives.
Catch him!
Please take me with you!
Am I your nurse?
Watch how you can manage it.
Caesar's troops aren't a joke.
Take me to Kyo-O...
I want to use his magic power
for myself. I implore Kyo-O!
Where is he? Take me to his trail!
Here you are, Faust.
Caesar, my Lord.
He escaped again...!
My Lord, I have an idea.
Soon Kyo-O will be your prisoner.
Fine. I can hardly wait.
Chojin in Osaka is the only one
who can endanger our plan.
However if we gain the power
to destroy him...
nothing can stop us.
Yes, Caesar, we will conquer Chojin
and will rule the world.
By the way, is our small one
ready for his mission?
Don't worry...
Everything is going as planned.
The heart, which was torn
out of Nagumo's body,..
is fed with hatred of thousands
of murder victims...
But it still will take time time
until he is ready.
Stay up! Pull yourself together!
Pal... give me some water...
That guy is almost dead.
Out of the way with you!
Grace... please grace...
Damn...
Dumbass do you want to die
as well?! We must survive.
Listen to me, your unworthy!
If you want to live keep on working.
Work for Caesar!
Move! Work!
Makemonos... poor creatures.
Born while the three worlds died.
Why does my father hate
them so much?
Alector... what are you doing here
all alone in the dark, darling?
Father!
Do you still wonder about the underworld?
When will you finally show me this world?
That's nothing for you to see...
Your beautiful skin would
suffer from the air there.
You shouldn't go anywhere near the scum there.
You are my only daughter and I want you...
to stay with me forever.
You shouldn't go away from me...
You shouldn't meet anyone...
You are my single, beloved daughter...
Do you understand me, Alector?
Yes... father!
I will always be your obedient daughter...
Alector, my sweet child.
Bastard!
Is any one else disturbed
by my manners?!
Please... leave my pub.
This depends on you.
Seems today is my lucky day...
Could this freak be Kyo-O?
He doesn't seem to be much
of an opponent for Chojin.
Still there is something about him...
But I don't know what...
Buju... we searched for you.
Who on earth are you?
I don't know you.
We are the servants of
the priest of Kyoto.
We come to you as emissaries of the Gods.
You are a chosen one, Buju.
Me, a chosen one?
Yes, Buju.
At full moon, in the valley of the
eagle, the prophecy will be fulfilled.
What was that...? Come now...!
Yes...!
Chosen by the Gods? Seems
in the end it's worth...
observing this guy.
But who is the priest of Kyoto?
Amano!
Mimi!
How did you find me?
My lust guided me!
You already need it again?
Yes and this time you won't get away!
Well these two have their fun.
Why shouldn't we?
Stop talking and give it to me!
Come on I need it!
You are already wet...
I want too...
Hard...
Suck hard, Babe...
And now the main attraction...
Harder...
That's it...
I'm coming...!
You were great, Buju...
Who are you...?!
What do you want, witch?
Shut up! I have still a surprise for you.
Faust, my Lord! We have something to enjoy!
Hold it, wait!
What the hell is going on here?
Amano!
You know my name, bitch?!
Out of my way!
Why? Do I disturb you?
Have fun, small one...
Amano, are you OK?
Why didn't you finish her?
She surprised me...
Wanna fuck, Amano?
Seems someone else also search for Kyo-O...
I wonder, who...
What...? He isn't Kyo-O?!
No, Caesar. This Makemono isn't Kyo-O.
Indeed folks call him "The evil of the east" but he...
isn't the one we search for.
If I shall die then kill me fast...
A Makemono isn't worth such an effort...
Interesting...
He isn't Kyo-O yet a special power comes from him...
We can find Kyo-O with his help...
Really...?
Buju... You sure will help us to find Kyo-O, won't you?
I never heard of this before.
Even if I knew about Kyo-O I wouldn't tell you.
You will help us trust me...
You will die if you refuse...
OK OK! You win...
Nothing can stop us now...
What? Amano?
Yes!
So he is involved too...
Take the rat in it's hole.
It looks like my life ends here. In this darkened cell,..
I will die as Caesars slave.
Are you a Makemono?
What...?
Who dares...?! Show yourself!
Poor creature...
What is she doing here...?
What do you want?
Your bleeding...
I know but I'm still strong.
Therefore pay attention!
Yes, King Buju.
King Buju?!
King Buju, I have a request. Please show me the underworld!
The underworld? My home?
Yes!
The price is my freedom and your virginity.
Hold on!
I can hardly await it!
I will fuck Caesar's daughter...!
An adequate price...
for that I will show her the dark and dirty underworld.
What?! Buju escaped?!
Yes, my Lord.
Still more bad news?
I can't find your daughter anywhere...
What?! Alector?!
Take a closer look...
That's the underworld.
Even animals deserve a better treatment.
The wretchedness is pitiful...
What do you think, why are we treated so badly...?
Caesars troops would like to be as strong and potent as me...
They just have a lack of courage in their bones and dicks...!
Who is once here won't escape slightly anymore.
Fate played a stupid joke with us...
How could that happen?
The Princess and Buju escaped together...!
But we will find them.
I know their plan...
Alector!
Anyone here?
No one?
All this was constructed by imbecile believers.
But God... is dead!
However now to you.
It's time to keep your promise.
Sit down.
Spread your legs...
Wide from each other, further!
Very good, Princess... and now
move your butt, Your Highness...
Come on, a little more...
Only human women can move so randily...
Tears come to me from joy.
Buju... may we do this anyway?
You do that very skillfully...
I have never had such a small, submissive piece yet.
Show me more, Buju...
Wait, sweety... You will get what you desire.
Yes, there... great!
Oh Buju... Oh Buju!
An always horny bastard, this Buju.
What was that?
Buju, what's wrong?
Crying human! I send you to hell!
Please! Don't hurt him!
Don't do it!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Who are you?
You are in my way!
I will end that pitiful yelling.
Don't!
Himi... Himi...
Buju...
It laughs.. It laughs when I touch it.
Oh, how sweet!
Caesar, we found them!
They are in the eagle's valley.
Bring Alector back to me, UNHARMED!
Buju you can kill.
Take care of my daughter.
Buju, the temple is surrounded.
Release Alector!
First this human and now Caesar's troops...
Not a good day for Buju.
Buju, if you release Alector we will spare your life.
Let Alector go... now!
So many assholes... and all because of me.
Buju!
He will kill you! He kills everyone who crosses his way.
Let's flee together! We will be save in your world!
They won't kill me.
They want to use my powers to find Kyo-O...
I love you, Buju! I want to stay with you forever.
You want to stay with a Makemono like me?
Really...?
Stop it!
Don't shoot!
Alector...
Please, spare Buju! Please... father...
Please, I beg you...
Buju...! What did you do to Alector?
Buju!
You mustn't die...
Oh no! You are...?!
Buju...
Alector, I will never forget you...
Alector, I created you...
We don't need Kyo-O anymore...
because our creature will be soon ready.
Save Alector's body, Faust.
Yes. And Buju?
Kill him!
Thanks...
Why must I die for a human like you...
After you've got Alector we will withdraw.
Something is wrong here. Who is that baby?
What's going on here...?
What is that?!
It's Nagumo! Why does he return?
He wants that child! Then this baby must be...
He is the the true Lord of Chaos - the Kyo-O!
Mother... He awoke. I will have to combat him.
I'm sorry, Mother.