本字幕由輕之國度製作 僅供試看之用
如喜歡本作品 請支持Z版
片源：黑血  繁體：偉哥
Until I entered high school two months ago,
I didn't know...
The dampness of my uniform's hem,
soaked by someone else's umbrella...
The smell of naphthalene,
clinging to someone's suit...
The warm body pushed up against my back...
The chill breeze of the air conditioner
against my face...
- Shinjuku... Shinjuku station...
- Thank you for riding with us.
When I was little the sky was closer...
So much closer.
That's why I like the rain,
as with it comes the smell of the sky.
And often, on rainy mornings,
instead of transferring to the subway,
I exit out the station gates.
June
Chocolate, and... beer?
But, I think I've seen her somewhere...
- Here.
- Thank you.
U-Um... Have we met before?
N-No.
I'm sorry, my mistake.
It's okay.
Maybe it's fitting...
Narukami no sukoshi toyomite
(A faint clap of thunder)
sashi kumori
(Clouded skies)
Ame mo furanu ka?
(Perhaps rain comes)
kimi wo todomemu
(If so, will you stay here with me?)
The Garden of Words
This morning, the JMA has declared the start of
the rainy season in Kyushu,
5 days earlier than average.
Nagasaki, Saga, Kumamoto,
and Kagoshima prefectures
expect strong rains over a wide area.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I bought croquettes.
Great. Dinner will be ready soon.
Thank you.
Where's Ma?
Ran out.
Lucky us, we get all the croquettes
to ourselves.
She left a letter saying not to go
looking for her.
But maybe...
Leave her be.
I'm sure she'll be back after fighting
with her boyfriend.
I've picked out a place.
I'll be leaving next month.
Living alone?
With my girlfriend.
Don't think that's why mom ran out?
You told her yesterday, right?
I wish she could just let her children go,
you know?
She's the one who's making the rounds
dating younger men, damn it.
Oh, yeah? Well then I'm gonna go live
with my boyfriend!
She's got those youthful looks, after all.
That's 'cause she's never worked hard
her entire life.
You're the one who's been piling on the years.
All done.
You do the dishes. I've aged enough.
Won't you be glad to have more space?
'Suppose so.
Help me move, 'kay?
Sure.
Hey, have you heard of this?
What is this, a haiku?
It's a tanka.
As if.
Ask Ma when she gets back.
On sunny mornings, I transfer to the subway and
head here, like I'm supposed to.
But I think to myself
“This is not what I should be doing now. ”
Rain...
Hello.
Hey...
No school today?
And your office... Is it closed today?
I'm skipping work again...
And drinking beer in the park in the morning.
Drinking beer alone isn't good for
your health.
You need to eat something with it.
You know a lot for a high school kid.
It's not me. My mom's the drinker.
I've got snack food.
Want some?
You just thought to yourself
“This woman's a freak,” didn't you?
No, I...
It's okay. We're human, after all.
We've all got our little quirks.
Maybe...
Definitely.
Okay, it's about time for me to go.
Heading to school now?
I've decided to only skip school
on rainy mornings.
Then, maybe we'll see each other again.
Perhaps, when it's raining.
It was the first day of Kanto's rainy season.
Entrance Exam
About Tuition
A shoemaker?
I know it seems out of touch,
but I enjoy creating designs and making shoes.
Of course, I'm still terrible at it.
Of course...
But despite it all,
I want to make it my career... if I can.
I've never told anyone this before.
Do you have any idea how late you are?
You know why I've called you here, right?
Hey...
Evenings, before I went to sleep...
Mornings, in the moment I woke up...
I realized I was praying for rain.
I realized that on sunny days,
I was in a terrible, childish place.
With nothing but impatience.
She exists in a world of working adults,
so very far away from me...
To me she represents nothing less
than the very secrets of the world.
Honestly, there are only two things
I know for sure.
One: She must think of me and my
15 years as just some mere kid.
And two: Making shoes is the only thing
that will lead me out of this place.
Please stay behind the yellow line
for your safety.
Please be careful of the closing doors.
Good morning.
I thought you might not come today.
It's a miracle you haven't been fired yet.
Wow! Is that a shoe design?
Hey!
I can't see?
It's not something worth showing.
Really?
Yes, really.
Come on, sit down over there.
I'm going to eat breakfast.
Would you like to join me?
Okay, but I've brought my own.
You made it yourself?
What? I cook sometimes, you know.
Oh?
Then let's make a trade.
Wait, I'm not really that good a...
...cook, you know.
It's your own fault.
That's a side of you I didn't expect.
What?
Sorry. But it's tasty in its own way.
It's got... bite.
Don't patronize me.
Can I have another?
Hurry UP!
Wait, bro!
Takao, be careful.
Happy birthday, Mom!
Thank you.
What could the three of you have gotten me?
Hey... Do you think it's too late for me?
And you know what?
I could actually taste the food.
So your taste disorder has improved?
I wouldn't go that far.
But just a little while ago, all I could taste
was alcohol and chocolate.
I think you deciding to just quit
was really for the best.
Maybe so.
You speak to me so gently,
like you're touching something fragile.
But back then, when I found it hard
even to breathe,
you didn't believe me. You only listened to
the voices around you.
Then we'll start the paperwork
for you leaving after the holiday.
I'll notify the higher-ups.
Okay. Sorry to cause you all this trouble
even after we split up.
I'm glad, really...
About that old woman you met.
You know, the one you keep talking about
who brings her lunch box to the park.
It seems like you've really struck a chord.
Yeah, get some rest.
Ever since then...
...I've been nothing but lies.
Rain...
It's raining again today in Kanto.
Here at Shinjuku Station's south exit,
the commuters all have umbrellas in their hands.
July
Here, this is for you.
For me?
I've always ended up
eating your food, see...
And you said you wanted it, right?
This book isn't cheap...
Thank you... very much.
It's my pleasure.
Um...
I'm actually making a pair of shoes right now.
Wow... A pair for yourself?
I haven't decided whose shoes yet...
They're women's shoes.
But, I haven't been able to
get them right, and...
You know... Before I knew it,
I wasn't able to walk properly anymore.
Are you talking about your job?
Yeah... About a lot of things.
I don't know anything about her.
Her job, her age...
What worries she carries...
Even her name...
And yet I can't help but be charmed by her.
The rainy season is officially over 10 days
later than normal in the Kanto region.
The current temperature in the city
is 26 degrees.
Like someone just flicked a switch,
the sunny days came one after another.
Oh sure, now I think to myself
“I'm glad that he's not skipping class anymore”...
But in reality...
...I wish the rainy season had never ended.
This park sure is big.
I can't believe we're in Shinjuku.
Oh, pardon us.
Go ahead.
This is the Japanese gardens, right?
Where should we go next?
Isn't there a greenhouse?
Let's check it out.
It's like a totally different place
on sunny days.
Thanks for the help.
Hey, why don't you eat dinner with us, Takao?
Sorry, but I've got my part-time job today.
This late?
And I don't want to impose.
The opposite! I'm going to be living with him
from now on, so just this once...
I can hear you.
Well then, see you later.
He's a cute kid.
Did you notice his shoes?
They're handmade.
What? Seriously?
Just some ugly moccasins, though.
He's got a bright future, doesn't he?
I wonder if he'd make shoes for me?
Who knows? Teenagers' interests
change on a whim...
My brother moved out, and
the rainless days continued.
I had no excuse to head to that place.
August
And then, it was summer vacation.
I worked part-time almost
every day over the summer.
Hmm, maybe chicken with cashew nuts?
Looks good to me.
- We'll order it.
- Thank you very much.
I wanted to earn what I could
for tuition to a vocational school.
Tools and leather cost money, too.
Sure, I missed her, but...
I think it's clinging to those feelings
that is keeping me a little kid.
That's why I've decided to create shoes
that'll make her want to get up and walk.
What~ will the weather~ be tomorrow~?
I'm not a bit smarter at the age of 27
than I was at the age of 75.
I've always been here,
stuck in the same place.
September
It's just like Tsukishima...
to have got that confused for a week!
English class is no big deal.
That's cause Kiso's a pushover.
Akizuki!
Hey, long time no see.
Looks like you guys got a tan.
Yeah, we went to the beach a bunch.
You're still as pale as ever.
What'd you do over summer break?
Worked the whole time.
The whole time?
That's a lonely way to spend
your high school days.
School, part-time job, housework.
I skip school sometimes!
Now that you mention it,
you are late a lot, Akizuki.
Yup, this guy never shows up
for 1st period when it rains.
I've got a condition where I can't ride
the subway on rainy mornings.
Whatever, weirdo.
Teacher's Office
Miss Yukino?
Miss Yukino!
Sato...
Miss Yukino...
Sato, save it for later.
Miss Yukino!
- Same goes for the rest of you.
- I'm sorry, everyone.
I'll be here until after 5th period.
After that, I'd be happy to.
Yuki came to school?
You didn't hear about Yuki quittin'?
No. I didn't even know who she is.
You have old man Takehara for lit, right?
Yuki was always having trouble
with the 3rd year girls.
Yeah, but Miss Yukino
didn't do anything wrong.
Someone's boyfriend fell for Miss Yukino,
and as payback everyone in the class
treated Miss Yukino terribly.
They spread so many rumors
even her parents heard about them.
It went so far she couldn't
come to school any more.
Yuki's just too kind. She should have
brought it right to the police.
We told Mr. Ito again and again!
But he didn't want to make trouble
for the school in public.
Hey, what's the matter?
Those upperclassmen...
Do you know their names?
Miss Yukino!
He totally sucks at it.
You're so cruel.
But man, you sure go through 'em.
What do you want, frosh?
Are you the 3rd year, Aizawa?
An admirer?
Who the hell are you?
It seems like Miss Yukino is quitting.
Huh?
Like I care about what happens to
that slutty hag.
Who does this guy think he is?
Huh? What's this?
What's your deal?
Let's go tell a teacher...
Never seen this kid before.
Who are you? Fallen for that old hag?
What a creep! Does he even know
how old she is?
Poor guy, she must have tricked him.
She might go for him now, though.
Since she ain't a teacher no more.
Damn straight.
You should thank us.
I'm waiting for the rain.
Narukami no sukoshi toyomite
(A faint clap of thunder)
furazu to mo
(Even if rain comes not)
warewa tomaramu
(I will stay here)
imoshi todomeba
(Together with you)
Yes, that's the correct answer.
That's the right response to the tanka
I told you when we first met.
If it rains, I wonder if you will be staying here?
In response to that verse, I answer...
Even if it doesn't rain, I will be here.
It was in the classic Japanese
literature textbook.
Miss Yukino...
I'm sorry...
I thought you would realize
I was a classic literature teacher.
I mean, everyone at school knows about me.
But you're always off in your
own little world, aren't you?
Hey, what happened to your face?
I was acting like you
and drank too much beer.
Then I tripped and fell on the
Yamanote line platform.
Oh, my!
Just kidding. I got in a fight, that's all.
Look... It looks like we just
swam across the river.
I think this might...
...this might be...
...the happiest...
...time of my life.
Yukino...
Yes?
I think I've fallen in love with you.
Not Yukino... Miss Yukino, remember?
I'm going to be moving next week.
Back to my hometown in Shikoku.
I made the decision a while back.
I was practicing how to walk on my own,
there in that place.
Even if I'm barefoot...
So then...
So I want to thank you for
everything, Akizuki.
Um, thank you for lending me these clothes.
I'll get changed now.
But yours aren't...
Excuse me... I'm going home.
Thank you for your hospitality.
I made this lunch for myself,
but I made too much.
So if you'd like...
I haven't decided whose shoes yet...
They're women's shoes.
I was acting like you
and drank too much beer
Then I tripped and fell on the
Yamanote line platform.
Narukami no sukoshi toyomite
(A faint clap of thunder)
furazu to mo
(Even if rain comes not)
warewa tomaramu (I will stay here)
imoshi todomeba (Together with you)
Um...
Yukino, please forget what I said earlier.
I was wrong... I hate you after all.
Ever since we first met, you struck me...
...like a person I should avoid.
Drinking beer in the morning,
spouting off some random tanka at me...
You listen all day to other people talking,
yet never say a peep about yourself...
You knew I was a student, didn't you?
That's just unfair!
If I'd known you were a teacher,
I would have never told you about the shoes.
After all, you think
I'll never amount to anything!
So why didn't you say anything to me?
You thought maybe you'd humor
the little kid's fantasies for a while?
Tell me I'll never live up
to my expectations!
Tell me I'll never measure up to my dreams!
You knew from the very beginning!
So tell me, god damn it!
Tell me I'm in your way!
Tell me that little kids should
run along to school!
Tell me that you hate me!
You...
It's because you act like that!
You never say what's important!
You pretend it's none of your business!
You've been living your whole life, alone!!
Every morning!
Every morning I put on my suit
to go to school...
But I was... scared...
I just couldn't go...
In that place...
You...
You... saved me!
I lived on with feelings frozen,
never expressed in words,
言葉にできず凍えたままで
人前ではやさしく生きていた
And I clumsily held you in my
arms on a rainy night
しわよせで  こんなふうに雑に
雨の夜にきみを抱きしめてた
Street flyers and broken lamps,
everybody was rushing back
道路わきのビラと壊れた常夜燈
街角ではそう  だれもが急いでた
It's not you but me who is to blame.
I couldn't hide my own impulsiveness
きみじゃない  悪いのは自分の激しさを
かくせないぼくのほうさ
Lady, you started running through
a deserted station
Lady きみは雨にけむる
すいた駅を少し走った
どしゃぶりでもかまわないと
Unconcerned about getting soaked
from the pouring rain
ずぶぬれでもかまわないと
The sight of you splashing through
puddles disappears
しぶきあげるきみが消えてく
Morning comes quicker in the back alleys,
so I have to get hold of you now
路地裏では朝が早いから
今のうちにきみをつかまえ
To say, Don't go away, don't go away
行かないで  行かないで
そう言うよ
Summer ended, and it came time to
switch to our winter uniforms...
I got terrible marks on my final exams...
I wasted who knows how many
pieces of expensive leather...
I worked part-time over winter break as well...
And every time I added a layer
to my clothing,
I wondered to myself...
how was she doing?
I don't have enough strength anymore
別々に暮らす  泣きだしそうな空を
にぎりしめる強さは今はもうない
Voice: Miyu lrino / Kana Hanazawa To grab on
to the sky that's welled up with tears
Voice:
Miyu lrino / Kana Hanazawa
変わらずいる心のすみだけで傷つくような
きみならもういらない
You are strong enough not to feel hurt
because of my unchanging heart
Original Story/Screenplay: Makoto Shinkai Lady. All wet
from the rain, you looked into my eyes for a moment
Lady きみは雨にぬれて
ぼくの眼を少し見ていた
Character Design/Animation Director: Kenichi Tsuchiya
Unconcerned about getting soaked from the pouring rain
どしゃぶりでもかまわないと
ずぶぬれでもかまわないと
口笛ふくぼくがついてく
Background Art Director Hiroshi
Takiguchi Whistling, I walk after you
I have known you too much, just like
the night when we first quarreled,
ずいぶんきみを知りすぎたのに
初めて争った夜のように
To say, Don't go away, don't go away
行かないで 行かないで
そう言うよ
Color Setting:
Yoko Miki
Composite:
Makoto Shinkai
Edit: Makoto Shinkai When I head out the
gates and my shirt's shoulder's are dry,
肩が乾いたシャツ改札を出る頃
きみの町じゃもう雨は小降りになる
Sound Director: Haru Yamada
It' no longer rains much in your town
今日だけが明日に続いてる
Music: KASHIWA Daisuke
Today, only, continues into tomorrow
こんなふうに  きみとは終われない
Ending Theme Song “Rain” Written and Composed by Senri Oe Arranged by Makoto Minakawa
/ Akifumi Tada Performed by Motohiro Hata That's how you and I can never end
Ending Theme Song “Rain” Written and Composed by Senri Oe Arranged
by Makoto Minakawa / Akifumi Tada Performed by Motohiro Hata
Lady, even now you still
Lady きみは今もこうして
don't even open up a little umbrella...
小さめの傘もささずに
Production: CoMix Wave Films Unconcerned
about getting soaked from the pouring rain
どしゃぶりでもかまわないと
ずぶぬれでもかまわないと
Production: CoMix Wave Films
しぶきあげるきみが消えてく
Morning comes quicker in the back alleys,
so I have to get hold of you now
路地裏では朝が早いから
今のうちにきみをつかまえ
To say, Don't go away, don't go away
行かないで  行かないで
そう言うよ
Unconcerned about getting soaked
from the pouring rain
どしゃぶりでもかまわないと
ずぶぬれでもかまわないと
口笛ふくぼくがついてく
Whistling, I walk after you
Producer: Noritaka Kawaguchi I have known you too
much, just like the night when we first quarreled,
ずいぶんきみを知りすぎたのに
初めて争った夜のように
All rights reserved by Shinkai Creative / CoMix
Wave Films To say, Don't go away, Don't go away
行かないで  行かないで
そう言うよ
Director: Makoto Shinkai
This letter has gotten quite long
without me even realizing it.
沒料到會寫得這麼長
謝謝你讀完它
Thanks so much for reading it all...
希望秋月快樂
溫暖的季節早日到來
I hope you are doing well, Akizuki.
I wish the warm days of Spring come soon.
雪野百香里
- Yukari Yukino
I was practicing how to walk, too.
I think that now.
回望當初  那時我一定也一直在
訓練自己邁步
One day, when I can walk
much farther on my own...
如果有一天
能夠走得更穩更遠了
...I will go see her.
就去見她吧