Avril Lavigne
Let me Go
love once hung on the wall
Used to mean something
But now it means nothing
The echoes are gone in the hall
But I still remember
the pain of December
Oh, there isn't one thing left you could say
I'm sorry it's too late
I'm breaking free from these memories
Gotta let it go, just let it go
I've say goodbye set it all on fire
Gotta let it go,just let it go
oh , oh
You came back to find I was gone
That place is empty
like the hole that was left in me
Like we were nothing at all
It's not that you meant to be
Thought we were meant to be
Oh, there isn't one thing left you could say
I'm sorry it's too …
I'm breaking free from these memories
Gotta let it go,just let it go
I've said goodbye, set it all on fire
Gotta let it go, just let it go
I let it go (and now I know)
A brand new life (this tale is rude)
Where it's right (You always know)
So this time, I won't let it go
There's only one thing left here to say
Love's never too late !
I've broken free from these memories
I've let it go, I've let it go
And two goodbyes,lend you this new life
Don't let me go, don't let me go
Oh,  Oh,  Oh
Don't let me go, don't let me go, don't let me go...
Won't let you go
Don't let me go