## ["Sweet Emotion" By Aerosmith]
# Sweet #
# Emotion #
# Talk about things
and nobody cares #
# Wearin' out the things
that nobody wears #
# You're callin' my name
but I gotta make clear #
# I can't say, baby
where I'll be in a year #
# Some sweat-hoggin' mama
with a face like a gent #
# Said my get up and go
must-a got up and went #
# Well, I got good news
She's a real good liar #
# 'Cause a backstagin' boogie
set your pants on fire #
# Sweet #
- # Emotion #
- [ Bell Ringing ]
- I'm headed this way.
- Oh.
- Later.
- So what did we decide?
- About what?
- About tonight?
Oh, uh-- Look, I'll probably get,
you know, hung up with the guys.
- Maybe, you know--
Why don't we meet at the party?
- Okay.
- Wouldn't want you waitin' around
all night for me anyway.
- All right.
- Cool. See ya later?
- Bye.
Bye.
[ Woman On P.A., Indistinct ]
- Slater-son.
- Hey, man.
[ Hissing ]
- How's it goin' ?
- Fixin' to be a lot better, man.
- What time is your party, man?
- 9:30, man.
9:30. Hmm.
Okay, um...
I'll be there, man.
- [ Chuckles ]
- See ya later, alligator.
Wait, wait !
I gotta cruise by
this afternoon...
on a little business,
if you know what I'm talkin' about.
[ Boy ]
That's what you're talkin' about.
That's what
I'm talkin' about.
Oh, man,
I'm fuckin' wasted.
Walkin' down the hall
by myself.
Smokin' a "J" with 50 elves.
- Later.
- Woodward. Bernstein.
Guess that makes you Deep Throat.
- So, is this a smoked or liquid lunch?
- Hey.
- Smoked, right?
- [ Chuckles ]
- Are we gonna play poker tonight?
- Count me out.
- Sure.
- I'll probably be going
to Pickford's party.
We should do somethin' like that.
Goodwin's off on the senior trip.
- We can play poker anytime.
- Go to a party?
- Mike. Cynthia.
- Come on. Don't worry about it.
I don't feel comfortable
at those kinds of things.
- Pick us up at 8:00.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be all right.
- I guess we're going
to the party then.
- Okay.
- All right.
[ Sighing ] Oh, Mike. I gotta
tell you about this dream I had.
- Oh, yeah?
- But, um...
- you gotta promise not to tell anyone.
- Yeah, sure.
- Say, "I promise."
- Oh, Jesus.
- I promise not to tell anyone.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay, there I am,
and I'm gettin' it on...
- [ Snickering ]
- with this perfect female body.
- Uh-huh.
But--
[ Sighing ]
- What? What?
- I can't say.
Come on, man. You can't give
a buildup like that and not deliver.
A perfect female body.
It's not a bad start.
But the head of
Abraham Lincoln.
- Aaah.
- I mean, the hat and the beard.
- Oh, well. Best not think
too deeply on this one, right?
- Best not.
I gotta get some stuff
from Mr. Birchfield.
- See ya in a few minutes.
- Right. Sorry.
[ Girl ]
Gilligan's transistor radio.
That was a good one.
What about that one where that sexy
surfer guy catches that huge wave?
- Do you remember that?
- Oh, yeah !
- The Mosquitos. Remember that?
- [ Boy ] Pink, let's go.
They were a rock group. Ginger and
Mary Ann formed their own group--
I can't go until Miss Wilk gets here,
so get Benny...
and check me out on the way back.
-What?
-Coach gave me something to give to you.
- [ Pink ] They're really doin' this.
- Yeah.
He wants 'em all back
by the end of the day.
Can you believe that?
- And everybody's signing it?
- Just to get him off our backs.
The coach is just
a big fuckin' asshole.
You sign it, never think about it again.
Just let it go.
You're gonna make a big deal
outta this, aren't ya?
You're gettin' air
from there, man. It's no good.
You see this?
It's gotta be tight.
Put some gum around the base
to get a good hit.
[ Snoring ]
[ Whispering ]
Slate.
Benny.
[ Slater ] I ain't believin' that shit
about Bonham's one-hour drum solo.
One hour on drums? You couldn't
handle that shit on strong acid.
We're gonna go to the bathroom.
Could you let Miss Wilk know?
All right.
This is totally amazing.
"I voluntarily agree
to not indulge in any alcohol,
drugs or engage
in any other illegal activity...
that may in any way jeopardize
the years of hard work...
we as a team have
committed to our goal...
of a championship season in '76."
What bullshit.
- Guys are actually signing this crap?
- Apparently.
What are they gonna do next,
give you guys urine tests?
I didn't know drugs and alcohol
were such a big problem...
that they had to resort
to neo-McCarthyism.
They're just afraid some of us
might be having too good a time.
It's the old
age-suppressing-youth thing.
- Neo-McCarthism. I like that.
- That's good, Tommy.
And there you guys were in class
trying to list all the
Gilligan's Island episodes...
without even
a hint of irony.
What the hell
are you talkin' about?
- You weren't
thinking about it, were you?
- Gilligan's Island?
It's what's called
a male pornographic fantasy.
- Oh my--
- Think about it !
You're basically alone
on a deserted island with two
readily available women:
one a seductive
sex goddess type,
the other a healthy girl-next-door type
with a nice butt.
So guys have it all--
the Madonna and the whore.
Women get nothing.
We get a geek,
an overweight middle-aged guy,
some nerdy scientific type.
- I mean--
- The professor is sexy.
[ Don ]
Pink ! Come on, man.
We're off to raise some hell.
Look at that !
[ Benny ]
Let's go kick some ass !
Hey, you guys.
You guys, wait up.
- What?
- Benny, I have a favor to ask ya.
-What do ya need?
-Take it easy on my brother this summer.
- All of you.
- Mitch Kramer?
- Yeah, Mitch Kramer.
- Yeah, yeah. I'm gonna
give him a beating...
- Ow !
- he'll never forget !
Just don't get him more than
the other guys, any of you.
- He's kinda little.
- You got our word, sis.
- Little brother'll be okay.
- Thanks.
See you guys. Ow !
- Benny ! These guys, I don't know.
- Oh, you love it.
There's just a little bit of bullshit
in all that, right?
- Major bullshit. He's a dead man.
He's fuckin' dead !
- Shotgun !
# # [ Rock 'N' Roll On Car Radio ]
[ Benny ] Check it out. I been
waitin' three long years for this.
Those junior high kids
are dead meat. I promise.
We're gonna beat 'em !
- Oh, yeah.
- [ Engine And Radio Stop ]
Okay, you freshman fucks,
listen up !
It's your lucky day.
Usually you spend your freshman summer
getting your asses busted...
and running
for your worthless little lives.
But this year, because we
feel so sorry for you,
we're gonna take it easy on you...
and save us all a lot of time.
So if you meet here--
right here--
after school today,
you'll only get one lick
from each of us.
But you run like cowards,
well, it's open season
all summer long, boys.
Oh, yeah, Mitch Kramer?
Mitchie? Mitchie,
Mitchie, Mitchie !
- [ All Laughing ]
- We're lookin' for you, pal.
Your ass'll be purple
before the day is over.
Have a nice afternoon.
[ Kissing Noise ]
[ Laughing ]
You better get outta town.
Go spend the summer
with your grandparents or somethin'.
[ Engine Revving ]
Hey, man. You are gonna show up
to our game tonight.
I'm pitching.
I kinda have to.
-How should we inscribe your tombstone?
-[ Laughing ]
- How 'bout "Bent over" ?
- [ Mitch ] Yeah, right, pissant.
- Why aren't they
after anybody else?
- [ Tommy ] They are, man.
- Believe me.
- [ Boy #2 ] I know, man.
- Come on, man. Hop on.
- Let's go, boy.
# # [ lndistinct Car Radio ]
- [ Engine Stops ]
- [ Pink ] Shit.
- [ Car Doors Opening, Closing ]
- Hey, Coach.
So tell me.
Any of you girls gonna be ready
to play football this fall?
- Oh, yeah.
- I don't know, Coach.
I've been doing so good
in English classes,
I figured I'd
become a writer.
- What do you think about that?
- [ Laughing ]
You wouldn't know how to write
your name if it wasn't
stenciled on your locker.
Seriously, everybody. Don't go
getting soft on me this summer.
You're sitting around the pool all day,
chasing the muff around.
- Break down !
- Uh !
Hell, man. My grandmother's quicker
and tougher than you pansies.
Course she's 6'3", 250
and runs a 4.5 40.
- [ lndistinct Chatter ]
- What's the matter with you, Floyd?
Quarterbacks don't have to do
what their coaches say?
Dawson, did you give him
that pledge sheet?
- Huh?
- The pledge sheet.
Did you give it to him?
Yeah, Coach,
it's right here.
If you could get that to us by the end
of the day, we'd feel a lot better.
- You guys see that he does.
- All right, Coach.
- Randy Floyd.
- Shit.
Before next fall,
you're in need of a serious
attitude adjustment, young man.
You better get
your priorities straight.
And watch out with that other crowd
you're runnin' with.
Don't think
I haven't noticed. Hey !
I want that piece of paper
on my desk...
before you leave here today,
do you hear me?
Attitude adjustment.
You know what I mean?
Priorities.
Runs with that bad crowd !
- Bad people.
- Watch yourself.
I've got Coach's
and everybody else's...
attitude-adjusted priorities...
right here.
- Yeah, that's good.
- Yeah.
[ Car Approaching ]
- [ Don ]
Did you hear O'Bannion flunked?
- [ Pink ] What a dumbshit.
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Engine Stops ]
Woo ! You all ready to bust some ass?
[ Laughs ]
What's up, Don, Benny, Melvin?
Good to see ya.
- See ya in about half an hour.
- Yeah.
Hey. We gotta take your truck.
I'm low on gas.
- We're gonna take my truck.
- Yeah.
- Okay? Good.
What are you doing,
picking up trash?
I was waiting for one of them
idiot coaches to piss me off again.
I think you take
the whole thing too personally.
You just gotta--
You gotta shake it off.
Don, have you ever thought
about why we play football?
How many times have you
gotten laid strictly because
you're a football player?
I don't know.
A few, probably.
A few?
All I'm sayin' is...
I bet we could do just as well
if we were in a band or something.
- Look, I gotta put in
a final appearance, so--
- Wait a minute.
Who you got going
in there? Shh.
[ Whispering ]
Vicky. Come on. Skip out.
Let's go get naked right now.
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
- Mr. Dawson.
- Yeah.
Why don't you take it
somewhere else?
Mr. Floyd, are you gracing us
with your presence today?
- Uh, might as well.
- You know, Ginny?
I was thinking you and l
could get together over the summer.
It'll be legal.
I'll keep things quiet.
I'll keep it mums the word.
I promise. I swear to God.
[ Carl ]
At the party tonight,
- I heard there's gonna be
a girl with knockers this big.
- Bullshit.
- Promise. Two handfuls.
- No way.
Hey. Psst ! Hey.
[ Carl ]
Pentico's got his brother's car.
- Let's go. Cool.
- Cool, man.
- Go talk to him.
- I'm not going alone.
- Ask him.
- [ Mitch ] Uh, Mr. Payne? Sir?
Every second that you could
let us out early...
would really increase
our chances of survival.
It's like our sergeant told us
before one trip into the jungle:
- [ Sighing ]
- Men !
Fifty of you are
leavin' on a mission.
Twenty-five of ya
ain't comin' back.
Okay.
[ Ginny ]
The '68 Democratic Convention
was probably...
- the most bitchin' time
I ever had in my life.
- [ Bell Ringing ]
Okay, guys, one more thing.
This summer when you're
being inundated...
with all this American bicentennial
Fourth of July brouhaha,
don't forget you're
celebrating the fact...
that a bunch of slave-owning,
aristocratic, white males
didn't want to pay their taxes.
- Yeah !
- Have a good summer.
# We got no choice #
# All the girls and boys #
# Makin' all that noise #
# 'Cause they found new toys #
# Well, we can't salute ya
Can't find a flag #
# If that don't suit ya
that's a drag #
# School's out for summer #
# School's out forever #
[ Car Horn Honking ]
# School's been blown to pieces #
# No more pencils #
# No more books #
- # No more teacher's #
- Over there. Let's get him.
# Dirty looks #
# Well, we got no class #
# And we got no principles #
- [ lndistinct Yelling ]
- # And we got no innocence #
# We can't even think
of a word that rhymes #
- [ Pentico ] Jump in. Come on.
- # School's out for summer #
- # # [ Continues lndistinctly ]
- Go, go, go, go.
- Hurry up, Hirschfelder,
or we're gonna leave your ass.
- Sorry.
- Let's go. Come on !
- Back it up.
- Oh, shit !
- Ducks on the pond !
- How're you doin', boys?
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Whooping ]
- Ow ! Ow !
- # No more pencils #
- Wake up, bitch.
Wake up. Open, open.
- # No more books #
- Hey, hey, open !
- # No more teacher's #
# Dirty looks # #
Okay, open wide.
Open wide.
- What do you think?
- All right. Let's go.
Hey, you. Come here.
You. Who are you?
Uh, nobody.
I mean, I wasn't in the truck.
- Are you a freshman?
- Yeah.
Well, are you in
or are you out?
- In.
- Let's go.
[ lndistinct Yelling, Laughing ]
# Jim Dandy to the rescue #
- Oh, God, hurry up !
- # Jim Dandy to the rescue #
- Come on. Hurry up !
- We're screwed !
- Lose them !
- I'm trying, man !
- [ lndistinct Yelling ]
- # # [ Continues lndistinctly ]
- Let's get 'em !
- [ lndistinct Shouting ]
[ lndistinct Yelling ]
Shit ! Here they come !
[ lndistinct Shouting ]
- # Jim Dandy to the rescue #
- Fuckin' turn !
[ Tires Screeching ]
- Oh, shit !
- Right on !
- Oh, shit ! Here they come !
- I think we really pissed 'em off, man.
Just drop me off at my house.
Are you still with me?
- Yeah, I guess.
- This is my house.
They're slowing down. You get out and
get 'em ! You get out ! You get out !
Good luck, man.
Be there tonight.
I'll catch up
with you later. Go, go !
[ Tires Screeching,
Engine Revving ]
Oh, shit.
Nice try, freshmen.
Tell you what.
For being brave little kids, I'm only
gonna give each of you five licks.
- All right, grab a pole
and let's get going.
- [ Door Opening ]
I don't think so, creep.
- Mom !
- Carl, get in the house.
Get in the house !
And you. [ Cocking Gun ]
Get the hell off my property.
I'm sorry, ma'am. I was just escorting
your fine young son home from school.
There's some ruffians
about and l--
Oh, and, Mitch, Carl,
we'll be seeing
each other again.
Oh, that's it ! I fuckin' saw that,
you little sack of shit !
You two are fuckin' dead !
You hear me?
You're fuckin' dead ! [ Growls ]
[ Darla ]
Excuse me. Thank you.
[ lndistinct Chatter ]
All right,
you little freshman bitches !
- Air raid !
- [ Whistle Blowing ]
That was pathetic !
Let's try it again !
That means get up, you lazy
little bitches ! Get up !
- Air raid !
- [ Whistle Blowing ]
That was horrible, you slut girls !
You little freshman sluts !
Get up ! Up !
Up ! Up !
Air raid !
What's fascinating is the way not only
the school, but the entire community,
seems to be supporting this
or turn their heads.
They apparently have permission
to use the parking lot.
- No parents seem to mind.
They're selling concessions.
- I know.
Well, seniors, we tried.
We gave you all a chance.
But since you little prick teases
can't follow instructions,
we're just gonna have to try
something else, won't we?
Seniors?
You love us. Smile.
You love us.
# # [ "Why Can't We Be Friends"
By War ]
- Move over !
- # Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo #
- Suffer, sisters !
- Suffer !
- # Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo #
# Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo #
# La-la-la-la-la-la #
- [ Darla ] Eat it ! Open wide !
- # La-la-la-la-la-la #
- Open wide ! Mmm-mmm-mmm !
- # Why can't we be friends #
- Yes ! Love it, girls.
- # Why can't we be friends
Why can't we be friends #
- Gorgeous babies.
- # Why can't we be friends #
-Welcome to high school, honey.
-# I been around for a long, long time #
# I remembered you
when you drank my wine #
# Why can't we be friends
Why can't we be friends # #
Propose to Mr. Dawson.
- [ Snaps Fingers ]
- Will you marry me?
Don't know.
What's in it for me?
- Anything you want. Anything.
- Anything?
Go like this.
- Do you spit or swallow?
[ Snickering ]
- [ Snickering ]
Whatever you like.
- Whatever I like?
I would definitely marry you.
- That's so degrading.
Let's go.
- You're an asshole.
- [ Don ] Yes, I am.
That's terrible, man.
Horrible.
- Aha !
- [ Laughing ]
I just want you guys to know
I feel for you, man.
I did it when I was a freshman,
and you'll do it when you're a senior.
[ Yelling ] Now fry like bacon,
you little freshmen piggies !
Fry ! Fry !
- Hi.
- [ Tony ] Hi. Hello, there.
I would like for you
to propose to Tony.
- Oh, God.
- What?
On your knees.
Will you marry me?
- What am I supposed to say?
- I don't know.
What will you do for me?
Um... anything you want.
- Imagine the possibilities.
- Oh, Jesus.
Seriously, you can stand up.
- What's your name?
- Sabrina.
- I'm Tony. Anthony, actually.
- Hi. Sorry.
- This is Mike.
- Hey.
We were discussing the utter stupidity
of these initiation rituals,
and we were wondering
why someone like you...
would subject yourself
to the losing end of it all?
What are we having,
social hour over here?
I'm supposed to be being a bitch.
Back to the pit.
All right.
It's almost over.
Am I mistaken, or was there a little
unspoken thing going on there...
with that young vixen, you stud?
You know how it is.
- I bet she's cute once you
clean the shit off her.
- I'll bet.
Okay, girlies,
it's hot out here,
and I'm really sick
of looking at all of you.
So let's just--
Let's get out of here.
What you lookin' at?
Wipe that face off your head, bitch.
Let's go !
Get in the truck !
Get in the truck. Come on.
Maybe if you ever left
the poker table--
If I ever left the poker table?
What about you?
The point is, that's why
we're going out tonight.
You might experience something more
tangible than an Abraham Lincoln dream.
- That's a hairline fracture.
What did you do?
- Holy shit !
I wouldn't doubt it. My boy, Benny,
was wearin' their asses out !
Just givin' them a little beatin'
they'll never forget.
Here's to ya, Ma.
That's your fuckin' mother.
Say, man, fuck the coaches.
Just do it for us, man.
- You pick this thing up?
- Yeah.
What are you doin' ?
He ain't doin' shit, man.
Any more details of my life
you can let me in on, Ben?
- I got lots of details.
- [ Laughing, Chatter, lndistinct ]
- Fellas, fellas !
- O'Bannion, what are you doin' ?
- You didn't hear, did you?
- No.
You didn't hear I got a shotgun
pulled on my ass? Swear to God.
# Seniors are the best
Seniors, seniors #
# S-E-N-l-O-R-S #
# Hail Seniors #
[ Girls Screaming ]
# ...O-R-S #
# Seniors, seniors #
# They are the best # #
[ lndistinct Singing ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Slater ] Hey, Mrs. Pickford.
- Hi, guys. You here to see Kevin?
- No, actually, we came to see you.
- Oh.
- Bet you're glad school's out.
- We got our report cards today.
- How did you do?
- Straight A's.
- Both of you?
- Just kiddin'.
- Big trip, huh?
- We're going away for the weekend.
- You're taking Kev with you?
- No, he's staying here.
Oh ! Oh, he is. Oh.
- Thanks.
- Go on in. He's up there somewhere.
- [ Engine Idling ]
- Let's get together sometime.
- Yeah, that would be fun.
- Yeah.
What do you do?
I mean, for fun?
Usually just hang out
with the girls, drive around.
That kind of stuff.
There's a big party tonight.
It should be really great. So.
- Do you wanna come? Yeah? Cool.
- Yeah. That would be fun.
- You think it would be all right?
- It'll be fine.
- Okay, great.
We'll pick you up about 8:30.
- Okay.
- See you then. Bye.
- Okay, bye-bye.
[ Girl ]
Let's go. We gotta get ready.
Sample of the goods.
Fifteen bucks.
- Can you spot me ten?
- Hmm?
I'll pay you like...
Tuesday and shit.
[ Laughing ]
- Thank you.
- [ Knock At Door ]
- Who is it?
- [ Mom ] Kevin,
- I think you need to come out here.
- [ Pink ] It reeks in here !
There's someone out here
who says he needs to talk to you.
- What about?
- Go get the door, man. Here.
- Slater, lose it !
- [ Dad Knocking ]
Kevin, open the door.
Hey, Dad, Mom.
What's up?
- Did you order some kegs of beer?
- No.
There's a fella on a beer truck
out on the street that says you did.
- Oh, really? Just a sec.
- Yeah.
[ Door Opening ]
Shit.
- That guy said
I ordered a keg of beer?
- Yeah.
He said it was to be delivered
to the Pickford residence.
- This address?
- This address.
Humph.
That's kinda funny.
- Why don't I go out there
and see what's goin' on?
- I think you better.
- I'll be right back.
- You guys...
know anything about
a party here tonight?
- No, sir.
- No.
[ Whistling ]
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, man. Aren't you
a little bit early?
Uh... yeah,
about an hour and a half.
I wanted to get here early,
see if anyone was here.
I got this little action happenin',
if you know what I mean.
So I guess you got
the wrong house.
Yeah. Inconvenience for you.
I'm sorry.
Wrong Mr. Pickford altogether.
Hey, these things happen.
Don't worry about it... Ben. Yeah.
Were you going to have
a party here tonight, son?
I don't know
what that was all about.
Start unpacking.
We're not goin' anywhere.
- [ Groaning ] Fucker !
- Frank !
# # [ "Free Ride"
By Edgar Winter ]
[ lndistinct Shouting ]
# The mountain is high
The valley is low #
# And you're confused
on which way to go #
# So I've come here
to give you a hand #
# And lead you into
the promised land, so #
- # Come on and take a free ride #
- # Free ride #
# Come on and sit here by my side #
# Come on and take a free ride #
# All over the country
I've seen it the same #
# Nobody's winnin'
at this kind of game #
# We gotta do better
It's time to begin #
# You know all the answers
must come from within, so #
- # Come on and take a free ride #
- # Free ride #
# Come on and sit here by my side #
# Come on and take a free ride #
# Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah #
# Ooh, free ride # #
[ Cheering ]
Look out, look out !
Hey, batter, batter, swing !
[ Man ]
Concentrate out there !
Strike... two !
- Time !
- [ O'Bannion ] Kramer, one more pitch.
You better get this kid out,
or we're really gonna beat your ass.
- Let's go !
- We're gonna beat you
like a runnin' mule.
Hey, man, forget about those guys.
Let's just get
this last guy out, okay?
- Easy for your ass to say.
- Hey, man, there's nothin'
you can do about it.
How did they know
I was gonna be here?
Hey, Kramer, quit stallin'.
Let's go !
Hope you got more than a jock strap
under there, you little rat !
Because you're not gonna be able
to sit for the summer, don't let it
affect your concentration.
Up yours.
Mitch, could you do us a favor and
leave through the gate in right field?
That'll draw them out of here.
They're gonna get you anyway.
[ lndistinct Shouting ]
Yeah, get outta here.
What are you lookin' at?
Keep your head in the game.
- [ Cheering ]
- Strike... three ! Ball game.
- Good game. Good game.
- Good game, man.
- Yeah, right.
Good game, good game,
good game, good game.
Yeah, right.
Good game.
- Good game.
- What's happening?
- Good game, good game !
- Way to go, buddy.
[ lndistinct Heckling ]
Aw, what happened
to your buds?
Come on.
Let's get this guy.
- Hey, Mitch ! Mitch !
- Kramer !
- How's your dad doing?
- He's doing great.
This arm ready to throw
about 2,000 yards next fall?
Oh, I don't know.
We'll see.
We're dependin' on you boys.
Let me tell you what.
You're looking good !
Thirteen starters coming back,
22 lettermen.
- Lookin' tough.
- Yeah.
- Well, you folks take care.
- Good to see you, Randy.
# # [ "No More Mr. Nice Guy"
By Alice Cooper ]
# I used to be such a sweet
sweet thing 'til they #
# Got a hold of me #
# I opened doors
f or little old ladies #
# I helped the blind to see #
# I got no friends
'cause they read the papers #
# They can't be seen with me #
# And I get real shot down
and I'm #
# Feelin' mean #
# No more Mr. Nice Guy #
# No more Mr. Clean #
# No more Mr. Nice Guy
They say #
# He's sick
He's obscene # #
- [ Laughing ]
- Oh, God, you know that hurts !
- You know that hurt him.
- What's goin' on here?
- Oh, Pink, you missed it !
- What's up buddy? What's up?
- Where are you headed off to now?
- The point. Gonna join us?
Yeah, see you up there.
Need you to sign
my paddle later.
- I gotta get seconds with him.
- Wait.
- You next, Pink?
- Sure.
- You already got him.
- All right, fuck it.
I'm gonna go find your little
skinny partner Carl and his mom.
I took it easy on you.
You're not smilin' now,
are ya, you little sack of shit.
Benny, Don.
- Say, man, bummer about
Pickford's party, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah. His old man found out.
Total rip-off, man.
[ Laughs ]
Hey, man, we got a few sixers.
You with us?
Yeah, I gotta go home and change.
I'll catch up with you.
All right, see you later.
Hey, kid, take care of that butt.
Say, guys, hold up !
[ Engine Starting, Revving ]
- You need a ride?
- Yeah.
Uh... I think they left me.
Here you go, man.
Yeah, there's always one senior
who has to be the bad ass.
I think O'Bannion's gonna be
the first senior in history...
to take that honor
two years in a row.
The guy's a dick, right?
Yeah, he's, uh,
kind of a joke.
- He's not a bad guy to have
on your side blocking for ya.
- Yeah.
- Did you get it bad
when you were a freshman?
- Aw. Shit, man.
They waited for my ass
after baseball practice and got me.
- God, it was vicious.
- [ Chuckles ]
Actually, it is best
to get a lot at once,
'cause after about ten licks,
your ass gets so numb,
you might as well get it over with.
I had some pretty cool seniors.
They'd take you out and bust the hell
out of you and then...
go get you drunk, stuff like that.
Cool.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah, take care, man.
Uh, hey, man, look,
since the party's not goin' on,
me and some of the other guys'll
probably end up ridin' around.
You want us to stop by
and pick you up?
- You think that's a good idea?
- Oh, yeah, sure, man.
The guys who haven't got you yet
will give you a few days to rest.
It, uh-- It'd be a pretty
cool move to show up...
and let 'em know it doesn't
bother you that much.
Yeah, okay. Cool.
- See ya later?
- Yeah, sure.
Thanks for the ride, man.
Hey, man, uh... put some ice on it
f or a while.
After that, it won't be anything
a few beers can't take care of.
# # [ "Low Rider" By War ]
# All my friends
know the low rider #
# The low rider
is a little higher #
# # [ Continues lndistinctly ]
Like, what did she say?
I'm just interested.
- I mean, what did she call me?
- You hang out with her. You know it.
We know they talk about us.
Just tell us.
- Nothing.
- Aw, come on ! Nothing?
That's a lie. When you do that,
I know you're lying, you bitch.
- You're not gonna get mad?
- I'm not gonna get mad.
I think it's a riot.
- I don't care what she thinks.
- Just tell us.
- She called you a bitch and you a slut.
- She called me a slut?
- That bitch !
- Everybody calls you a slut.
- Oh, shit !
- That bitch ! I'm gonna kick her ass.
I can't believe that.
What a bitch.
- You said you weren't gonna get mad.
- I'm not mad.
# Low rider
is the one to meet, yeah # #
[ Turns Down Radio ]
- Look, I got a confession to make.
- What do you mean?
You know I've been talkin' about
going to law school so I can
be an A.C.L.U. lawyer...
and help people who are
getting fucked over?
Well, I was standing in line
at the post office yesterday
and I'm lookin' around.
And everybody's looking
really pathetic.
People got drool
just sorta--
- And this guy's bending over,
you could see the crack--
- Aw !
It was just like wife beaters--
Anyway, it was--
And I realize I just
didn't want to do it !
It sounds good and all, but I have
to confront the fact...
that I really don't like the people
I've been talking about helping out.
I don't think I like people, period.
You guys are okay.
I'm just trying to be honest
about being a misanthrope.
So you're not gonna go to law school?
What do you wanna do?
[ Sighing ]
I wanna dance !
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Boy ]
All right, let's rock and roll.
Hey, hop in, man.
Hey, man, whose car?
- You know Wooderson?
- How's it goin', man?
Pretty good.
How's it goin' with you?
Say, man.
You got a joint?
Uh... no,
not on me, man.
It'd be a lot cooler if you did.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Wooderson ]
All right, all right.
[ Pink ] Hey, man, you
still drivin' into Houston and
get those Aerosmith tickets?
You damn right.
- Evenin', ladies. [ Howls ]
- [ Pink ] Nice.
- Need me to pick you up a couple?
- Yeah, two.
Cool.
- [ Mitch ]
Man, you sure I'm okay in here?
- [ Pink ] You'll be okay.
If anyone starts messin' with ya,
play it cool.
# # [ "Hurricane" By Bob Dylan ]
# Here comes the story
of the Hurricane #
# The man the authorities
came to blame #
# For somethin'
that he never done #
# Put in a prison cell
But one time he coulda been #
# The champion of the world #
# Three bodies lyin'
near the Spanish Sea #
- One to go. Prickford !
- # And another man named Bill
went around mysteriously-- # #
- "Wood-a-been," happenin' ?
- Bummer about your party.
What can I say? It's beyond me.
Delivery guy bricked.
And it's a-- Keep your eye on the ball.
Dead issue !
- How's it going?
- Good. What's goin' on?
- Nothin'. Nothin' at all.
- Not much?
- You know Mitch?
- I think I just heard about you.
- What did you hear?
- I don't know, man. Are you okay?
Oh. Yeah.
- Oh. I guess I'll see you guys later?
- Okay.
- Talk to you later.
- Okay. See you.
# Meanwhile far away
in another part of town #
- Hey, man.
- # Reuben Carter and a couple of
friends are drivin' around-- #
- What grade's she in?
- Sophomore.
Come on. Hurry up.
We gotta hurry, though.
- Check this out, man.
- Donny !
I got a big surprise for ya.
Come on.
Oh, God !
Hold onto this, tight.
- Yeah !
Oh, wow ! Geez !
Nice tongue !
- Who painted 'em? Ah !
- Mostly Michelle. Ah !
- I got an idea.
- What?
- A beer bust later on.
- Hey, man.
Pickford's got a duber
about to burn. You with us?
Think about it. Yeah.
You cool, man?
Like how?
Okay. Hey, man, wait up.
He was just askin'
if you get high.
- Yeah, like smoke pot?
- Yeah.
I never have before,
but, you know--
[ Engine Starting, Revving ]
- Where you goin' ?
All right, you... knock. Just--
Hi. No.
Crank it up !
# # [ "l Just Wanna Make Love To You"
By Foghat ]
- Oh, yeah !
- [ Laughing ]
# I don't want you
cook my bread #
make my bed #
# I don't want your money too #
# I just wanna make #
# Love to you # #
Hey, it's the chicks.
Shavonne's still mad at me.
- Watch me get something going.
- Hey, what's goin' on?
- [ Girl ] What are you up to?
- [ Slater ] A little weed.
- There may be a beer bust later on.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- Guess we'll see you around.
- All right, check you later.
Bye.
Slate, man, why are you
always such a dork, man?
- What are you talkin' about?
- "Check you later."
- [ Chuckles ]
- Get off my case, man.
Oh, man.
Chicks don't wanna hear that shit.
They don't wanna
hear anything, man.
The girls, man, in our classes,
they're all prudes.
- Worthless little bitches, man.
- Oh, my God.
The girls ahead of us were wild.
Our class is worthless, man.
Maybe you've never got past
the sniffin'-butt stage.
Hey, man, it's,
it's quality not quantity.
And wait 'til I get
to college, man.
- I can't wait to get to college.
- Yeah, when I get to college,
all I'm gonna do is
bang, bang, bang, bang !
# # [ "Love Hurts" By Nazareth ]
# Ooo-hoo, love hurts #
# I'm yours #
# I know #
# But even so #
- # I know I've been #
- Hey, Hirschfelder, let's go.
- # # [ Continues ]
- Let's go. Let's get outta here.
- Let's go.
- Come on, man.
All right.
- It's time to leave.
- I'll be right back.
# Really learned a lot #
# Love is like a flame
that burns you-- # #
Hey. You boys leave,
you can't come back.
Aw, gee.
You hear that?
If we leave,
we can't come back.
Oh, no !
What should we do?
[ Sighing ]
What the hell are we doing?
I was gettin' there.
- Man, I had my hand up her shirt.
- Oh.
You were gettin' there?
You hear that?
He was gettin' there.
You wouldn't know what to do if you had
gotten there, so don't worry about it.
-Just 'cause you guys are striking out--
-Grow up, boy !
- That was our last junior high party.
- That's right.
We're in the big time now.
We're freshmen, where all
the girls'll be puttin' out.
Your days of lyin' around
and pullin' tongue all night are over.
# # [ "Paranoid" By Black Sabbath ]
# Finished with my woman #
# 'Cause she couldn't help me
with my life #
- # # [ Continues lndistinct ]
- You didn't know she stuff s her bra?
- Terry stuff s her bra?
- You didn't know those were socks?
They looked real to me.
- Shit.
- Scatter !
[ Engine Revving ]
[ lndistinct Shouting ]
# All day long
I think of things #
# That never seems
to satisfy #
# Think I'll lose my mind
if I don't #
# Find something
to qualify #
# Can you help me #
Get over there !
Where you runnin' to?
We ain't gonna
hurt ya... much.
Hold onto that fence
and just squeal like a pig.
[ Squealing, Laughing ]
- You ready to switch hit?
- Oh, yeah.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Laughing, Squealing ]
- # I need someone to show me #
- Geez.
Bastards.
# # [ Continues lndistinctly ]
- Hey, you guys !
- [ Car Engine Stops ]
Take it easy on the kid !
Ladies.
Hey, who is that kid?
Some kid we saw that shouldn't
have been by the rec center.
Can we have some
of those beers?
- One of these?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Just gimme a beer.
Yeah? Catch. Huh, huh.
[ Don ] Tubs, catch !
Get outta here !
- What are you wastin'
a beer on him for?
- What?
- Son of a bitch.
- It's no big deal.
This fuckin' sucks.
Last fuckin' day of school,
- no fuckin' party, no fuckin' nothin'.
- [ Glass Breaking ]
- You just wasted another fuckin' beer.
- Shut up !
- Thanks.
- Hmm.
Hey.
Which one of your friends
bought you the beer this time?
[ Boy ]
Hey, fuck her. I did !
- Bite me !
- You wish, asshole !
- Fuck you !
- Why are guys such pigs?
- What?
- Let's get outta here.
- We're outta here.
- [ Engine Starting ]
[ Wooderson ] Let me tell ya
what Melba Toast is packin'.
We got 411positrack out back,
750 double pumper,
Edelbroc intakes, Ford over-30,
11-to-1pop-up pistons,
Turbo-jet 390 horsepower.
We're talkin'
some fuckin' muscle.
I know you got this thing
out of a comic book.
I saw the ad-- 295.
It was right next to the sea monkeys.
You see that? That's white lightning.
See the shoes on that thing?
- [ Chuckling ]
- You gotta get some tires.
They're pizza cutters, man.
- Yeah.
- Ow.
This is sad. Shouldn't we
be doing something else?
- Yeah, like what?
- I'm bored. Let's split.
Where do you want to go?
- Pink !
- Hey.
- You hear anything more
about a beer bust?
- Talk to this man right here.
Patience, darlin', patience.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
I was just about to ask you
the same question.
- I heard you got busted.
- Oh, yeah.
- They just got Hirschfelder too.
- Really?
- Like how bad?
- Bad.
- Was it O'Bannion?
- Yeah.
God, I hate that jerk !
I know.
So, um--
[ Sighs ]
Like, what have you guys
been doin' ? Just--
I don't know.
Drivin' around mostly.
I didn't know Jodi
was your big sister.
Hey, I hear my name over here?
You talkin' about me?
Hey, kiddo.
Heard they got you pretty bad.
Man, I asked them
to take it easy on you.
- I can't believe they did that.
- Man ! God, no wonder !
-Where'd they find Hirsch?
-Walkin' out of the rec center, I think.
- [ Laughing ]
- What have you guys been doing?
[ lndistinct Talking ]
- Hi.
- [ Chuckles ]
- Ow !
- Hi.
Face it. You got busted
because you couldn't get away.
You try and outrun those guys.
I'm gonna laugh my ass off
when it's your turn.
Oh, man, I heard last year,
they caught about ten freshmen at once.
O'Bannion backed his truck over
some pizzas and made 'em eat it, man.
Idiot flunks his senior year
so he can be a dick two years in a row.
Is that legal?
Damn you, Carl !
[ Don ]
Okay, let me out.
Hey, Slater, you fuckin' hippie,
gimme drugs, man !
- [ Slater ]
Get some from your mother, man.
- We just bagged your mother.
Fuck you, dick-head.
Those guys, man.
[ Chuckles ]
What's goin' on?
I haven't seen you in so long.
Man, what is happenin' ?
Long time... no see.
- What have you been up to?
- Same old shit, man.
- Workin' for the city.
- Workin' man, huh?
Been thinkin' about
gettin' back in school, man.
- Back in J.C., somethin' like that?
- Yeah, man.
That's where all
the girls are, right?
On the other hand,
I'd just as soon keep workin',
keep a little change in my pocket.
Rather than listen
to some dipshit...
who doesn't know what
the hell he's talking about.
- You're a freshman, right?
- Yeah.
So tell me, man. How's this year's
crop of freshman chicks lookin' ?
Wood, you're gonna end up
in jail sometime really soon.
No, man.
No, let me tell you.
That's what I love about
these high school girls, man.
I get older,
they stay the same age.
- [ Laughing ]
Yes, they do.
- Yes, they do.
- You guys wanna go for a spin?
- Yeah. Shotgun !
- Aw.
- Woods.
- I'm here, man.
- You gonna come along?
[ Sighs ]
Uh, yeah. Why not?
- You boys have fun now.
- Thanks a lot.
Listen, I'm gonna
give you shotgun.
But I want you to know
it's only 'cause I'm goin' inside.
- You keep that in mind.
- Got it.
- [ Mitch ] Hey, man,
whose bowling ball is this?
- It's yours.
- Hey, man, what's happenin' ?
- Play a little foosball?
- Yeah !
- All right.
# # [ "Tush" By ZZ Top ]
# Yeah #
# I been up
I been down #
# Take my words
my way around #
# I ain't askin' for much
Mm-hmm #
Pull over to the trash here.
[ Mumbling ]
# I been bad
I been good #
# Dallas, Texas
Hollywood #
# I ain't askin' for much
Mm-hmm #
- [ Laughing ]
- Shit, yeah !
# # [ Music Continues ]
- [ Laughing Loudly ]
- Yeah ! Yeah !
- Hey, guys, pull over
to that one over there.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[ Pink ]
Here, hold this, hold this.
# # [ Music Continues ]
Got it ! Go ! Go !
[ lndistinct Yelling ]
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Pickford ] Yeah !
[ Laughter Continues ]
Yeah !
- [ Coughing ] Bowling ball.
Throw the bowling ball.
- Yeah.
Think I should?
- Yeah. Throw it. Throw it.
- Throw it. Throw it.
- Come on. You're playin'
with the big boys now, man.
- Do it. Throw it.
[ Don ]
Faggot-sissy-pussy-freshman,
throw it ! Throw it !
Heave it !
# I ain't askin' for much #
- # Mm-hmm # #
- Fuck 'em ! [ Laughs ]
That bowling ball said "Oof!"
to that damn windshield !
- Yeah.
- [ Pickford ]
You're nuts, Junior ! You're nuts !
[ Laughter ]
Hey, man, we're outta beer.
We gotta make a Grab-'N'-Go stop.
- I don't have any money.
Who's got money?
- I gave mine to--
Where's your money? Doesn't matter.
Pull in, heading out that way.
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Music Stops ]
- Are you gonna hoist it?
- Yeah. All I need's
the freshman as a lookout.
I don't wanna get in trouble.
Do you, Pink?
- [ Pink ]
I don't know about this, Don.
- Come on.
Better be careful...
Junior.
- Sunflower seeds.
- Zigzags.
- Hey, man, I'm not
too sure about this.
Shh ! I'm gonna pay for it.
I'm just messin' around with 'em, okay?
Good.
[ Sighs ]
- Run ! Go, go, go, go !
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- We gotta get outta here, man !
- Let's go !
- Come on. Let's go !
- Oh, my God !
Don't try anything,
or I'll shoot the shit outta you.
- Don, give the beer back, man.
- I paid for the beer, man.
You busted my mailbox,
didn't you?
Look me in the eye, punk !
- I don't know what you're talking
about, but I suggest that you--
- You busted it, didn't ya?
Tamperin' with mailboxes
is a felony offense.
Now I done called the police.
[ Uncocking Gun Hammer ]
- I think you boys oughta
get outta the car.
- Just go, man.
- Nice and slow.
- Go, go, go, go, go !
[ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Gunshots ]
- Get down !
[ Pink ]
He's shooting at us ! Holy--
# # [ "Rock And Roll Hootchie Koo"
By Rick Derringer ]
Fairly uneventful, huh?
Which one of you
had the theory...
about how President Ford's old football
head injury is affecting the economy?
- Did you know Ford was
on the Warren Commission?
- Who cares?
- He's outta there this fall.
Look, we need some alcohol.
- That's a thought. [ Chuckling ]
# Rock and roll
Hootchie Koo #
# Lordy, mama
Light my f use #
# Light my f use #
# Rock and roll
Hootchie Koo #
# Truck on out
and spread the news #
# Mosquitoes started buzzin'
'bout this time of year # #
Say, man, why don't you run out
to the Centennial over there...
and pick me up
a sixer of this stuff.
- Think you can do that?
- Uh--
Thanks, man.
[ Boy ]
Good luck.
I'm just sayin'
if we're gonna drive around,
we should just do somethin'.
Yeah, you know,
you're right, man.
I'm just gonna get drunk,
maybe get laid or get in a fight.
I'm serious.
We should be up for anything.
I know. We are, but what?
I mean, God, don't you ever feel
like everything we do...
and everything we've been taught
is just to service the future?
Yeah, I know. It's like
it's all... preparation.
- Right. But what are we
preparing ourselves for?
- Death.
- [ Tony ] Life of the party.
- [ Mike ] It's true.
You know, but that's valid.
If we're all gonna die anyway,
shouldn't we be enjoying ourselves now?
You know, I'd like to quit
thinking of the present,
like right now is some minor,
insignificant preamble
to somethin' else.
Exactly. Man, that's what
everybody in this car needs...
is some good ol' worthwhile
visceral experience.
[ Man ] Remember to eat a green thing
every day, and have lots of calcium.
It's very important for young mothers
to have lots of calcium.
- Here you are. See you tomorrow night.
- Bye.
- How are you this evenin' ?
- Pretty good. How's it goin' ?
- Be goin' a lot better when l
get off in a couple of hours.
- Yeah, I hear that.
- You're 18, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Just graduated.
- Graduated. Congratulations.
- So you off to college in the fall?
- Oh, ya know,
I'm still not sure;
I'm workin' right now for the city.
- [ Cash Drawer Bell Rings ]
- Thinkin' of holdin' on
to the job for a while.
- It's like-- You know,
it's money in my pocket.
- I hear that.
Here's some more money for your pocket.
You have a nice night tonight.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, take it easy.
[ Tommy ]
Psst ! Hey, Mitch.
- Hey, there you guys are.
- Hey, man, what's in the bag?
- Uh, sixer. You owe me one, man.
- Yeah.
- They busted the hell
outta Hirschfelder too.
- Yeah, I heard.
- Hey, man, you over at the Emporium?
- Oh, yeah.
- Eh, is that bastard
O'Bannion over there?
- Yes. I hate that jerk.
- Do you guys wanna get him back?
- [ Boys ] Yeah.
# # [ "Slow Ride" By Foghat ]
# Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
-[ Julie ] They really sold it to you?
-Of course.
- Cool.
- # Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
- [ Groans ]
- There ya go, buddy.
- Whoo !
- Paycheck. Oh, yeah.
- Way to shoot, man.
- Thanks, man.
- [ Laughing ] Oh, yeah.
- He got it.
- Whoo !
- I got your change too.
Oh, don't worry 'bout it, man.
A beer for my partner.
- Want a beer?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Guys, party at the moon tower.
- Oh, I'm in.
- You and Benny pick up the first keg.
I'm going to collect for the rest.
Spread the word, man.
- Max, Phil, party at the moon tower.
- Eh, good game, man. You too.
Y'all are an embarrassment
to the sport of pool...
and should be proud
that I let you play... at my table.
You are the worst pool player
I've ever seen in my life.
You keep watchin' me,
you might learn somethin'.
Shit, you got so many balls
on the table,
I'm gonna have to start knockin'
your balls in to get 'em out of my way.
- Corner pocket.
- # Take it easy #
- [ Julie ] Check this out.
- God, you are terrible !
[ O'Bannion ] Okay, Elmo,
I hope you are ready...
to taste the agonizing,
bitter humiliation of defeat.
So did you hear they're busting
Carl Burnett out back?
- What did you say?
- About what?
- Carl Burnett.
- I just heard he's gettin' busted.
- Benny, they got Burnett out back.
- Carl Burnett?
- Let's go, let's go.
- Gimme two, three minutes
and let me finish this game.
- You hold him for me !
- All right, all right !
- [ Laughter ]
- [ Don ] Hey, man.
That Julie chick?
Loves you.
Oh, yeah. You want her?
Gotta play it cool, ya know.
Can't let her know how much
you like her. If she knows,
she'll dump ya like that.
Like if she asks you to ride out there
with her, you say somethin' like,
"Nah, got my own ride,
but maybe I'll see ya later."
Sounds stupid, doesn't it?
It works.
[ Making Hog Call ]
We got another one, huh?
Whoa, whoa, guys. You wouldn't mind
if I went first there, would ya?
Is that all right?
It's kind of a personal thing...
between me and this
little piece of shit here.
So... we meet again, huh?
Did y'all hear this little
motherfucker's mom pulled
a shotgun on me this afternoon?
Fuckin' bitch.
- You, you haven't had any
licks yet, have ya? Hmm?
- No.
Whoo ! Another cherry, boys.
Man, get the fuck
against the wall.
You have to be the dumbest
freshman, skinny little
cocksucker, son of a bitch...
to be out here tonight,
ya know that?
You knew I was gonna find you. I would
like to dedicate this first lick...
to your mother.
Fucker !
Oh-ho, not yet.
Oh, it's gettin' warmer.
- [ lndistinct Crackling ]
- What the fuck?
# # [ "Lord Have Mercy On My Soul"
By Black Oak Arkansas ]
Remember me, you pig?
[ Imitating Pig ]
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- Oh !
# I walked through
the halls of karma #
Let's go, man !
Come on !
- Hurry, man !
- [ lndistinct Yelling,
Tires Screeching ]
- Let's go !
- I'm hurrying !
Come on, come on ! Hurry up, guys !
It was beautiful !
You should have seen the look
on that fuck's face. Get in !
# # [ Music Continues ]
[ Cheering, Screaming ]
Jesus ! You let that
little fuck get away !
What is the matter with you?
It's fuckin' pitiful !
Fuck !
Freshmen shit-heads !
What the fuck are you
lookin' at, huh?
Kick your fuckin' ass right now.
Pussy.
[ Growling ]
What are you smilin' at,
freshman faggot, huh?
Fuck you.
Fuck all of you !
Fuck you !
Goddamn it !
- Oh, man.
- [ lndistinct Talking ]
[ Laughing ]
# # [ "Show Me The Way" ]
By Peter Frampton ]
Oh, I can't believe
I'm doing this. I swore to God
I'd never come to a Top Notch,
and here I am sorting through
jalapeño burgers and soggy fries.
- Here take 'em.
- [ Wooderson ] All right,
all right, all right.
[ Mike ]
Oh, Christ.
- How ya doin' ?
- [ Clearing Throat ]
Pretty good.
Cool. You heard about the party
bein' busted, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah? Not to worry.
There's a new fiesta
in the making as we speak.
It's out at the moon tower.
Full kegs, everybody's
gonna be there. You oughta go.
- Okay.
- Okay, we'll be there.
- So ya need a ride?
- Uh, no. I got my own car. Thanks.
- Yeah, well, listen.
You oughta ditch the two geeks
in the car and get in with us,
but that's all right.
We'll worry about that later.
I will see you there.
- All right?
- Bye.
- I love those redheads, man.
- I know you.
We had geography together,
remember?
Oh, great.
- Oh, God.
- What a dick.
That was so creepy. Ugh !
- Why are you smilin' ?
- I thought he was cute.
- Oh, that's disgusting.
- You thought he was cute?
Do you realize when he graduated,
we were like, three years old?
Cynthia, what are
you thinking? Ugh !
I don't know.
- Ugh !
- So we gonna still go?
Huh? Yeah, what the hell?
# # [ "Rock And Roll All Nite"
By Kiss ]
Oh, get back !
# You show us everything you've got #
# You keep on dancin'
and the room gets hot #
# You drive us wild
We'll drive ya crazy #
Gangway ! This is
a moving party, butt face !
- Hey, Benny, you better have
your wood screwed...
- Fuck you !
'cause I'm gonna blow
your doors completely off !
[ Laughing ]
# You drive us wild
We'll drive ya crazy #
# You keep on shoutin'
You keep on shoutin' #
# I wanna
rock and roll all nite #
# And party every day #
# I wanna
rock and roll all nite #
[ Coughing ]
- # And party every day # #
- [ Coughing ]
# # [ "Balinese" By ZZ Top ]
# Deep in the south of Texas #
# Not so long ago #
# There on a crowded island #
# In the Gulf of Mexico #
- [ Burps ]
- # It didn't take too much money #
# Man, but it sure was nice #
# You could dance all night
if you felt all right #
# Drinkin' whiskey
and throwin' dimes #
[ Mike ]
Man, someone's tokin' some reefer.
# # [ Continues ]
- [ Coughs ]
- Hey, man. Hey, slow down.
- Yeah, what?
- What's up?
- What'd you just say?
- When?
Just now, man, when you walked past.
What'd you say?
- A-About what?
- You said, "Someone's
tokin' some reefer."
[ Laughs ] No, I may have said
somethin' about smellin' some pot.
- It was just an observation.
- Oh, an observation, huh?
Well, who the hell are you, man,
Isaac fuckin' Newton?
Well, guess what, genius?
I'm the one smokin' marijuana?
You got a problem with that?
- No, of course not.
- Well, why'd you say that?
Come on, man. Don't let your mouth
write a check your butt can't cash.
I'm blazin' with my friends,
so I'm a fuckin' pothead, man.
What's it to you, huh? Huh?
Outta observations? Observe while l
punch your teeth down your throat !
Come on, dude, relax !
- He's cool, man. Relax.
- Hey, I'll be watchin' you, Newton.
I only came here to do two things, man:
kick some ass and drink some beer.
- [ Laughing ]
- Looks like we're almost outta beer.
- You okay, man?
- Yeah.
[ Mitch ]
Why's it called the moon tower?
Uh, I guess they just decided
to put it up here when they
were buildin' the power plant.
Actually, it's a good idea.
I mean, you got a full moon out here
every day of the year, you know?
Yeah, but nothing's ever been
repaired, so this whole place
could fall down at any time.
So you better watch
your step, Junior.
- Whoa !
- This place used to be off-limits, man,
'cause some drunk freshman
f ell off.
He went right down the middle,
smackin' his head on every beam, man.
I hear it doesn't hurt
after the first couple, though.
Autopsy said he had one beer, man.
How many'd you have?
- Four.
- You're dead, man.
You're so dead.
[ Laughing ]
Look at the bloodstains right there.
Shut up.
- I'm gonna get that guy.
- What guy?
That asshole
on the way in. Clint.
That superdominant male
in a '50s greaser uniform.
- I wouldn't suggest that, Mike.
- Most fights at places like this...
never get past a punch or two
before they're broken up.
There's an almost natural instinct
not to upset the herd.
So all I gotta do is get in one
good punch, play defense and wait.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
At first, I was relieved
to get out of the situation,
but now there's this...
level of humiliation setting in that's
gonna be with me for fucking ever !
I'm not gonna
let this be another situation
which contributes to me being...
a little ineffectual nothing
the rest of my life, you know?
[ Slater ] Would you look at this
fucking town, man? It's dead.
Imagine how many people
out there right now are fuckin', man.
[ Chuckles ]
- # Step inside my-- #
- Just goin' at it.
# # [ "Do You Feel Like I Do"
By Peter Frampton ]
- Hey.
- Remember me?
- Sure. You're Sabrina, right?
- Right.
- How ya doin' ?
- Okay.
- Hey, let's go.
- What brings you here?
- Oh, just hangin' out.
- You havin' fun?
- Yeah. Yeah.
So, uh, does your offer
from this afternoon still stand?
[ Laughs ]
What am I supposed to say?
Anything you want.
# Do you, you #
# Feel like I do # #
[ Cynthia ]
Why'd we even come here?
I always feel a little out of place
at these things, you know?
You're tellin' me.
I'm being stalked by a Nazi.
That a little bit of reefer
I smell on you, boy? Coach is right.
You're running with
that bad crowd again.
You've got an attitude adjustment
you've gotta make right now.
Like I'm the only athlete
at this fuckin' party.
Coach is right, Don.
Those guys don't care if we win or lose.
Just remember that.
Check this out. Watch this,
both of you. Watch me get this beer.
Watch.
Oh, no, it's the cops !
Look ! Look, look, look, look !
It was so easy.
Oh, shit. He needs
another drink real, you know, bad.
[ Laughing ]
# # [ "Right Place, Wrong Time"
By Dr. John ]
[ Laughing ]
Ah !
[ Coughing ]
# I was in the right place
but it must have been the wrong time #
# I'd have said the right thing
but I must have used the wrong line #
# I went down the right trail
but I must have used the wrong car #
# Head is in a bad place
and I wonder what it's good for #
# I was in the right place
but it must have been the wrong time #
- # My head is in a bad place--#
- Hey, Mitch !
-Hi. Wonderin' if you were around here.
-How's it goin' ?
- # I've been runnin', tryin'
It gets hung up in my mind #
- Aw, man !
So, uh, I just wanted
to talk, you know?
Are you quittin' football?
Or is it just this pledge?
You don't wanna sign the pledge, right?
That's what it is.
I don't know, man.
Well, maybe I'm not
into any of it anymore.
# But it must have been
the wrong song # #
- You're not into any of it anymore.
- Um.
[ Sighs ]
That will be the biggest mistake
of your life, Pink.
No one quits senior year,
pal, especially if you're
starting quarterback.
I mean, we got a shot at state.
We kicked some butt this year.
It's what we've been working
f or all of our lives, man.
Me and you, Benny.
We wanna be champions together.
Look, man,
all I'm sayin' is...
that if I do play next year,
it's gonna be on my terms,
not theirs.
You just remember
one thing, Pink.
It ain't just about you, pal.
It's about us: me, Donnie, Mel.
You'll be fuckin' us over.
Or maybe you're just
fuckin' scared, huh?
Have a nice night.
[ Slams Door ]
# # [ "Cherry Bomb"
By The Runaways ]
# Can't stay at home
Can't stay in school #
# Old folks say
you poor little fool #
- [ Laughing ]
- # Down the streets
I'm the girl next door #
# I'm the f ox
you been waiting for #
# Hello, Daddy
Hello, Mom # #
# # [ Folk ]
# Watch them fly #
# Away # #
[ Pickford ] Do you guys know what
that song's about? It's about aliens.
We're the aliens, man.
We're the savages.
Wait, man.
That song's about that?
- Yeah, man, that song's about that.
- About aliens?
Yeah, man. You didn't know that?
This country is founded--
It was founded by people
who were into aliens, man.
George Washington, man,
he was in a cult, and the cult
was into aliens, man.
- You didn't know that?
- No.
Oh, man. They were way
into that type of stuff.
It's like the every-other-decade
theory, you know?
The '50s were boring,
the '60s rocked, and the '70s--
Oh, my God,
they obviously suck.
- Come on.
- Maybe the '80s will be radical.
You know? I figure we'll be in our 20s
and, hey, it can't get any worse.
# Here I come
again now, baby #
# Like a dog in heat #
# You can tell it's me
by the clamor now, baby #
# Tide like a tapestry #
# Now I been smokin'
f or so long #
# You know I'm here to say # #
Wait a minute. Who put the keg
way out here in the woods?
- Hmm, I don't know.
- Uh-uh.
- This is just where
they told me it would be.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah. I don't think
we need beer anyway.
- George toked weed, man.
- Absolutely George toked weed.
Are you kiddin' me, man?
He grew fields of that stuff, man.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
- He grew that shit
up in Mount Vernon, man.
- He grew it all over the country.
He had people growin' it
all over the country.
The whole country back then
was gettin' high.
'Cause he knew he was
on to somethin'.
He knew that it would be a good
cash crop for the southern states, man.
So he grew fields of it, man.
But you know what?
Behind every good man,
there's a woman, and that woman
was Martha Washington, man,
and every day,
George would come home,
she'd have a big, fat bowl
waiting for him, man,
when he'd come in the door.
She was a hip, a hip,
hip lady, man.
[ Laughing ]
Wait a minute.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
Don't you have
a girlfriend?
- What girlfriend?
- What's her name?
Simone.
Hmm?
[ Sighs ]
And she, she was real cool too.
She'd harvest the crops.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
She'd put in, um, bushels and
stuff and sell it, you know?
Because they had to,
you know, make ends meet and stuff.
I mean, did you ever look
at a dollar bill, man?
There's some spooky stuff goin' on
on a dollar bill. It's green too.
- Later.
- See ya.
- Yeah, cool.
- Wait, wait, wait.
What was that all about?
- What were you doin' back there?
- Exactly what you wish you were doin'.
- Look at your boy. Look at your boy.
- Kramer !
[ Don] Yeah, you, you !
Freshman, right here. Come on.
- Right here, buddy.
- He waves at us.
- What is this wave shit?
- [ Don ] Freshman, over here.
- Over here. Now. Come on.
- Over here. Come on.
- [ Don ] Come on, come on, come on.
- Aw, shit. I should go.
- Yeah, I guess you probably should.
- [ Sighs ] Shit. I'll be back.
Okay.
He's like a little Casanova.
It's amazing.
- Look at that shit-eatin'
grin on his face.
- Not bad for a freshman,
but you better watch out
f or them older girls.
Hey, hey, hey, come here.
We just wanna know
somethin', okay?
Are you gonna be fuckin' that later,
or are you gonna be a little wimp?
- How do you know I haven't already?
- Oh, yeah !
Get outta here. I think
it's past your bedtime. Run along.
- [ Laughing ]
- Come here.
Why don't you go get
a ride with her? Say we left ya.
It will work.
It will work. Go.
- Hey, Kramer, show it to her.
- Give it to her. Go, boy.
[ Laughs ]
- Air raid, freshman.
- What?
Air raid, freshman.
- Aw, come on, Darla.
Leave her alone.
- This is between me and her,
and she better be
on the ground in five seconds.
[ Tony ] Wait. She doesn't have to
air raid because she's with me, okay?
Air raid or it's your ass.
- [ Tony ] Don't do it, Sabrina.
- [ Darla ] Oh, that's it.
Miss Hot Stuff.
I'm going to make the next year
of your life a living hell.
[ Darla Laughing ]
Lick me, all of you !
Good for you.
[ Laughs ]
Don't air raid for that bitch.
I hate that shit.
It's like that Clint fucker
in front of all his friends.
- "Huh? Huh, motherfucker?"
- All right. Okay, Mike.
- Dominant male monkey motherfucker.
- God !
- [ Girl ] T-A-R-A.
- I never met a "Tara" before.
You're my first.
Hey, what--
- [ lndistinct Talking ]
- All right !
- He did it. I can't believe it.
- I fuckin' knew I should have
kicked your ass.
Come on ! Come on, man !
Come on !
- Ha ! Whoo-hoo !
- [ Girl ] Stop now !
- [ lndistinct Yelling ]
- You guys, that's Mike.
Oh, shit.
That crazy bastard.
- [ Clint ] You like this?
You like this, motherfucker?
- [ Punches Landing ]
Kick his ass !
Come on, man ! You want some more?
You fuckin' bitch !
- Come on, you fuckin' bitch !
- Aaah ! Aaah !
Hey, hey, hey, hey !
[ Clint ]
Get the fuck off me !
- Come on. Stay down !
- Fuckin' dick ! You fuckin' faggot !
You got fuckin' smoked !
Yeah, come on, man.
You want some more?
You dick !
[ Panting ]
# # [ "Tuesday's Gone"
By Lynyrd Skynyrd ]
[ Air Hissing ]
Hey. Hey, little brother.
[ Laughing ]
- Is that a beer in your hand?
- Why, yes, it is.
- Have you had more than
one of those tonight?
- A few. Nobody's counting.
- Hey. How ya doin' ?
- Hey, how's it goin' ?
Guess I might as well just get
used to you being at the same
social functions as me, huh?
And, uh, hangin' out
with people I know?
Hey, what time are you supposed
to be home anyway?
Oh, geez, I don't know.
Couple of hours ago.
That's bullshit.
That's major bullshit.
Do you know Mom barely even let me
out of the house when I was your age?
- Aw !
- [ Sarcastically ] Aw !
Don't think for a minute...
she's not gonna be
waiting up for you.
- I've been through it.
And she's tough.
- Yeah, well--
Just don't ask her
to take it easy on me, please.
What's that supposed to mean?
Take it easy on him?
- Let's go smoke that joint.
- He's in for a surprise.
# Believe in my woman #
# And all here #
- [ Burps ]
- # Tuesday's gone #
# With the wind #
- # Tuesday's gone with the wind # #
- All right.
- Good.
- Thanks a lot, man.
Hey, man, no worries.
Take care.
- Listen, I'll pick ya up
tomorrow at 4:00?
- Okay.
Hey. Aerosmith.
Three weeks.
- Front-row seats, babe.
- All right.
I won't forget.
So, uh, who's
buying breakfast?
- Not me.
- I will, I guess.
- Great. You comin' along?
- [ Sabrina ] Sure.
- Night, John Boy. Ali.
- Good night.
- "Wood-a-been."
- Pink, my man. What's happenin' ?
- Not a lot.
- Cynthia, man? I like it, man.
- Very nice. My favorite color.
- Yeah? Red's a good color for you.
- Hey, have you seen Jodi around?
- She left your ass.
Really?
Well, ya win some, ya lose some.
What about Peter Pan?
Hey, brother, roll it back.
What's goin' on, man?
- Guys, what's goin' on?
- Nothing.
- Pickford wouldn't know.
- What time is it?
Let's go smoke a joint, man,
on the 50-fuckin'-yard line,
- in honor of your daddy, Coach Conrad.
- [ Laughing ]
- We're there.
- Great idea.
- Hey, man with the plan.
- Wanna come with me?
- Okay.
- Yeah, dude, man.
- Hey.
- Joint subcommittee meeting
on the 50-yard line in 15.
- You there?
- Okay.
[ Wooderson ] Don, y'all ride
with me. Let's hit it.
- This is cashed, man. It's cashed.
- It's in there, man.
You can ride with us, man,
but you're ridin' in the back
'cause I ain't gonna shotgun you.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, watch the leather, man.
[ Laughing ]
[ Starts Engine ]
- [ Don] Don't you quit?
You wanna hit him?
- [ Pink ] He was wide open !
-You want to hit him !
-Jesus, son, you're wearin' Rebel gray !
- Now break down ! Break down !
- I'm sorry, coach.
I want you on him like stink
on shit, stink on shit !
Break down ! You don't deserve
to wear that Rebel gray, boy !
You won't hit him?
O-T-S-S !
Only the strong survive !
- Only the strong survive !
- That's it !
- Now where's your pitch man?
Hit your goddamn pitch man !
- Oh, my God !
He spins around ! Pink runs !
Ya ! He fumbles !
[ lndistinct Yelling ]
Hell, my grandmother
can hit harder than that.
What the fuck, man?
'Course she's a 8-f oot-4,
652-pound hairy-ass gorilla,
drives a Mack truck
and runs a 40 in 10.2.
She's gotten bigger.
She was only six-two, 195 in my day.
- Still drivin' that Mack truck, though.
- Pink, you got my papers?
- Uh, yeah. There's some
in my glove compartment.
- I got 'em.
Hit me on the slant.
Gimme the keys to an inside.
Hut ! Down !
- Marijuana on one.
- [ Laughing ]
Reefer on two.
Hut ! Hut !
- Wide open !
- Huh !
[ Laughter Continues ]
[ lndistinct Yelling ]
- Oh, that's pretty good, you know?
- Yeah.
Could be a little-- I don't know--
Maybe perhaps a little more symmetrical.
- Does that hurt?
- Ow ! Yes, it hurts.
- Sorry, sorry.
- It's a, it's a bruise.
I don't know.
Let me ask you somethin'.
I mean, I got some
pretty good ones in there.
- I mean, you wouldn't say
I got my ass kicked.
- Oh, no.
After a couple of years, people won't
even remember if you won or lost.
No, you're right,
'cause like I read about, um,
like a Jackson Pollock
or Ernest Hemingway.
- You never read who won or lost,
just they got into a brawl.
- Exactly.
- Well, uh, thanks for the ride
and breakfast and everything.
- No problem.
Sure is nice to pile on
some old pancakes and syrup...
after a night of beer drinking,
isn't it?
Um--
Good night.
[ Car Engine Starting ]
- Hope you're not grounded or anything.
- Thanks.
[ Car Door Slams ]
"Not to indulge in any alcohol,
drugs, sex after 12:00...
or any other illegal activity."
Slater, babe. Found that
in your glove compartment, man.
You know, you're the third person
who's given me this today? God.
What do you reckon
you're gonna do?
I'll probably end up signin'.
I just don't wanna give in so easy.
Man, it's the same bullshit
they tried to pull in my day.
If it ain't that piece of paper,
some other choice they're
gonna try and make for you.
You gotta do what
Randall "Pink" Floyd wants to do, man.
Let me tell ya this.
The older you do get, the more rules
they're gonna try to get you to follow.
You just gotta keep livin', man.
L-l-V-l-N.
[ Laughing ]
If you're gonna sign that paper,
man, you should throw a little
grass right in the middle,
roll it up,
sign the joint, man.
- That's gonna tell 'em somethin'.
- That's what I'll do. Yeah. Assholes.
They're all a bunch of assholes,
but you gotta think about it.
- We've had a lot
of good times here, Pink.
- Yeah, come on, Pink.
I can't believe this.
You act like you're so oppressed.
Man, you guys are kings of the school;
you get away with whatever you want.
- What are you bitchin' about?
- Well, look, all I'm sayin' is...
that if I ever start ref erring to these
as the best years of my life,
remind me to kill myself.
All I'm sayin' is...
I just wanna look back
and say...
that I did it the best I could
while I was stuck in this place,
had as much fun as I could
when I was stuck in this place,
played as hard as I could
- dogged as many chicks as I could
when I was stuck in this place.
- [ Laughing ]
Yeah, right,
Mr. Premature Ejaculation.
[ Slater ] Ooh !
Oh, that's great.
That's good. That's good.
- [ lndistinct Talking ]
- [ Simone ] That the cops?
- What the hell--
- Hey ! All of you ! Get over here !
- Now !
- Hey, man, ditch that pot.
- Is it illegal to be
on the football field?
- I got some more.
All right, just be good, okay?
- Come on, Slater.
- [ Don ] What'd we do?
You got any Visine?
Man, I can't believe this.
If it ain't old Richard Wrath.
How ya doin', Dick?
Well, well, well.
Couple of football players.
Wonder what Coach
is gonna think of all this.
Line up.
[ lndistinct Police Radio ]
- Wooderson?
- Slavey?
Reliving old glories
on the football field?
Get through there.
You shouldn't still be mad 'cause l
got all-district and you didn't.
[ Radio ] # Sweet days of summer
The jasmine's in bloom #
# July is dressed up
and playing her tune #
# And I come home
from a hard day's work #
# And you're waiting there #
# Not a care in the world #
- # See the smile-- #
- [ Laughs ]
# # [ Music Continues ]
- What?
- Floyd !
Dawson !
Get your scrawny butts over here !
[ Don ]
Mornin', Coach.
So what the hell's goin' on?
- Why am I gettin'
wake-up calls from the cops?
- [ Don ] Oh, that was nothin'.
- They just left.
- False alarm, Coach.
Come here, Randy. Come here.
- You been out with
those losers all night?
- Hey, Coach Conrad.
Remember me?
Second-period gym class?
That's the kind of people
I was tellin' you about.
Trouble like this means
nothing to that bunch of clowns.
- You're the one with something to lose.
- Coach, you don't even know them.
- How can you even pretend
to talk that way, huh?
- Okay, Randy.
I shouldn't do this, but I'm
willing to wipe the slate clean
and forget about this.
I want you to get
your priorities straightened out,
quick hangin' out with hoodlums
and sign your commitment to your team.
- Have you done that yet?
- I'm still thinkin' about it.
No one's paying you
to think about it ! Just do it !
You know, Coach?
I gotta get goin'.
Me and my loser friends, you know,
we gotta go get Aerosmith tickets.
Top priority of the summer.
Oh. Coach, uh...
I forgot.
I might play ball,
but I will never sign that.
[ Sighs ]
[ Starting Engine ]
[ Pink ]
Let's rock and roll.
All right, man. Livin'.
Shit ! I'm gettin' my third wind.
Let's get on the road.
- Let's go. You gonna come, man?
- Shotgun !
- All right, man,
talk to you later then.
- Yeah.
- You guys not goin' ?
- Pink, can I use your keys?
- It's time to boogie on outta here.
- Hey.
So that's that, huh?
All right.
Slater. Aaah !
I never get shotgun.
Aah ! Oh, hi, Mom.
Hmm. Okay, Mitchell.
[ Chuckles ]
This is your one
get-outta-jail-free card.
- So I hoped you enjoyed it.
- No.
Your sister told me everything, so I've
decided to make this deal with you.
I'm-- Well, I'm gonna be open-minded
about it this time,
but... next time you
come in at sunrise,
we've got problems.
And, uh, who is this older girl
who gave you a ride?
Oh, she's just like--
Have you been drinking?
No.
- Are you drunk?
- [ Laughs ]
[ Cassette Clicks ]
# # [ "Slow Ride" By Foghat ]
# All right #
# Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
# I'm in the mood #
# The rhythm is right #
# Move to the music #
# We can roll all night #
# Ooh-ooh #
# Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
# Slow down #
# Go down #
# Got to get your lovin'
one more time #
# Hold me #
# Roll me #
# Slow-ridin' woman
you're so fine #
# Whoo #
# I'm in the mood #
# The rhythm is right #
# Move to the music #
# Yeah, we can roll
all night #
# Yeah #
# Ooh-ooh #
# Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
# Slow down #
# Go down #
# Got to get your lovin'
one more time #
# Hold me #
# Roll me #
# Slow-ridin' woman
you're so fine #
# Slow ride #
# Take it easy #
# Slow down #
# Go down #
# Come on, baby #
# Oh, I feel all right #
# Ya know the rhythm is right #
# You know the rhythm
is right, ohh #
# You gotta rock
all night, hmm #
# You gotta rock all night #
# You know the rhythm
is right, yeah #
# We gotta rock all night #
# You know the rhythm is right #
# Whoa, we're gonna rock all night #
# Whoo #
# Whoo-hoo #
# Now, baby, uh-uh #
# Now, baby, uh-huh #
# Whoo #
# Ow #
# Slow ride #
# Yeah # #
Dazed.And.Confused.1993.720p.HDDVD.x264-iLL.English
Upload to subscene.com by ViSTA™-VNHD