演唱：Drake
压制:随Feng
Hold On( We're Going Home)
I got my eyes on you, you're everything that I see
I want your hot love and emotion endlessly
I can't get over you, you left your mark on me
I want your high love and emotion endlessly
Cause you're a good girl and you know it
You act so different around me
I know exactly who you could be
Just hold on we're going home
It's hard to do these things alone
I got my eyes on you, you're everything that I see
I want your hot love and emotion endlessly
I can't get over you, you left your mark on me
I want your high love and emotion endlessly
Cause you're a good girl and you know it
You act so different around me
I know exactly who you could be
Just hold on we're going home
It's hard to do these things alone
You're the girl, you're the one
Gave you everything I love
I think there's something, baby
You're the girl, you're the one
Gave you everything I love
I think there's something, baby
Cause you're a good girl and you know it,
You act so different around me,
I know exactly who you could be
Just hold on we're going home
It's hard to do these things alone
压制:随Feng