-This will good Alex, move back home to Saltis.
-It's going to be so perfect, it's so beautiful out here, close to the nature, own parking space in front of the house as well
-And all the isles around the corner, all...all my old friends out here
-€80 for a taxi home from the pub in the city, no cinemas, no cafés
-But shit Alex what the fuck have I done, stop it now Alex, don't get paranoid now
-This is going to be great!
-This is gonna be so fun, we will get on so good out here
-But you don't have to feel like its written in stone, I mean if we don't feel comfortable here we can always sell the house in that case
-Ye of course
-We can move back if it feels totally wrong
-Actually not, mom would kill me. No way we are moving, now we are stuck out here for the rest of our lifes
-Oh fuck now I get trouble to breath again
-If I was a junkie, GOD, this would be the place I would hang out at a lot
-What do you mean, does it feel like an area junkies hang out
-No but why do the junkies hang at the subway, in that piss scent that's there
You could just as well sit out here
-What? What do you mean?
-Ye but why would they sit there all day? You could just as well sit out here
-They don't have jobs, they got their little spoon which they heat up, they could just as well do that on the boardwalk at the beach
-Junkies at the boardwalk, ye maybe would spice it up a bit
-Look over there, right there
-No we can go to Hornholster, he got a nice garden. So can we get smoke a pipe there
-Look who comes here. Heey
-Hello!
-Welcome to Solsidan!
-Back to the crime scene!
-How is it?
-It's good
-When can we come and check out the house?
-But if your big strong man is going to help carry some boxes you might as well come over
-Do I need  some gloves?
-Would be great, I only got dads old. Have you bought new or what?
-Thats unnecessary fast driving in that way
-Honey, kiss
-I'm feeling so nervous
-But you know honey, there's nothing to worry about. It's going to be great with a house together, I'm sure about it, we handle ourself, it's only me and you honey
-Hi, what a long time it took
-Yeee...Mom also
-Ye I know, Hi mommy!
-Hej
-Hej Hej
-Thought she had given you that key
-Ye, so did I
-Hej, thanks
-Welcome
-Hey mommy
-How will it be now, are you moving back into your boy room or are you taking over your moms bed?
-Ye exactly... No but it feels totally right now with an own house. Own garden, just be able to let out the kids out and take a beer in the evening sun
-You don't have any evening sun
-Don't i?
-No, this is a north-east lot
The fuck I got evening sun, don't I?
-A north-east lot in Stockholm corresponds to a south-west lot in Kiruna if you count the sun hours
-But what the fuck I've grown up here, didn't i have any evening sun here when I was younger. What do you mean? Some times I had it
-No, never. Check out the school pictures. You were always less tan than anyone else. You and Eva also a north-east lotter
-Shit, you lie so much
-Not much
-But Anna, this room is so wonderful
-Ye isn't it nice
-With a terrace and all
-Ye, now it was meant for Alex mom to pack up her stuff here which she haven't done apparently
-But fuck that, here I feel that I would like a accent wall in some bright color
-Ye that could look good
-If you'd let me say what I feel
-Ye
-A accent walls feels a bit 2001, I would watch out for it. I think you should make it all white. Then you can open up with some nice colors on the textile like we got in our lounge you know?
-At the couch up there, with the pillows. Kamimakiatri you know. That isn't white but not beige either. A bit in the middle, kinda like cream, egg shell, latte, not latte but coffe colette. Somewhere there
-Alex, I don't think I will sleep over tonight so you can place boxes in my room if you'd like
-Okey, what room are you talking about?
-But we agreed to that I was going to keep my old bedroom here
-Mommy wasn't it more like you were keeping your stuff here for a while in a room
-A while?
-Ye
-To I die you mean?
-No, no I'll talk to Anna
-Good
-It's no worry
-Viktor, stop it. Do you hear me Vikor, stop it
-Here you could have some evening sun
-Up here?
-Few hours at least
-Ah ok
-If we take down the tree over there. I can help you with it, I have a new saw
-Ok, but is Malmberg still living here? Wasn't he going to move, mom said so
-He didn't get the asking price
I really hate him, hey hey, hey Tod
-Ey Viktor I said stop it
-Margareta, I've thought about the fact that you've still got a key
-Ye but you don't need to worry about that, I have my key.
-Ye but I was just thinking that we only got three
-Ye but of course, then we have one each
-Ye but I was thinking more that it would be good if there was a key here
-Why?
-Because it would be good if we would like to go away impulsively and someone can water the plants, some neighbor
-Nooo, that won't be nessessary. I will do that without hesitation
-Ye ok you think like that. But it's possible to have different thoughts about it
-I have bad bowel movements. Candida is a guest mushroom so I have to help the small intestines on the way
-I was thinking more about the key
-Hello there, hi Tod
-Hey, hey, hey
-Out polishing the boat a bit today?
-Yeah, Monica that I've named after my lovely wife. Do you remember her?
-Ye. Worst fucking bitch ever. Aunt Monica ye she was so alive, when she was alive
-You're a dentist right, like your dad?
-Ye, do you still work?
-Do you remember the time when you were 8/9 year olds and had gotten locked outside? Then you went out here and sat down below my berry bushes and took a shit.
-Do you remember that?
-We used to called him the free pooper, my wife and me. Which we found funny. We never said Alexander but instead "Here he comes, the free pooper", "Now he have graduated, the free pooper" and so we kept on
But you I was thinking about the tree behind here, it's a bit in the way for the evening sun. So i was going to ask if it's ok for you if we take it down?
-Ye of course no problems.
-Ah how nice
-Then I will get free view to see if you and your wife are going to sit down and have a shit
-Ye ,here she is Anna my wife
-Hey, Anna
-Hey hey, Malmberg
-Ah Malmberg, nice to meet you.
-Are you also a dentist?
-No, I'm an actor
-That you are of course
-But have Lindeblad had a divorce? When did that happen?
-Ye Christoffer, but that was a long time ago, over a year ago.
-It's a fantastic house he got, now he have turned the entire lower floor into a pool. Pretty much all of it
-But was it she that left him?
-Ye, then he must have invested in renovating the whole house when he separated. But the dude can furnish and decorate. I've been there and checked it out. Unbelievable
-Honey do you feel sick?
-Yeeee...little a bit
-The pregnancy Alex, anyone that want some more food?
-Mikaela, ain't you gonna eat anything?
-Margareta let her sleep! We are currently learning Ebba to sleep in her own bed. She's dead tired.
-Viktor, take down the elbows
-Have you seen that your mom still have her stuff in the room upstairs?
-Ye, she have had the room as bedroom since dad died
-Ye I know but it feels like it's time for her to get it out of here, dont you feel that way?
-Ye absolutely, I agree
-Do you want me to talk to her?
-No, it's fine I can do that, it's good I'll handle it
-How long have you been going on for?
-I've just begun, 45 minutes
-Ain't she getting a concussion of that?
-No, it's like this you do according to SAN
-SAN, whats that? It sounds perverted
-Sleep-All-Night the Hanna Wahlgren method. The buffing is telling the baby this is a safe place where the wolf can't come because the mom stands between the baby and the wolf
-Much information "is missed".
-Buffa buffa buffa. I got to pull it down or I will get wrinkles.
-Can you breath a bit more quiet, it is very annoying. This have been such a calm and joyful neighborhood
ALEXANDER
-Of course mom will understand that she must move out of the house. Oh my god and if she doesn't agree to that I must put my feet down Alex. Just tell her
-Mommy, there is a thing we got to talk about. You can't get upset now, but I've fertilized the Rhododendron (a flower)
-Ye, I did it by mistake
-But you it has to be special fertilizer for that
-Ye i know, I took this rose fertilizer. You ain't mad at me right?
-No
-Good, shall we home and check up on it?
-Honey, how long were you doing it tonight?
-Effective buffing time approximently 4 hours
-Seriously, this has to stop, this ain't working. Tonight we will use the 5 minute method
-No we ain't
-Yes we are. There's no question about it. We put her down and let her scream for 5 minutes before we even think about taking her up
-Ye, ye but if a fire starts? Earthquake?
It doesn't matter, it has to have gone 5 minutes. That's the principle. Now I'm gonna down a tree
Ain't you gonna have some safety equipment on you?
-Do you know what I was thinking of?
-No?
-Can't we have our bed out this way?
-Are we going to have our bed room in here?
-Ye
-Ok but it is really chilly here at the window
-Oh god, we will just have to isolate it the window better or what
-Ye in one way, that always possible.
-But you, you might find it silly but here at this spot there is E-ray emission
-E-ray emission?
-Ye you know the magnetic earth lines, they go here. It's not good if you're pregnant
-Are you serious?
-I don't know but in the past when they barns they never let the cows lay down on E-ray places because then the cows were born with two heads and so
-But please, who have told you this Alex?
-Yeah...I don't know, wasn't it the nurse?
-Ye, was it? I don't belive that at all
-I don't know are we gonna risk it?
-No, really do you know what I feel now? You're only saying this because you can't tell your mom that she can't have this room
-Please honey, stop being so silly
-Hell, she haven't let go of you for 5 cents Alex
-Of course I have!
-Of course she have done that! I'll go bring down a tree now anyways
-No, don't walk here
-But the fuck, I'm just wondering if we shouldn't attach some rope incase it...
-But you can't climb up the tree now, I've already begun sawing it. Its dangerous
-But serious, the terrace is just over there, imagine if it falls down on it.
-It will fall just next to it
-How do you know that?
-Because I've laid out incisions here so it will fall that way. If you saw correct, it falls correct
-I'm just so worried
-Don't be worried, here we go
-Fuck, fucking hell
-Blessing in disguise that Malmberg ain't home
-Unlucky? Sawing correct, falling correct someone said
-Focus now, it ain't really time to place out blame
-It was clearly your fault
-There was a gust (wind)
-Look theres scratches in the lacquer, there also
-Where?
-Here
-It ain't sure it came from the branches
-Lets get the saw, for fuck sake hurry
-So then we begin
-What no, ain't it 5 minutes since we put her down?
-Nono
-Now it have already gone atlest 1 and a half minute
-You count from the point which she starts to scream so have this method always gone
-Little honey
-Only 4:50 left now ,hold back
-Hold back
-Hold back, no that's not holding back. Fuck
-Good, good now we have tried the 12 second method. What do you say shall we try the 5 minute method also?
-Now I'm doing it this way, if this don't work then she can will have to keep on sleeping in our bed
-I actually read about Katarina Janoush children, her children slept in their bed till they were 8 9 years old
-No no don't fucking bring up Katarina Janoush in this house shes one of those fucking persons that breastfeed their kids till they start university. She's not sane
-You ain't sane
-I got a Lagavol in the drinks cabinet, I'm not saying we should but I won't sit like that. We just put some fumes
-Fredrik go to sleep if you're so tired
-Just another suggestion
-Alexander?
-Ye?
-Where is all my things?
-Oh, someone must have emptied in here
-It must have been Anna if not you, haven't you talked to her about it?
-Of course I have, but she's pregnant so she's forgetful and confused. It's all the hormones. You can tell her stuff multiple times but it ain't going in
-Ye, I remember. It was like a dough in the head
-Ye exactly, a bit like that
-Honey, I was thinking about moms old room, ain't it just as good if she keeps her stuff in there for the time being
-What the fuck Alex, what is your problem?
-I don't have any problem, it's you that have them
-But why can't you go in and tell her how it is then?
-But that's what I've done
-No you haven't
-Yes I have done it
-How come nothing is happening then?
-She got Alzheimer, what the fuck is it I'm saying...Alzheimers
-She got Alzheimers?
-I'm telling her stuff multiple times but it ain't going in.
-But honey why haven't you told me this, thats something you tell to each other?
-Ye I just haven't gotten it out of me before
-But of course that's something you have to tell me
-Alexander, Alexander, Alexander
-But go to him if he's calling you so fucking many times
-Hey there
-So good if became with the tree
-Ye didn't it, it became really good
-Imagine that it hasn't been done earlier
-Ye precisely
-It is weird that it hasn't been done before
-Ye it's weird
-Maybe because it's hard to take down a tall tree
-Ye but now I had Fredde Schiller to my help, he got really good stuff
-So it went perfect?
-Ye, kinda
-Kinda? You, now I've gotten my boat completely ruined here all sudden. There is branches that have ruined the whole lacquer
-Actually it could have been some branch that flew there
-So the tree trunk went one direction and the branches another?
-Hej Magareta
-Hej Anna
-Like Alex told, were you going to move your stuff out of here
-Oh honey, it's not easy to keep all in the head when you're pregnant with hormones and all
-But now ain't you pregnant Margareta, you are a pensioner
-But you are pregnant Anna, that you remember?
-Yes I remember that
-And Alex have told me that this room we are going to keep just as it is
-Ye but that is not true magareta, this room...
-Anna, you have to trust me
-But that I can't really do Margareta
-Can't you?
-No because Alex told me that you're ill
-Ill?
-Ye, you might have forgotten now but that doesn't matter. I don't feel like it is something that we have to hide, it's something that happens when you get old. We will take care of you, make the best of it
-What is it Alex have said?
-So I found this secateurs, it was laying under the boat. It is your fathers. His initials is here R L. Ruthger Löfström. Here you go this you can take
-ALEXANDER
-I go to mommy now, we make a deal later
-Mommy, mommy I'm sorry
-Mommy you can't drive car
-Ain't I still authorized anymore
-Yes you are but you're too upset now, mommy do you know, it was really stupid, can you listen to me...
-How can you say so to Anna that I got Alzheimer
-But I didn't say that, I'm sorry, maybe I said it but it was something else and I was unclear, I'm sorry it wasn't on purpose. What I wanted to say was that we love you so much, you are more than welcome to come here but you'll have to understand this is our house now
-Yes but it ain't so easy when I've lived here for 40 years
-Mommy, we move together
-Weren't you going to make this your workspace?
-Yes, but now it became like this. Do you have any issues with that?
-No, no I don't have any issues with it, but you're going to share it with mom then?
-Yes I'm going to share it with mommy
-Oh, how cozy for you two
-Ye
-I think I smell some odor in here, there is something. Don't you feel it? I wonder if it doesn't lay a piece of Umbilical cord in here rotting
-Get out of here, stop it
-Sorry
-Out
-How long are you going to have it dangling like that?
--They only said it was a buffering arm, that I'm overworked here and here
-God that's annoying, does Ebba sleep in her own bed now?
-You could say that, she sleeps alone in our double bed. Mikkan sleeps on the couch and me on the mattress on the floor
-Now we have it nice, now we got evening sun
-Ahh what the hell, whats this, there was evening sun for like 5 minutes
-We will have to take down those 2 also
-No forget it
-Pretty small tree trunks
-Are you cold Viktor? Shall we get some jackets
-What jackets? Why are you going to get a jacket?
-Because I'm cold
-It not cold now, this is how cold it is a summer evening
-But Alex if I want a jacket I will get one
-But you don't have to ask about that you can just get one if you feel cold. We don't freeze
-We can go in and sit there instead