Buttons
纽扣
歌手：The Pussycat Dolls Ft.Snoop Dogg
What it do babyboo
怎么了 小妹
Yeah, little mama you lookin' good
噢 小妹你好辣
I see you wanna play with a player from the hood
我看你想和帅哥好好玩玩
Come holla at me, you got it like that
让我告诉你什么是眼见为实
Big Snoop Dogg with the lead Pussycat
Big Snoop Dogg 和 Pussycat
I show you how it go down, yeah, I wanna go down
Me and you, one on one, treat it like a showdown
You look at me and I look at you
I'm reachin' for your shirt what you want me to do
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
我来帮你解开扣子 大哥
But you keep fronting (Uh)
但是你总面对着我
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
说你将要跟我做什么
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
但是我觉不出什么
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
我告诉你来解开我的扣子 宝贝
But you keep fronting (Uh)
但是你总面对着我
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
说你将要跟我做什么
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
但是我觉不出什么
Typical Hardly the type I fall for
又帅又有型是我想要的
I'm liking the physical
我喜欢真实的
Don't leave me asking for more
别离开我要求更多
I'm a sexy mama (Mama)
我那么性感
Who knows just how to get what I want and (Want and)
谁恰好知道我想要什么
What I want to do is spring this on you (On you)
我想要在你的身上弹起
Back up all of the things that I told you (Told you)
告诉过你的所有事都实现
You been saying all the right things all along
你总是永远说对的事情
But I can't seem to get you over here to help take this off
但是我觉得无法让站在那边的你脱了它
Baby, can't you see?
你看不到吗 亲爱的
How these clothes are fitting on me
这些衣服多适合我啊
And the heat coming from this beat
火热从节奏中体现
I'm about to blow
I don't think you know
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
You say you're a big boy
But I can't agree
'Cause the love you said you had
Ain't been put on me
I wonder
If I'm just too much for you
Wonder
If my kiss don't make you just
What I got next for you
What you want to do? (Do)
Take a chance to recognize that this could be yours
I can see, just like most guys that your game don't please
Baby, can't you see?
How these clothes are fitting on me
And the heat coming from this beat
I'm about to blow
I don't think you know
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
Now you can get what you want
But I need what I need
And let me tell you what s crack-a-lackin fo I proceed
I'ma show you where to put it that
PCD on me, yeah, I thought I saw a puddy cat
You roll with the big dog
All six of y'all on me
Now tell me how ya feel babydoll
Ashley, Nicole
Carmit, Jessica, Kimberly, Melody
You tellin' me
Ho,ho...hot
Hot,hot..Loosen up
hot,hot,yeah...
hot,hot,I can't take this
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)
I'm telling you loosen up my buttons baby (Uh huh)
But you keep fronting (Uh)
Saying what you going to do to me (Uh huh)
But I ain't seen nothing (Uh)