Good morning, Dad!
Good morning, Madoka.
Is Mom up?
Tatsuya's waking her up right now.
Go help him, will you?
Okay!
Mommy! Mommy!
Morning! Morning!
Wake up! Mommy! Mommy!
RISE AND SHINE!
Huh?
Mommy woke up!
So what's been
going on lately?
Hitomi got another
love letter.
That's the second
one this month.
Boys who don't even have the guts to
confess their love in person are no good.
And how's Kazuko doing?
It seems like Ms. Saotome's new
relationship is going well.
She gushes about him
all during homeroom.
It'll be their 3-month anniversary this
week, so I guess that's a new record.
Hmm, I guess we'll see.
They're reaching a crucial
juncture right now.
They are?
If it's not the real thing,
it's around this point in the relationship
that things start falling apart.
Well, if they make it past 3 months,
they're probably good for at least a year.
Perfect!
Which ribbon should I wear?
Huh? But isn't this too flashy?
That's at LEAST as flashy
as you should be!
A woman's appearance is the one thing
she can't afford to get looked down at.
Excellent!
That should make all your secret
admirers melt in adoration.
I don't have any
secret admirers!
But you should go about
as though you do.
That's the secret behind every
pretty girl's success!
Uh-oh!
Safe!
There, eat it all up now, okay?
Okay!
More coffee, honey?
Hmm, better not.
All right! I'm off then.
Have a nice day!
Now then, you'd better
hurry too, Madoka.
Huh?! Oh, right!
I'm heading out!
Have a nice day, sweetie!
Have nice daaaay!
PUELLA MAGI MADOKA MAGICA
THE MOVIE Part 1 : Beginnings
Good morning!
Good morning.
Madoka, you're late!
Oh! Cute ribbons!
You think so?
They're not too flashy?
I think they look lovely.
So my mom said...
A boy who confesses tis love with a letter
instead of in person is no good.
Your mom is just
too cool, Madoka!
I mean, she's gorgeous and
a successful businesswoman!
If only I could make up my mind
to reject a boy so easily.
What an enviable
problem to have!
It really is! I wish I could get
a love letter from someone too.
Just once!
Oh-ho!
So you want to become a beautiful,
popular girl like Hitomi, Madoka?
And you've decided to start changing your
image with these hair ribbons, huh?
You've got it wrong!
My mom made me–
I see! You even got your mom to tell
you the secret to becoming popular!
How shameless!
Let me show you what happens
to bad girls like you!
My, such a cute girl!
But I won't allow you to go off and
become popular with the boys.
You must be my bride, Madoka!!
Now, I have something very important
to discuss with you today, class.
I want you all to
listen very closely!
When frying an egg, should it be fried
sunny side-up or over hard?!
Mr. Nakazawa–what do you think?!
Huh?! U-Um, well–
Tt-They can be fried
either way, can't they?
Precisely!
They can be fried
either way!
And it should go
without saying...
...that judging a woman's
attractiveness...
... by the way she fries her eggs
is the gravest of mistakes!
Now, girls–
I want you to remember...
...that you must never date men who insist
they can't eat fried eggs done over hard.
Guess it didn't work out.
Yeah, guess it didn't.
And boys–
You'd better not grow up so petty as to
fuss over how your eggs are done, okay?
Well, then!
Now that that's out of the way, let's
welcome our new transfer student!
Hey, shouldn't that
have come first?
Come on in, Miss Akemi!
Wow, she has long hair! She's very cute!
Wow, she's gorgeous!
Huh?
Now, then! Why don't you tell
your classmates about yourself?
My name is Homura Akemi.
Pleased to meet you.
Please, go on.
HOMURA AKEMI
So, Miss Akemi...
What school did
you come from?
Did you do any club activities
at your old school?
How about sports?
Or cultural activities?
Your hair is so beautiful!
What kind of shampoo
do you use?
She has a mysterious air
to her, doesn't she?
Hey, Madoka, do you
know that girl?
Maybe it was just me, but it seemed
like she was glaring at you earlier.
Well... Um...
I'm sorry.
I think today's been a
little stressful for me.
I'm not feeling very well.
Would you allow me to excuse
myself to the Nurse's Office?
Oh! Then let me show
you the way there.
I'll come too!
No, you needn't
trouble yourselves.
I'll ask the Nurse's Aide
to take me.
Miss Madoka Kaname.
You are the Nurse's Aide
for this class, are you not?
Huh? Um, well...
May I ask you to
accompany me?
To the Nurse's Office, that is.
U-Um, I, uh...
How did you know I was
the Nurse's Aide?
Ms. Saotome told me.
Oh, I see.
Oh, um, the Nurse's Office is...
This way, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Um, but... um...
It seems like you already
know how to get there...
Um... Miss Akemi?
You can call me Homura.
Homura...?
What is it?
Oh, um...
That's kind of an unusual
name, isn't it?
O-Oh!
But not in a bad way! I-I was just
thinking it sounded kind of cool–
Madoka Kaname.
Do you treasure the life
you currently live?
Do you consider your family
and friends precious?
W-Well... I... Yes, I do.
Both my family
and my friends–
I love all of them, and
consider them very precious!
Do you really?
Yes, really! I couldn't
lie about that.
I see.
If that's really the case,
then you wouldn't try to change the
person you currently are, would you?
Because if you do, you will end
up losing all of those things.
... Huh?
You should stay as you
are, Madoka Kaname.
Stay as you are, and as
you always shall be.
Huh?! She said WHAT?!
It doesn't make any
sense, does it?
Just when I was thinking she was someone
gifted with both brains and beauty...
... it turns out she's a crazy
New Age weirdo!
Exactly tow far was she going to
keep up that weirdo character act?
Is that what gets her MOE?!
How the heck is that even exciting?!
Madoka, are you sure you've
never met Miss Akemi before?
Hmm... Well, the sensible
answer is, "yes," but...
What's that supposed to mean?
That you have met her before
in some "insensible" way?
Well...
Last night... I first met her...
in a dream...
Or something.
Awesome! You're acting like you're
an anime character, too!
That's mean! This is
really bugging me!
Well, it's all obvious now!
You must have known each
other in a previous life,
and were brought by fate across time
and space to meet once again!
You said you met in a dream.
What kind of dream was it?
It was... To be honest, I can't
really remember anymore.
I do know that it was a really
strange dream, though...
Then maybe you actually have met
Miss Akemi somewhere before.
Huh?!
Though you may not
consciously remember,
your subconscious could
have taken note of her...
...and later brought her
image out in a dream.
Isn't that a little far-fetched?
I mean, that's some coincidence!
I suppose.
Oh! It's already this late?
I'm sorry, I'd better go.
Piano lessons, right? Or is it
Japanese classical dance today?
Tea Ceremony lessons.
Even though Entrance Exams
are right around the corner.
I wonder how long Mother intends
to make me continue with them.
Whew! Makes me glad
I wasn't born rich.
Should we get going too?
Madoka, do you mind if we stopped
at the music store on the way home?
That's fine. Buying another
CD for Kamijo?
Sort of.
Well, see you later.
- Later!
- Bye-bye!
Help me...
Help me... Madoka...
Huh? What?!
Please... save me...
Who's there? Who is it?
Save me...
Where are you?
Who are you?
Save me...
Is that you?
Save... me...
Homura...?
Get away from that thing.
B-But... he's hurt!
No! Please, don't do
something cruel!
This has nothing
to do with you.
But he was calling me!
I could hear him begging
me to save him!
...I see.
Madoka! This way!
Sayaka!
Now, of all times... !
Wh-What is with that girl?!
Now she's attacking
people in cosplay?!
And what is that thing?
It's not a stuffed animal,
is it? It's alive?
I don't know.
I don't know what any of this is.
But we have to save him!
Huh?! Where'd the exit go?
What is this place?!
There's something wrong
with this place.
The path keeps changing!
What is going on here?!
There's something over there!
This has got to be
a joke, right?
I mean, I must be
dreaming, right?
Right?! Madoka?
H-Huh?!
What is...?
That was close!
But you're safe now.
Oh! You rescued Kyubey
for me, didn't you?
Thank you. He's a
dear friend of mine.
I-I was called to him.
I heard his voice
inside my head.
Ahh, I see.
Those uniforms...
You must be students at
Mitakihara Middle School too.
Are you second-years?
Who are you?
That's right, I haven't
introduced myself yet.
But before all that...
...mind if I wrap up
a bit of work?
A-Amazing... !
W-We're back... !
The witch escaped.
If you want to finish it off,
you'd better go after it right now.
I have business here.
You don't read between the
lines very well, do you?
I'm telling you I'll overlook
what you did this time.
Don't you think it would be better for
both of us not to court needless trouble?
Thank you, Mami!
You're a lifesaver.
If you want to thank anyone,
it should be these two.
I was just passing by.
Thank you very much.
My name is Kyubey.
Were you the one
who was calling me?
Yes, I was, Madoka Kaname.
And you, Sayaka Miki.
How do you know
our names?
I came here because I have
a request for you two.
A... a request?
I want you to make contracts with
me and become magical girls!
I am Mami Tomoe.
I'm a third-year student at
Mitakihara Middle School.
And...
...I am one who has made a contract
with Kyubey – a magical girl!
Wow...
What a wonderful room!
I live here alone, so feel free to
make yourselves comfortable.
Though I'm afraid I don't have much
to offer as refreshments...
Oh, Mami! This is so delicious!
Seriously–insanely tasty!
Thank you.
Since you two have been
chosen by Kyubey as well,
it means you are now
involved in all of this.
So I thought there were a few
things we should go over.
Right, right! Feel free to ask
us anything you want!
Sayaka... I think you've
got it backwards...
How pretty!
This is a Soul Gem.
When Kyubey makes a contract
with a girl, a Soul Gem is born.
It is the source of our magic, and also
the proof that we are magical girls.
What about that
"contract" business?
I will grant you one wish
- any wish you desire!
Huh? Really?!
A wish...?
Yes, anything at all.
I can grant you even the most
impossible of miracles!
So we could wish for
riches and treasures?
Or eternal youth?
Or even the fabled 108-dish
banquet of the emperors?!
Uh, maybe not
that last one...
Yes, but in exchange for that wish,
your Soul Gem is created.
Those who possess a Soul Gem are
duty-bound to do battle with witches.
Witches?
So what exactly
is a witch?
Are they different
from magical girls?
If magical girls can be said
to be born from wishes,
then witches are creatures
born from curses.
Just as magical girls spread hope to
the world, witches spread despair.
And since they're invisible
to regular humans,
it makes their evil
all the more insidious.
Anxiety and mistrust...
Irrational rage and hatred...
They sow the seeds of disaster
throughout the world.
Many of the inexplicable suicides
and murders that occur...
...are caused by
a witch's curse.
Its formless darkness grows
within the cursed human...
...until it consumes him
from the inside out.
If these witches are so dangerous, why
don't people know about them yet?
Because witches hide themselves deep
within the labyrinths they create...
and take care never to appear
before human eyes.
That maze-like place you wandered
into today was a labyrinth.
Actually, they're very dangerous.
Humans who stray into them
usually don't make it out alive.
And you fight such
scary creatures?
Yes, often at the
risk of my life.
That's why you two...
should think very carefully before
deciding to become magical girls.
Having been chosen
by Kyubey,
you have the rare chance
to have any wish granted.
But remember that that wish
lies side-by-side with death.
Oh, man... This is gonna
be a tough choice.
To help you make
up your minds,
why don't you come along with
me on a few witch hunts?
Huh?!
You should see for yourself what
it's like to do battle with witches.
Also... you should think
long and hard...
about whether there's something
you want badly enough...
...to make it worth putting
yourself in danger.
KYOSUKE KAMIJO
Hi...
Here. For you.
Really, thank you so much
for all of this.
You're really some kind of genius
at finding rare CDs, aren't you?
Nah!
I just get lucky,
that's all.
This soloist's interpretations
are really incredible.
Do you want to try listening
to it too, Sayaka?
I-If you don't mind...
I wish I could play this on a speaker for
you, but we are in a hospital, after all...
Hey, Madoka...
Have you come up
with a wish yet?
Not really...
Have you?
Nope, not a clue.
Seriously...
I've gone through and considered
so many different things too.
I mean, there are plenty of things
I want to have or do, but...
...I guess the whole "risking your life
for it" part is what's getting me.
None of the stuff I want
is worth that much.
Yeah...
How odd.
Most of the girls I make my
offer to accept right away.
Well... Maybe the pair
of us are just fools?
Huh? You think so?
Yep. A pair of blissfully
ignorant fools...
I'm sure it's not
all that unusual.
Wishing for something so strongly
you'd gladly trade your life for it...
There must be countless
people in this world...
...who have such wishes
in their hearts.
Most likely...
It means the two of us who can't even
figure out what to wish for...
...haven't experienced even a fraction
of those people's suffering.
Doesn't it seem unfair?
There are probably people who would
give anything for a chance like this...
Sayaka...
It's all right.
Picking up where you
left off yesterday?
No. I have no
such intention.
I had hoped to kill it before it made
contact with Madoka Kaname,
but it is too late
for that now...
So what will you do?
Will you become a
magical girl as well?
I...
Like you have any right
to ask us anything!
... Do you remember what
I said yesterday?
Yeah...
Good. Then I'll pray that my warning
will not have been in vain.
H-Homura!
Um...
What did you wish for when
you became a magical girl?
Now, then!
Shall we begin Lesson 1 of our little
"A Day in the Life of a Magical Girl" class?
Are you ready?
I don't know if it'll
be any help, but...
...I brought this along!
I figured it was better than having
nothing to defend ourselves with.
Well, I'm glad you're going into
this with that kind of mindset.
How about you, Madoka?
Bring anything?
Huh?!
Well... I...
Ooh!
I-I thought maybe I should at least
start thinking about costume ideas...
Huh?!
Well, you've certainly brought
enough enthusiasm!
Well, I can't top that!
You totally beat me... !
These are remnants of the magic used
by that witch we faced yesterday.
The core of witch-hunting is
scouting the city on foot.
Once your Soul Gem picks
up a witch's trail,
you just follow it until it
leads you to the witch.
It's a lot less exciting
than I was expecting.
Say, Mami...
Do you at least have an idea
of where the witch might be?
You often find traces
of witches' auras...
...around car crashes
or deadly accidents.
That's why I usually check high-traffic streets
and spots in the Red Light District...
...where fights tend
to break out first.
Also, out-of-the-way places where
people might try to commit suicide.
Then, there are hospitals–the most
awful places for a witch to take up.
It's unbearable to see them...
...draining the precious life force...
out of those who are already
weakened with pain and illness.
It's reacting to some
very powerful magic.
It must be close.
There's no mistake!
It must be here!
Mami, look!
A Witch's Kiss...
Just as I expected.
I-Is she...?
No, she's fine.
She's only fainted.
Let's go!
I won't let you
escape this time!
Wh-Whoa!
Wow!
It's not much,
but it should serve to protect you from
any immediate dangers at least.
You must stay near me once
we're inside, all right?
Right!
Stay away!
Stay away!!
So?
Are you scared yet,
you two?
A-As if!
I am scared...
But...
Keep it up!
We're almost at the deepest
point in the labyrinth!
Look.
That is a witch.
Eww... Disgusting...
Y-You're going to
fight that thing?
I'll be fine.
As though I would
lose to that!
Stay back!!
Mami!!
I'm fine.
As though I could let myself look so uncool
in front of my future magical girl juniors!
Close, but no cigar.
Tiro Finale!
S-She beat it...?
Amazing... !
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch's egg.
E-Egg?!
Witches carry them sometimes. If you're
lucky, you'll find one after a battle.
It's all right. In this form,
they're perfectly safe.
In fact, they're incredibly valuable
because of what they can do.
The color of my Soul Gem looks a little
muddier now than it did last night, right?
Now that you mention it...
But if I use the Grief Seed...
See?
Oh! It cleared up again!
Right?
With this, the magic I expended
during the fight is restored as well.
It should be good
for one more use.
I'll let you have it...
... Miss Homura Akemi.
Her again?!
Or do you dislike
sharing with others?
It was your kill.
You should keep the
reward for yourself.
I see.
So that's your answer.
Ugh! She really does bug me!
We could have been friends...
It only works if both
parties feel that way.
Where am I? Huh? I...
O-Oh my god, what
was I about to...?
Why would I...?
It's okay. You're safe now.
You were just having
a bad dream, that's all.
Well, that's one case closed.
Yeah...
It's too confusing, figuring out
what I would wish for...
But Mami looked so amazing when
she was fighting to save people...
If even someone like me...
...could go around truly
helping people like that...
...I think that would be...
It really isn't an
easy decision, is it?
And considering my position, I can't
rush you into deciding either.
Suggesting wishes would
also be against the rules.
So I guess just wishing to become
a magical girl wouldn't work, huh?
Is power for its own sake
what you desire, Madoka?
It isn't that.
...Or... Maybe it IS that...
I mean, I'm not very smart, and
I don't really have any talents.
So if I could become someone as
cool and wonderful as Mami...
...I'd be more than
happy with just that.
If you became a
magical girl, Madoka,
you'd be much more
powerful than Mami.
Huh?
Though, of course, part of that depends
on what kind of wish you make.
Even I can't completely gauge how large
the Soul Gem you'd create would be.
I've never met another girl with
such enormous potential as you.
You're just teasing me, right?
You do understand,
don't you?
That you're leading innocent
bystanders into real danger?
They were chosen
by Kyubey.
They're not innocent
bystanders anymore.
You're trying to lead them so that
they want to be magical girls.
And you don't like
that, I take it?
No. It's a problem.
... Particularly in the case
of Madoka Kaname.
I see. So you've noticed
it as well, have you?
That she has incredible potential.
She is the one person I absolutely
cannot allow to make the contract.
Afraid that a magical girl stronger
than you will get in your way?
That's the way a
bullied child thinks.
I have no wish
to fight you, but...
Then take care to ensure that our
paths will never cross again.
Tonight will probably
be the last time...
...that we will be able to speak
without coming to blows.
Hey. Sorry for the wait.
Huh? Weren't you able
to see Kamijo today?
Apparently, he couldn't be inconvenienced
to see me today or something.
Seriously, after I took all the trouble
to come here. How rude!
What's wrong?
There's... something
over there.
A Grief Seed!
It's about to hatch!
No way! Why here
of all places...?
This isn't good.
A Labyrinth is about
to open up here!
You mean one of
those crazy mazes?!
Madoka, do you have Mami's
phone number on you?
N-No...
This isn't good...
Madoka, find Mami
and bring her here.
I'll stay here and keep
an eye on that thing.
No!
That's too dangerous.
Though there's still time before
the witch emerges,
once the labyrinth pulls you inside,
you won't be able to leave it.
There's no guarantee that Mami
will get here in time to save you.
But once the labyrinth opens, we'll
lose track of the witch, won't we?
I can't afford to let
that happen. Not here...
Madoka, you go on ahead.
I'll stay here with Sayaka.
Huh?
Once Mami gets here, she'll be able
to track my position using telepathy.
So if I stay and watch the
Grief Seed with Sayaka,
I'll be able to guide Mami...
...down the shortest path to us.
Thank you, Kyubey!
Then, I'll find Mami and bring
her here as fast as I can!
Are you frightened, Sayaka?
Well, yeah... that kind of
goes without saying.
If you were just to
decide upon a wish...
...I could turn you into a magical
girl right here and now.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
If things get bad enough,
I may ask you to do that.
But I'll hold off for now.
Because this is such an
important decision to me...
...I don't want to make it
rashly if possible.
Here, right?
Kyubey, what's the situation?
We're still okay.
It looks like the witch isn't
going to hatch just yet.
Sayaka, are you okay?
Totally fine.
I'm so bored I'm about
to doze off in here!
Right now,
it'd be better not to use any large amounts
of magic that might disturb the egg.
There's no need to hurry,
so come to us as
quietly as you can.
Got it.
Thank goodness
we made it in time.
Though Sayaka took such a huge
risk that I'm actually a bit angry...
But in this one case, it was a good,
clear-headed call on her part.
This way, we won't have to worry
about the witch getting a–
I thought I told you I didn't
want to see you again.
I shall hunt this prey.
The two of you
should leave here.
I don't think so.
Miki and Kyubey are
waiting for us in there.
I shall guarantee
their safety.
And you think we
could trust you?
F-Fool!
This isn't the time for–
I don't want to hurt
you, of course.
But if you insist on struggling,
the cords will only tighten.
This witch is not
like the others!
Behave and I will release you
unharmed after I finish up here.
Let's go, Kaname.
O-Okay.
Wai–!
Um... Mami?
What is it?
I've been thinking really hard about
all sorts of different wishes, but...
Did you decide on one?
Yes.
But, I think it might be the naïve kind
of wish that would make you mad...
So what is this dream
you want granted?
Well, I've never been
good at school,
and I don't have any kind of talent
that I could take pride in...
And I'm sure I'll
continue on like this,
being no use to anyone and having
to bother others for help...
Thinking about that makes me
feel so awful, I can't stand it.
But then I met you, Mami.
And you showed me
what it's like...
...to fight to save people.
And then...
...when I heard that even I might
be able to do the same thing...
... it was the happiest thing I'd
ever experienced in my life.
That's why, I think that just becoming
a magical girl would fulfill my dreams.
If someone like me can help people
and live my life with pride...
That would be
my greatest dream.
It won't be easy,
you know?
You'll get injured,
and you won't have time to go on
dates or have fun with friends.
Even so, after watching the way
you keep doing your very best...
...I really look up
to you, Mami.
I'm really not worth
looking up to.
Huh?
I only push myself and
pretend to be cool.
Even when I'm scared, or hurting,
there's no one I can talk to.
All I can do is cry
on my own.
It isn't a good thing...
to be a magical girl.
But you're not alone
anymore, Mami.
You're right...
I'm not alone
anymore, am I?
Will you really stand and fight
with me from now on?
Will you really
stay with me?
Yes. If someone
like me will do.
Oh, goodness!
Some role model
I'm supposed to be.
I'm really no good
at this, am I?
Mami...
Still, it's not every day you
can have a wish granted.
So try to think of
something you want.
Yeah, it is a special
chance, isn't it?
You're still making
a contract, after all,
so you may as well get
something out of it.
You could wish to become a billionaire,
or maybe to have a perfect boyfriend.
Anything you want.
Um, but...
Okay, then how
about this?
If you can't decide on a wish by
the time I finish off this witch...
...we'll ask Kyubey to give us a huge
feast with a fabulous cake!
C-Cake?!
Yep!
The biggest and most
extravagant cake ever!
And with it, we'll have a
big party for everyone–
To celebrate the two of us
becoming a magical girl duo!
But I can't become a
magical girl for a cake!
No? Then decide on a wish
you really do want.
Mami!
The Grief Seed's moving!
It's going to hatch!
Hurry!
Okay! I've got it.
Today's a special day,
so I'll finish it off fast!
Wha! B-But–
I'm not afraid of
anything anymore.
Because... I'm not
alone anymore!
Sorry for the wait!
You're just in time!
Be careful.
It's coming!
Sorry to rain
on your parade.
But I'm going to
finish you right here!
Got you!
You did it!
TIRO–
FINALE!!
It can't be...
You two! Make a contract
with me right now!!
Madoka! Sayaka!
Decide on a wish! Hurry!
That won't be necessary.
I shall be the one to slay it.
A moment later and you
would have been dead.
Burn this sight
into your minds.
This is what it means
to be a magical girl.
...Give it back.
Give it back! That–
That belongs to Mami... !
I said to give it back!
Back to Mami!
That's right. This belongs
only to magical girls.
Neither of you has
any right to touch it.
While a woman's prime age for childbirth
is indeed based in medical fact...
...counting backwards
from there...
...to determine whether she
is of a marriageable age...
... is an extremely
grave mistake!
In other words...
...of course women
over the age of 30...
...still have a chance of marrying
for love. Therefore...
...we would use the present progressive
tense here instead of the past perfect–
It... feels like we're in a foreign
country or something.
Even though nothing about school or
Hitomi has changed since yesterday...
Somehow, it feels like I'm
surrounded by strangers...
It's because no one knows.
No one knows about
witches... or Mami...
It's because we know,
and no one else does.
It's like we're seeing and living in an
entirely different world from them.
Madoka, do you still want to
be a magical girl, even now?
Yeah, I know.
Well, I can't blame you.
I know it's unfair...
I know it's way too selfish of
me to back out now, but...
But I just can't.
Just thinking about
the way she died...
Even now, it gets so
hard to breathe...
I'm scared...
I don't want that... !
Hey, Kyubey... What's going
to happen to this town?
Who's going to fight to protect everyone
from the witches from now on?
This town has been Mami's
territory for a long time.
But once the other magical girls realize
she's gone, they won't stay back for long.
I'm sure one of them will arrive
here soon to hunt witches.
But all they care about are
finding Grief Seeds, right?
Just like that
transfer student.
It's true that magical girls
like Mami are rare.
Most do approach witch-hunting
with their own benefit in mind.
But it's natural for people to want
to be rewarded for their work.
Then–
But I think the only ones who have
a right to judge their actions...
...are their fellow magical girls, who
bear the same destiny they do.
All right, I understand.
It really is an awful shame, but
I can't force you, after all.
I guess this is
good-bye then.
I'd better go search for girls with greater
need to make a contract with me.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
No, I should apologize for getting
you mixed up in all this.
Though we weren't together for long,
thank you, Madoka. It was fun.
I'm sorry...
MAMI TOMOE
I'm sorry.
For being so weak...
I'm sorry...
Homura...
You're blaming yourself
too much for this.
Huh?
No one could criticize you
for anything you've done.
And even if they did,
I wouldn't permit it.
It seems you've taken
my warning to heart.
Yeah...
If I had only listened
to you earlier...
It wouldn't have changed
Mami Tomoe's fate.
But I was able to
change yours.
I'm glad I was able to save
at least one person.
S-Say, Homura...
You seem like you're a veteran too.
Though in a different way from Mami...
Perhaps. I won't
deny it, at least.
Have you seen a lot of people
die like yesterday?
Yes.
How many?
Too many to try keeping
count of anymore.
I wonder if Mami's apartment
will just stay like that.
Mami Tomoe had
no close relations.
It will be a long time before a missing
person's report will even be filed for her.
Then, no one will even know
that Mami is dead?
It can't be helped.
If someone dies on the other side,
there won't be a body left behind.
In this world, she will simply remain
a missing person forever.
That is the end that
all magical girls meet.
That's horrible!
She fought to protect everyone
for so long on her own!
To think that no one will
even realize she's dead...
...that's just too sad!
That is the nature of the contract
that grants us the power we hold.
And we don't fight
to protect people.
We fight for the sake
of our own wishes.
If our deaths go
unnoticed by others...
and we are ultimately
forgotten by this world...
I suppose that
cannot be helped.
I won't forget...
I'll never forget
about Mami!
Never!
I see.
I'm sure with that alone, Mami
Tomoe must truly be happy.
I envy her.
You too, Homura!
You too–
I swear I'll never
forget you either!
I'll never forget...
...the way you saved
us yesterday!
Homura...?
You're too kind for
your own good.
Huh?
Remember this...
That kindness may bring about
an even greater tragedy.
What are you listening to?
"The Girl With the Flaxen Hair."
Ah, by Debussy, right?
It's such a beautiful song!
I-I guess I don't strike people as the type
who would listen to classical music.
Sometimes, people get so surprised
when I can name a piece like that.
I guess it's so unexpected, people
sometimes get impressed with me.
It's only because you taught
me about all this.
If not for you, I may never have given
classical music a real chance.
Maybe not for my
whole life, even.
Hey, Sayaka...
What is it?
Are you torturing me?
Why are you still making
me listen to music?
Are you trying to
cause me more pain?
But I thought you loved
music, Kyosuke...
I don't want to
hear it anymore!
I don't want to hear these songs
that I can't ever play again–
That I can only ever
listen to anymore!
I just... I just...
I can't move it...
I can't even feel
the pain anymore!
What use is a hand
like this...?
It's going to be okay.
I'm sure someday,
somehow...
Just don't give up hope,
and I'm sure someday–
But they've already
told me to give up.
They said I had no chance
of ever performing again.
The doctor came and
told me himself.
He said that with current medicine,
it just wasn't possible.
My hand will never move again.
Not until the day miracles or magic
start existing in this world.
They do exist.
Miracles... and magic... are real!
Homura...
When I actually tried talking with her,
it seemed like we could really be friends.
So why did she end up
fighting with Mami?
Huh?
Hitomi?
Hitomi!
Don't you have
your lessons to–
Huh? It's the same
as that woman's–
Hitomi!
Hey! Hitomi, come on!
Ah, Kaname!
Good evening.
What's happened to you?
Where are you going?
Where am I going, you ask?
I'm going somewhere
far better than here...
Hitomi...
Oh, yes. You simply
must come along!
Yes, indeed. It would
be so wonderful!
What should I do?
This couldn't be...?
If only I could
contact Homura...
Oh, but I don't have her
cell phone number!
It's true... I'm completely...
worthless...
I couldn't even keep such
a tiny factory running...
In an era like this one...
...there's just no place
for someone like me...
Stop!
You can't use those!
You mustn't interfere.
This is a sacred ceremony.
But those chemicals!
They're dangerous!
Everyone here will die!
That's right.
All of us are going to journey to a
magnificent new world together.
Don't you see how
wonderful that will be?
These physical bodies would
simply get in our way.
Kaname, I'm sure you'll
understand very soon...
Let go of me!
What should I do?!
No!! No...
This can't...
No! Someone help me!
I wonder if this...
... is my punishment.
For being...
...a coward...
...and a liar.
I guess this...
... is a fitting punishment.
Sayaka?!
This is the end for you!!
Hey, sorry about that!
I cut it pretty darn
close, didn't I?
Sayaka...
Those clothes...
Huh? Oh...
Uh, well. Guess I had
a change of heart.
Oh, I'll be fine!
After all, I did pretty well for
my first time out, didn't I?
But...
You...
Aren't you pretty late,
Transfer Student?
It's been a while since
I've felt this good.
I'm totally refreshed!
Sayaka... Aren't you
scared at all?
Huh?
Well, I am a little.
But I was able to beat that witch
yesterday pretty easily.
And when I think of how I might've
lost both of my best friends...
...that scares me a lot more.
Which is why...
I don't really know what to call
it. Self-confidence, maybe?
Or relief?
I guess I'm a little bit proud
of myself right now, too.
Anyway!
I'm really getting fired
up for this now.
From here on, I
- Magical Girl Sayaka -
will keep Mitakihara City
super-duper safe and sound!
You really don't have
any regrets at all?
Well... If I have any regret...
... it's probably that I
hesitated for so long.
Since I ended up
doing it anyway,
I feel like I should have
made up my mind sooner.
If I had been there to fight
that witch with Mami,
then maybe she wouldn't
have had to die.
I...
Come on, you're not thinking
something silly, are you?
I... I should've...
It's easy for me to say so only because
I have become one already.
The important thing is that
I've made my decision.
Honestly, I really do think I was
meant to be a magical girl.
Sayaka...
After all, I found something
I truly wished for.
Something that I wouldn't mind
having to risk my life fighting for.
Having a wish that strong
gives me reason enough.
I guess the one
frustrating thing...
... is how long it took me to realize
how much it meant to me.
Which is to say, you have
no reason to feel guilty.
This just means there's no problem if you
don't want to become a magical girl.
Anyhow! It's about
time I got going.
Do you have something
to do this afternoon?
Yeah, sort of.
I see. So they're not
discharging you yet?
I've still got to finish
my leg rehabilitation.
After all, I can't do much of anything
until I can walk again.
Plus, we still have no idea why my
hand suddenly healed like that.
So the doctors want me to stay
to run a few more tests on it.
And how do you feel, Kyosuke?
Does any part of your body
feel strange at all?
No. In fact, I feel so fine
that it's a little scary.
The accident almost feels
like a bad dream now.
So much that I sometimes wonder
what I'm doing in this bed.
It's just like you said, Sayaka...
It's a miracle.
What's the matter?
I... said some really awful
things to you, Sayaka.
Just because I was depressed,
it doesn't excuse–
Oh, forget about
stuff like that!
Right now, you should be completely
over-the-moon happy about your hand.
So don't make
a face like that.
Right...
Though it still hasn't
really sunk in.
Well, that's no surprise.
Ah, it's about time.
Kyosuke, why don't we
go out for some air?
What are we going
to the roof for?
You'll see.
Why are all of you...?
We'll have the real party after you get
released from the hospital, but...
Since your hand
healed already...
Is that...?
You told me to
get rid of it, but...
I just couldn't bear
to throw it away.
I...
Go on, give it a try.
Don't be afraid.
Mami...
My wish has been granted.
There's no way
I'll ever regret it.
This is the happiest
moment of my life.
So that's the city's
new magical girl, huh?
Are you really going to
pick a fight with her?
Sure, seems like
an easy win to me.
She won't even know
what hit her.
Or, what?
You got a problem
with that?
It may not all work out
the way you imagine.
There is another
magical girl in this city.
Huh? Who is it?
I'm not really sure myself.
Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
If she's a magical girl, she must've
made a contract with you, right?
You could say yes.
You could also say no.
She's quite the "irregularity."
Even I can't guess when
or where she'll strike.
Hmm... Sounds good to me!
Gettin' kinda boring
around here, anyway.
Gotta shake things up once
in a while after all!
Are you nervous?
Yeah, kind of.
After all, one mistake
and I'm done for.
Madoka?
Sayaka... Are you going to...?
Yep! Time to patrol
for wicked witches!
After all, that's a duty
of any ally of justice!
Will you really be all
right on your own?
I'll be just fine.
Mami always did this
on her own too.
As her successor, I can
do that much, at least!
Um... I know I can't
do anything to help,
and I'll probably just
get in your way...
But -
As long as I'm not
being a bother -
For as far as you
can take me...
Please let me
come with you?
Aren't you trying
a little too hard?
I-I'm sorry...
I'm asking too much.
I knew I'd be a bother...
No - I'm really
happy you asked!
You could tell,
couldn't you?
That my hands were shaking?
They haven't stopped
this whole time.
Pathetic, aren't I?
Even though I've become a
full-fledged magical girl,
I get so scared
when I'm alone...
Sayaka...
You wouldn't be a bother.
I'd really like you to come.
Just knowing I'll have someone with
me makes me feel incredibly brave!
I feel like I could beat up
100 bad guys!
I...
I swear I'll keep you safe.
So come with me, and don't
worry about a thing.
Let's go hunt witches together,
just like we used to.
Okay.
This is it.
This labyrinth was probably made
by a familiar, not a witch.
It'd be nice if I
can beat it easily.
I'm still new at
this, after all.
Getting caught off guard
could be fatal.
I know.
Is that it?!
It's getting away!
Leave it to me!
Hey, hold on now.
What do you think
you're doing?
Wha...?
It's getting away!
Can't you tell just by looking at it?
That was a familiar, not a witch.
You weren't gonna get any
Grief Seeds off of that one.
But -
If we just leave it alone, it might
go off and kill someone!
I'm telling you.
You should wait for it to eat 4 or 5
people and become a real witch.
That way, you'll be sure to get
a Grief Seed when you kill it.
Seriously, what were you thinking killing
the goose before it laid its golden eggs?
What...?
What about the
people it'll attack?
Are you just going to sit back
and let them get killed?
As long as we collect
enough Grief Seeds,
we can do as we please with our
magical powers for the rest of our lives.
Looking at it that way, it's worth making
a contract with Kyubey, isn't it?
Listen, kid - you've got this whole
thing all wrong from the get-go.
Ever heard of
the food chain?
They taught you about
it in school, right?
Witches eat weak humans.
And in turn, we eat
those witches.
It's the basic rule
of this world.
The weak have to give
way to the strong.
Oh no...
You...
Don't tell me...
...you actually believe in all that "saving
people" and "justice" crap?
You didn't actually make the contract
over that load of bull, did you?
And what if I did?
Come on. Give it up already.
The way you're butting into this
and acting like it's a game...
It kinda ticks me off.
Sayaka!
Hmph! What an amateur...
Go cool your head
for a while.
Strange...
That should've put you out of
commission for at least 3 months.
Is Sayaka really okay?
It's because she made her contract
wishing for someone to be healed.
She heals twice as fast as a regular
human being does now.
Who... would lose to you?
It's because of magical girls
like you that Mami...
That pisses me off.
That REALLY pisses me off.
But seriously - you sure
have a mouth on you.
That's not how you're supposed
to speak to your elders.
Shut up!
This ain't the time to be
jumping around, dummy!
Sayaka... !
Madoka, it's dangerous for
you to get any closer!
You don't get it when
I try to explain.
I beat it into you.
Guess there's no choice but
to kill an idiot like you!
I won't lose...
I won't lose to you!
Why...?
Why is this happening?
She's not a witch.
Why are the two of them fighting
when they should be allies?
It can't be helped.
Neither of them is willing to back
down from the other now.
Please, Kyubey...
Make them stop!
This can't be right!
I don't have the ability
to stop them.
But...
If you're determined to stop them, even
if it means using force, there IS a way...
Only another magical girl could
get between them now.
But you have the qualifications
to become one, after all.
If you truly wish it, that is.
That's right...
I can make the contract...
It's over!
I...
There's no need for that.
Homura...?
You!
Wha–
What the hell did you do?
Oh, I see. You're that
"irregularity", aren't you?
What the heck kind of
magic are you using?
Stay out of our way!
Sayaka!
She's all right.
She's only unconscious.
Who the hell are you?
Whose side are
you on, anyway?
I am on the side of those
who think rationally,
and an enemy to those who
engage in needless conflict.
Which are you...
... Kyoko Sakura?
Have we met
somewhere before?
Perhaps. Who knows?
Since I don't know
anything about you...
Well, I'll be taking
my leave for today.
That's wise of you.
You... saved us?
How many times
must I warn you?
How foolish can
you possibly be?
You should not become
involved in this.
I've told you many
times already.
But I...
If reasoning with a fool won't work,
I will turn to more drastic measures.
Homura... Why...?
In any case, it's certain that
she's planning something.
We'll have to be more
careful than ever.
Yo! So what do
you want now?
I want to put this city
in your charge.
And why the sudden
change of heart?
Girls like you are most suited
to be magical girls.
Sayaka Miki is not qualified.
Hmph!
Well, that's what I was planning
from the start anyway.
So what about
that Sayaka girl?
If I leave her alone, she'll
probably come bug me again.
I want that settled as
peaceably as possible.
You keep out of it.
I will handle her myself.
You haven't told me the most
important thing, though.
Who the heck are you?
What's in all of
this for you?
Two weeks from now, "Walpurgisnacht"
will descend upon this city.
How do you know that?
That is a secret.
In any case, if we are
able to defeat it,
I will leave this city, and you will be
free to do with it as you please.
"Walpurgisnacht, " huh?
Guess it would be pretty tough
to beat it by yourself.
But if we double-teamed it,
we could probably win.
Want some?
WELCOME HOME.
THERE'S SOME POTATO
SALAD IN THE FRIDGE.
-TOMO
Can't sleep?
No... Can we talk?
One of my friends...
is in a lot of trouble.
Even though she keeps trying so hard to
do the right thing, the more she tries,
the worse things get for her...
That happens quite a bit.
It's sad to say,
but just because you keep
trying to do what's right...
doesn't mean you're guaranteed
a happy ending.
What do you think
I should do?
In a case like this,
no one else can bring about
a neat and tidy end to it.
But would you still want
to help resolve it,
even if it wasn't a neat
and tidy resolution?
Yes.
Then you should make
a mistake for her.
Make a mistake...?
Sometimes you tell an awful lie, or
run away from something scary...
...and then later look back...
... and realize that that was actually
precisely the right thing to do, right?
If you can see there's no way for your
friend's problem to end but in disaster...
... it'd be better for her to crash and
burn sooner rather than later.
But do you think she'll understand
that I'm doing it for her own good?
Sometimes they do, sometimes
they don't - especially at first.
But I warned you it wouldn't
be a pretty ending.
So what seems
better to you?
To give up on your friend, or to
be misunderstood by her?
Madoka... you've grown up
to be a very good girl.
You don't tell lies
or do bad things.
You always try your best
to do the right thing.
You've already passed your
childhood with flying colors.
Which is why it may
be good for you...
... before you become an adult
- to learn how to mess up, too.
Learn how to mess up?
After all, wounds heal faster
when you're young.
If you learn how to fall well now,
I'm sure it'll help you later in life.
When you grow up, you see,
the consequences for messing
up get bigger and bigger.
The more responsibilities
you start shouldering,
the more important it gets not
to make a wrong move.
But isn't that...
really painful?
Oh, us adults are
always in pain.
That's why we're allowed
to drink alcohol!
I wish I could hurry up and drink
alcohol with you too, Mom.
Then grow up super-fast, my dear.
For adults, it's only
as fun as it hurts!
Oh!
If you're looking for Mr. Kamijo,
he was discharged yesterday.
He was doing so well with
his physical therapy...
KAMIJO
...that they moved up
his discharge date.
Going home without
even seeing him?
After you spent the whole day
running around chasing him?
You...
I know who you're after.
The little rich boy who
lives here, right?
The one you made the contract
with Kyubey for...?
Jeez!
You wasted your once-in-a-lifetime
miracle on something that stupid?
What would you know?!
Apparently, a lot more
than you, dummy!
Magic is only supposed to be used
to grant wishes for yourself.
If you use it for somebody else,
it always ends up going bad.
Didn't Mami Tomoe even
teach you that much?
If all you wanted was to
possess the boy you love,
aren't there a lot of
better ways to do it?
After all, you've got
all that magic now...
What?
You should bust in
there right now...
...and break his arms and legs so bad
he'll never be able to use them again.
Make him so helpless he won't be
able to do anything without you.
Do that, and this time, he really
will be yours and yours alone.
Both his body and heart
will be all yours...
If you don't have the guts to do it, I
wouldn't mind busting him up for you.
You know, as a favor to
my fellow magical girl?
It'd be so easy
to do, too...
No way...
You are the one person
I'll never forgive!
This time, it ends!
Let's take this
some place else.
We're bound to attract
attention here.
Your friend is trying
so hard to do right...
...that someone's got to make
some mistakes for her.
But how could I ever...?
Madoka...
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in trouble!
Come with me!
We won't have to
hold back up here.
So gimme your best shot!
Wait! Sayaka!
Madoka... !
Don't get in my way! You
don't even belong here!
You can't do this!
This just can't be right!
Hmph! Annoying jerks sure
attract annoying friends.
Then what kind of friends
would you have, I wonder?
This isn't what
we agreed on.
I thought I told you to leave
Sayaka Miki alone.
Well your way would've
been too soft!
Besides, it's not like
she's backing down...
I'll take her on, then.
Stay out of it.
You got until I finish
eating this then.
That's all I'll need.
Don't underestimate me!
Sayaka!
I'm sorry!
Madoka! How could you...?!
Because if I hadn't–
Sayaka?
That wasn't good,
Madoka...
No matter how
mad you are,
you shouldn't throw your own
friend away like that.
What?
What did you say?
No, stop!
What the heck is this?!
She's dead!
Sayaka?
Hey, Sayaka...?
Wake up! Hey!
Come on...
What's wrong?
I don't want this...
Sayaka... !
What the hell is
going on here?
Hey!
It's because the furthest you magical
girls can control your bodies...
...would be within about
a 100 meter radius.
100 meters? What are
you talking about?
What do you mean?!
You rarely have this
sort of accident...
... because you usually carry
it with you all the time...
What are you saying,
Kyubey?!
You have to help her!
Don't let Sayaka die... !
Madoka, that isn't Sayaka.
It's just an empty shell.
Huh?
Sayaka is what you just threw
away a moment ago.
What... did you say?
Did you really think you
could fight witches...
...with the same fragile bodies
that humans possess?
It's unthinkable.
For magical girls,
those so-called "bodies" that you possess
are really just exterior hardware.
Your real bodies
are your souls,
and in order to make them able
to use magic more efficiently,
we put them in these compact,
easy-to-protect forms instead.
To complete the contract to
become a magical girl...
...what I do is rip your souls out of your
bodies and turn them into Soul Gems.
Bastard... What have you done...?!
You've gotta be
kidding me!
So now you've made us into
zombies or something?!
But isn't it handy
this way?
Even if your body's
heart gets crushed,
or you bleed out your very
last drop of blood...
...you can just heal your bodies with
magic and get right back up!
So long as your Soul Gem
remains unharmed...
...you're basically invincible!
Isn't that a lot better for battle than
those breakable human bodies?
That's horrible...
Too horrible for words...
You humans always
react this way.
Whenever I try to tell
you the simple facts,
you inevitably have
this same reaction...
I just don't get it.
Why are humans so touchy about
the placement of their souls?
What?
What is it?
Stand.
Bow.
Homura... Did you know?
Then why didn't
you tell us?
I've tried telling
others in the past.
Not a single one has
ever believed me.
Why would Kyubey do
something so cruel to us?
Because it doesn't
think of it as cruel.
It is a life form that cannot
comprehend human values.
It would probably insist that it is simply
fair payment for the miracles it grants.
But it's not a fair
exchange at all!
To have that done
to her body...
when all Sayaka wanted was to heal
the wounds of the boy she loved!
That doesn't change the fact
that it was a miracle.
Because it made something
impossible possible.
Even if Sayaka Miki had spent
her entire life caring for him,
that boy never would have
regained the ability to perform.
In truth, the value of a miracle is far
greater than that of an entire human life.
And it is that which
that creature sells.
So Sayaka will never be able
to go back to her old life?
Unless she uses her magical power,
she won't need a Grief Seed, will she?
She doesn't need to
fight witches, right?
Even just maintaining our bodies,
we consume magical power little by little.
Therefore, we will need
a Grief Seed, eventually.
The only way to get them
is to defeat witches.
You should give up
on Sayaka Miki.
But Sayaka saved my life!
If she hadn't become
a magical girl then,
both Hitomi and I
would have died!
Don't confuse gratitude
with responsibility.
You have no ability
to save Sayaka Miki.
If you hope to repay her in order to
alleviate your own sense of guilt, don't.
There is no need for
such presumption.
Homura, why are you
always so cold?
Perhaps...
... it is because I, too,
am no longer human...
You tricked us,
didn't you?
I told you precisely what
I wanted from the start:
For you to become
magical girls.
I just didn't explain exactly what
form you'd be taking to do that.
Why didn't you
ever tell us?!
Because you
never asked.
Even though you didn't know, there
wouldn't have been any inconvenience.
In fact, even Mami never
noticed to the very end.
I put your souls in a form that's easier
to keep track of and protect.
That makes it as safe as possible
for you to battle witches. Right?
Well, no one asked for your "help"
with something so ridiculous!
You still don't fully understand
what it is to do battle, do you?
This is what real
"pain" feels like.
See? You could be totally
incapacitated with just one hit.
You only managed to finish
the fight with Kyoko...
... because you were spared the
full extent of your body's pain.
It was only possible because your mind
and body weren't directly connected.
And as a result, you were able
to live through that fight.
Once you get better at it,
you can even detach yourself enough
to block out all sense of pain.
Why...? Why would you do
such a thing to us...?!
Before you took on this destiny
of battling witches,
wasn't there a wish
you wanted granted?
That wish has really
come true, hasn't it?
Now that I've got
a body like this...
... how can I possibly
face Kyosuke again?
How long are you planning to sit
up there moping, blockhead?
Can you come out
for a sec?
I wanna talk.
What did you bring me all
the way out here for?
It's gonna be kind
of a long talk.
Want one?
Don't ever waste food.
I'll kill you if you do.
See... this was
my dad's church.
He was an overly kind
and earnest man.
Like, the type who cries reading the
morning paper every morning...
and seriously thinks about
how to make things better.
He thought that in order to
save a new generation,
we needed to have
a new religion.
That's what he
always said.
That's why, one day,
he started preaching stuff that wasn't
in the Bible to his parishioners.
Naturally, people stopped
coming to his sermons.
Then he got excommunicated
by the church...
...and no one would listen
to his words anymore.
I guess it was only
natural, huh?
From the outside, he probably
looked like some raving cultist.
No matter how
right he was,
no matter how logical the
things he said were,
the world only saw him
as some crazy outcast.
It got to the point where our entire
family didn't even have food to eat.
I just couldn't
understand it.
My dad wasn't saying anything
that was wrong.
It was just different from what
people were used to hearing.
If they would've given him just 5 minutes
to hear what he had to say,
anyone would've agreed
that he was right.
But no one would listen.
I got angry.
I couldn't accept it.
I couldn't stand that nobody
would give my dad a chance...
...and understand
what he was saying.
So I asked Kyubey...
...to make everyone listen seriously
to what my dad said.
The next morning, the church was
packed full of people again.
Every day, they came in bigger and bigger
crowds to hear my dad speak.
And as for me, I happily began
my work as a magical girl.
After all, even if my dad was
preaching truth to the world,
someone still had to take
care of the witches.
And so...
... like an idiot, I thought of it as my role,
and threw myself into witch-hunting.
I thought that
my dad and me–
one from the front,
one from the shadows–
were going to save
this world together.
But one day, my dad
found out about me.
When he heard that all the
people were there...
because I'd used magic
to make them come,
and not because they really
believed, he flipped out.
He called me - his own daughter - a
witch who tainted people's hearts.
Isn't that hilarious?
After I'd been out hunting
real witches every night!
After that, my dad
had a breakdown.
He was miserable
in the end.
He wasted away from drinking so much,
got messed up in the head...
...then finally killed my whole family
and committed suicide.
Leaving only me behind...
My wish destroyed
my whole family.
Right then, I vowed in my heart never to
use magic to help anyone else again.
I would use
this power up...
...for my sake
and mine alone.
Miracles aren't free,
you know.
If you wish for hope,
an equal amount of despair will
be rained down upon you, too.
That's how everything
stays in equilibrium...
...and the world's balance
doesn't get disturbed.
Why are you telling
me all of this?
'Cause you should just quit caring
and do whatever you want, too.
"You get what you
pay for, " right?
Now, that's odd.
Since you only live
for your own benefit,
why are you worrying
about me, all of sudden?
'Cause you started off with
the same mistake as me.
You shouldn't keep living the kind of life
that's gonna bring you more regrets.
I mean, you've already paid your dues
- and paid way too high a price.
So now, you should just think about
how to get your money's worth.
Like you do?
Yep.
I've already figured out how
things really stand,
but you're continuing on
with the wrong idea.
I couldn't watch you
go on like that.
I was really wrong about you.
I apologize for that, really.
But even then, I don't regret making
my wish for someone else's sake.
To make sure the feelings I made that
wish with never become a lie,
I've decided I'll never
regret anything. Ever.
Why are you–
Actually,
I don't think I paid
too high a price.
Because, depending on how we use it, this
magic can be used for wonderful things.
Which reminds me...
Those apples...
How did you get them?
Where did you get the
money to pay for them?
You can't answer
me, can you?
In that case, I can't
eat those apples.
You jerk!
We're magical girls!
There's no one else who
can do what we do!
I'll do things my own way
and continue my own fight.
If that interferes
with your life,
you're welcome to come
and try to kill me again.
I won't lose to you.
Nor will I resent you
or anyone else.
Sayaka! Good morning!
Good morning, Sayaka.
H-Hey!
Good morning!
Where were you
yesterday?
Oh, I was just feeling
a little sick...
Sayaka...
It's okay. I feel
all right now.
You don't have
to worry.
Well, then! Let's do
our best today–
Oh!
Has Kamijo already been
released from the hospital?
Kamijo, are you really okay
to come to school already?
Yeah.
If I just sat bundled
up at home,
it wouldn't help my leg
rehab much anyway.
I'm aiming to walk without
crutches again by next week.
I'm so glad for Kamijo.
Yeah...
You should go say
hi to him, Sayaka.
You haven't talked
to him yet, right?
I'm... fine here.
So...
What did you want
to talk about?
About love.
I have a secret that I've been keeping
from both you and Madoka.
Huh? Um, okay...
For a long time now, I...
...have been in love
with Kyosuke Kamijo.
O-Oh, really?
I never would've
guessed, Hitomi!
Kyosuke, the lucky guy–
Sayaka, you were a childhood
friend of Kamijo's, weren't you?
Y-Yeah, or, um, maybe more of
a tag-along or something...
Was it really only that?
I've decided not to lie
to myself any longer.
How about you?
Sayaka, can you face
your true feelings?
W-What are you
talking about?
You are a precious
friend to me.
That's why I don't want to cut in
or steal him out of your hands.
The amount of time you spend looking
at him surpasses even mine.
So I think you have the right
to try for him before me.
Hitomi...
I will confess my love to Kamijo
after school tomorrow.
I will wait one
full day for you.
So please decide what to do so
you won't have regrets, Sayaka.
Decide whether you want to confess
your feelings to Kamijo, or not...
I-I...
Madoka...
Is it okay if I come along?
I don't want you to be all alone,
Sayaka. So please...
You... Why...?
Why are you so nice?
I don't deserve
such kindness...
What?
I had a moment today, where
I almost regretted something.
For just a split-second,
I thought,
"If only I hadn't saved
Hitomi that time... "
I completely fail at being
an ally of justice.
How will I ever
face Mami?
I'm going to lose
Kyosuke to Hitomi... !
And there's nothing
I can do...
Because I'm already dead...
Because I'm a zombie... !
I can't ask him to hold me
when I have a body like this!
I can't ever ask
him to kiss me!
Thank you...
I'm sorry.
Sayaka...
I'm okay now.
I got it all out.
Now, let's go.
We've got some more
witches to beat up today!
Okay.
It's not like you to just
sit quietly and watch.
She's battling a witch
today, not a familiar.
It's sure to drop
a Grief Seed.
So it isn't a waste
this time.
But I'm surprised that you're handing
over your prey for such a reason.
That idiot! How long does
it take her to finish it!?
Sayaka!
For Pete's sake! I just
can't watch this!
Just get back for now.
I'll show you how it's done!
Hey!
Stay out of my way.
I can do this alone.
Sayaka!
You... you're not...?
It's really true!
If I just detach myself...
...I really don't feel any pain!
It's easy once you
know how to do it.
I'm sure I'll never
lose this way.
It's yours.
That's what you're
after, isn't it?
Hey...
I don't want to be
in your debt.
Now we're even, got it?
Come on, let's go, Madoka.
Sayaka...
Ah... Sorry...
I'm just... a little tired...
Sayaka...
That way of fighting...
it's no good...
You say it doesn't hurt,
but you're lying.
I can tell just by
looking at you.
Just because you don't feel it,
it doesn't mean it's okay to get hurt.
If I don't fight like
that, I can't win.
Because I don't have
any natural talent.
Even if you can use
that method to win,
it doesn't mean it's
good for you, Sayaka.
What's "good for me?"
With my body this way, what
could ever be "good for me?"
Sayaka...
All I can do now
is kill witches...
That's the only worth I
have left in this world.
I'm just a walking, talking corpse,
pretending it's still alive.
What kind of "good" could anyone
possibly do for me now?
It's stupid to even
think about it.
But I just want to make you
happy again, Sayaka...
Then you fight them.
If you really want to
do something for me,
you should experience what
I've experienced first.
You can't, can you?
Of course not.
You can't give up being human
just out of a little pity, can you?!
Pity...?! That's not...
In place of you, who could
accomplish anything but won't–
I am suffering
in your stead!
So don't talk like you care, when you've
conveniently overlooked that!
Sayaka...
Don't follow me!
HOMURA
Walpurgisnacht's descent will
occur within this area...
How do you know?
Statistics.
Statistics?
I've never heard that Walpurgisnacht
appeared in this town before.
So what "statistics" are
you estimating with?
Look, I'm not saying we should
trust each other or anything,
but can't you show me your
hand just a little bit more?
I'd certainly like
to ask the same...
... Homura Akemi.
You've got some nerve
showing your face here!
My, my. I take it I'm an
uninvited guest here?
And here I came all this way just to give
you some important information...
Sayaka Miki's deterioration is happening
far quicker than I expected.
It isn't just all the
magic she's using...
She, herself, has begun
to curse the world.
And who's fault do you
think that is, huh?
At this rate,
she'll be causing you
some trouble...
... before Walpurgisnacht descends.
You'd best be on your guard.
What? What's that
supposed to mean?
Perhaps you should ask
her instead of me.
I'm sure you already know what
I'm talking about, Homura Akemi.
I thought so.
Just where did you learn
such interesting things?
I'm very, very
curious to know...
Are you by chance...
I've heard all I care
to hear from you.
Begone.
You're just letting him go?
There's no point in
killing that creature.
More importantly, what's
up with Sayaka Miki?
What's this "trouble" that fuzz
ball was talking about?
Her Soul Gem has
become too tainted.
If it is not purified soon, there will
be no coming back for her...
HOMURA AKEMI
But Shizuki...
I never realized that your
house was in this direction.
I feel like I've never seen you
walking home this way before...
You're right.
To be honest, I live in exactly
the opposite direction.
Huh? Then why did you
walk this way today?
Because, Kamijo...
I have something
I need to tell you.
No way, man, you can't let the
dumb slut make any excuses.
Gotta get her to fork over all the
money she makes, no shit.
Yeah, seriously, man...
You just can't treat women
like rational human beings.
You give'em an inch and they're all over
you, whining to get married and shit.
You just can't let
up on them.
God, they're so annoying when
it comes time to dump them.
You are really good at dumpin'
hoes, though, Sho. I envy you!
Dude, I gotta learn from you.
Hey, tell me more about her.
Um, what?
The woman you were talking
about just now.
Tell me more about her.
Are you a middle schooler, kid?
You shouldn't be out this late.
That woman... she probably loves you
and tries hard to make you happy.
I bet you know that
too, don't you?
And yet you call her a dog? Have
you never told her, "thank you"?
Are you really going to dump her
once she stops being useful?
What the... Do you
know this kid?
No...
Hey... is this world even
worth protecting?
What have I been fighting
for all this time?
Tell me.
You, right now. Tell me.
Or else, I'll...
Sayaka... Where are you?
Are you upset
with me, too?
If I was, would you
turn Sayaka back?
I can't. It's beyond
my power to do that.
Hey...
You once told me that I could become
an incredibly powerful magical girl.
Was that true?
"Incredible" doesn't even
begin to describe it.
Your power would be almost
incomprehensible!
You'd probably be the strongest
being in this world!
If I had made the
contract with you...
...would Sayaka not have had
to become a magical girl?
Sayaka had her
own wish as well.
You really had nothing to
do with her decision.
Why me, though?
I have no idea, either.
Truth be told,
your latent potential is on a scale that
theoretically shouldn't even be possible.
If you were to
release your power,
the miracle you could unleash might
twist the very fabric of the universe.
Why you alone should carry
such unthinkable power...
I can't guess the
reason right now.
I...
I always thought there was
nothing special about me.
That I would just kind of
stumble through life,
never being able to help anyone
or be of any use at all.
Madoka, if you wished it...
...you could even become
the god of this world.
Then...
Would I be able to do things that
even you can't do, Kyubey?
What do you mean?
If I made a contract with you, would I be
able to turn Sayaka human again?
That would be child's
play for you.
Would that be worth trading
your soul for, then?
For Sayaka, yes.
I'll do it.
Make me into a mag–
Th-That's horrible...
You didn't have to kill him–
You–
Why must you always try to
sacrifice yourself like that?
Huh?
Calling yourself useless,
and meaningless...
Don't treat yourself
like you don't matter!
Think about all the people who
consider you precious!
Stop being such a fool!
There are so many people who
would grieve if you died.
Why can't you
understand that?!
What about the people who are
trying so hard to protect you?!
Homura... !
Have the two of us...
met somewhere before...?
That's...
I'm sorry.
I've got to go find Sayaka.
Wait!
Sayaka Miki is already...
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Wait!
Madoka!
You knew there was
no point in doing that.
You just don't
learn, do you?
I have countless
spares, of course,
but making me use them up
for no reason like this...
It's a waste.
That's the second time
you've killed me.
But thanks to that, I was finally able to
see what your magical specialty is.
That was Time Magic,
wasn't it?
That's what I thought.
I had suspected as
much already, but...
You're not from this
timeline, are you?
I know what you really are
and what you're planning.
I see.
So that's why you've been trying so
hard to keep interfering with me.
Do you want to change Madoka
Kaname's fate that badly?
Yes.
I won't let things go according
to your plans, Kyubey.
Or should I say...
..."Incubator"?
Found you at last!
How long were you planning to
go on being stubborn like this?
I'm sorry for making
you look for me.
What?
That doesn't sound like you.
It's because I just can't care
about anything anymore.
I can't even remember what I thought was
so important, so worth protecting...
None of it makes
sense anymore.
Hey...
Hope and despair balance
back out to zero...
You told me that
once, didn't you?
Now I get what
you meant.
It's true that I've
saved a few people.
But in equal measure, my heart became
filled with resentment and hatred.
So much so that I even
hurt my dearest friend.
Sayaka! You didn't–?
For as much happiness as
we wish on one person,
we can't help but
curse someone else.
That's how it works
for us magical girls.
I was stupid... so stupid.
Sayakaaaa!!
In this country, half-grown women
are called "girls," right?
In that case,
it's appropriate that you, who will
one day grow into witches,
should be called "magical girls."