--==本字幕由 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩字幕 请关注 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric
Life was given to us a billion years ago.
What have we done with it?
Lucy?
It's as easy as pie. In and out, all done and dusted.
Then why don't do it yourself?
The last thing the guy is expecting is a total 10 turning up to deliver the case.
You'll blow his mind. Come on.
What's in it?
Sweetheart...
Don't get paranoid on me, alright? You trust me, don't you?
Richard, I really do like you but...
I've to take care of myself right now, I got a...
I don't know, I gotta concentrate on so many things.
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
I'm going home because I have exams on Monday.
I have to shower and I have to study, OK?
You know what? The other day I was in this museum and you know what I found out?
What?
The first ever woman was named Lucy.
Is that suppose to make me feel better?
Yeah...
- No.  - I'll call you, OK?
OK! OK! OK!
I'll be honest with you. I can't deliver the case myself.
I've a little falling out with the guy. It's nothing major...
but if it's you, problem solved.
You walk in there, you go up to the reception,
you ask Mr. Jang to come down.
He comes down, he takes the case, you flash him your prettiest smile and bounce.
Look, you can even see the reception from here.
Come on.
- What's in the case?  - I don't know, it's just some paperwork.
- Yeah? Let's see it then.  - It's locked
and no one but Mr. Jang has the code.
I'm just the delivery boy.
- Do you get paid to do this?  - Yeah, kinda.
Like how much?
OK, we're negotiating now or ...?
No, no, how much do you get paid? I want to know, how much?
A thousand dollars.
You get paid a thousand dollars for delivering paperwork, really?
I don't know, it takes me 10 minutes and they're paying a grand and the rest is none of my business.
Well, it's not my business either. I'll tell you now...
- Listen!  - What?
We split it down the middle.
That's 500 for you and 500 for me.
- Richard, I will call you.  - Listen! It is the third time this week
I'm showing up at the same hotel with the same cowboy hat.
Problem solved.
- Go! Go! I'll wait for you to go.  - Lucy, honey,
I... I've done this a dozen times.
It's paperwork! It's probably just some designs they swept so they can copy them.
That's how it works in this country.
Even my Stetson was made here. Look!
It says so on the label: "Made in Taiwan"
So long, cowboy, with a fake Stetson.
Baby, please!
Richard, I gotta go.
- What the hell are you doing?  - I'm sorry.
- What the hell are you do...  - I'm so sorry. I really need your help.
Stop it! Stop it! Take this off me, right now!
- I can't!  - Take this off me, right now!
- I can't! Mr. Jang is the only one who has the key!  - No!
All you have to is go into the hotel and ask for him at the reception.
No! Take it off me, right now!
I'm so sorry, I really have no choice. The sooner you go in, the sooner you'll be back out.
I can't believe you did this to me.
- I'll be right here, you have my word.  - Your word isn't worth shit!
Uh... it's worth 500 bucks, upfront.
You're an asshole!
And you're wonderful, huh?
Miss, may I help you?
Yes.
I'm here for, uh...
Mr. Jang.
Yes.
Who should I say is here?
Richard.
Uhm... no... Richard sent... Richard sent me.
What is your name?
No, Richard.
Richard's... uh... he's just looking for a place to park.
Mr. Jang still wants to know your name.
Lucy.
Lucy what?
Just Lucy. If he could... If he could he quick 'cause I have... I have to...
Just a second while I translate...
Mr. Jang is on his way, stay right here.
Can I sit?
Mr. Jang said you need to stay right here. I think it's better if you stay right here.
Excuse me. Regent Hotel.
No!
No, wait! No!
Please!
Wait, I don't know anything!
I don't know anything! Please! Please!
No, please!
Do you speak English?
Tambien hablo poco Espanol.
Lucy, yes, I'm Lucy.
It's just been a terrible mistake. I'm just suppose to deliver this case.
If you lost the key, you don't have to chop off my hand, you can just cut the chain, OK?
Please!
I'm begging you, please!
No! No! No!
No! No! Please!
Please!
Hello, Miss, I speak English. I translate for Mr. Jang.
Please tell him that I haven't done anything. I don't know anything.
It's all just a big mistake, OK? Please, please tell him that.
Yes, OK, OK, hold on.
Mr. Jang wants to know what's in the case.
Well, I don't know what's in the case. Do you speak English or don't you speak English?!
Yes, I do! I studied one year at International High School in New York.
OK.
Richard gave me the case to give to you, that's all I know.
OK, please tell him that.
He gave me a paper with numbers written on it, I don't... what is this?
It's the code to open the case.
What's really in here?
Nothing dangerous.
So why won't he open it himself?
He doesn't trust Mr. Richard.
I don't trust Richard either.
I only dated him for a week.
OK! OK! OK!
- Mr. Jang insists that you open the case.  - OK! OK!
Please God, help me.
He wants you to hurry up, Mr. Jang has other things to do.
Can you describe the content of the case?
It's 4 plastic pouches filled with blue powder like a...
or maybe a purple powder? I don't know, it looks gross.
Mr. Jang wants to offer you a job.
A job?
I don't want a job!
If life starts approximately a billion years ago,
we'll have to wait 400,000 years
to see the aberration of the first nerve cells.
This is where life we know it begins.
Brains in formation of only a few milligrams
is not possible to determine any sign of intelligence yet.
It acts more as a reflex.
One neuron, you're alive. Two neurons, you're moving.
And with movement, interesting things begin to happen.
Animal life on Earth goes back millions of years.
Yet, most species only use 3-5% of its cerebral capacity.
But it isn't until we reached human beings at the top of the animal chain,
that we finally see a species used more of its cerebral capacity.
10% may not seem like much but it's a lot if we look at all we've done with it.
Now let's discuss a special case.
The only living being that uses its brain better than us...
the dolphin.
It's estimated that this incredible animal
uses up to 20% of its cerebral capacity.
And in particular, this allows it to have an echo-location system
that's more efficient than any sonar invented by mankind.
But the dolphin did not invent the sonar. It developed it naturally.
And this is the crucial part of our
philosophical reflection we have today.
Can we therefore conclude
that humans are concerned more with
"having"
than "being".
Lucy.
What did you do with my stomach?
Nothing! Just a little horizontal slit. It's very well done
and you'll find that in a month, this scar is practically invisible too.
You'll be able to show your tummy off on the beach next summer.
I don't care about the scar.
Is it, uh... is it why we opened you up?
Rest assured, we didn't harvest your organs or anything.
Uh, we merely slipped a little package in your lower tummy.
It's a... it's a new drug the kids in Europe are gonna love, believe me.
- What is it?  - Well, the scientific term is CPH4,
which is not very sexy from a sale's point of view.
So, uh... we're... we're still working on something a little bit more pop...
Any suggestions?
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Welcome, come on in. Lovely, oops...
Splendid! Splendid!
Marvelous! Lovely lovely!
- How are you?  - Very good, my dear.
OK.
Right, uh... first of all, many thanks for taking part in this enterprise
which I'm sure will go off flawlessly.
These lovely passport and tickets
will enable you to return home in the next 24 hours.
Now, upon arrival, you'll be taken in hand by our people
so that we might recover our merchandise
and you might re-discover the freedom which you so richly deserve.
I'm sure I don't need to remind you but, for any of those who may be tempted to
warn or turn themselves in to the authorities,
we have the names and addresses of the families of every one of you down to the distant cousins.
So, we rely therefore, on your complete discretion.
Good, anyway, uh...
gentleman, madam, allow me to be the first to wish you
bon voyage!
Oops!
You gonna sell this?
I'm afraid it's our business model.
For primitive beings like us, life seems to only have one single purpose.
Gaining time.
And its going through time, seems to be also the only
real purpose of each of the cell in our bodies.
To achieve that aim, the mass of the cells
that make up earthworm and human beings
has only 2 solutions:
be immortal...
or to reproduce.
If its habitat is not sufficiently favourable or nurturing,
the cell will choose immortality.
In other words, self-sufficiency and self-management.
On the other hand, if the habitat is favourable,
they will choose to reproduce.
That way, when they die,
they hand down essential information and knowledge to the next cell
which hands it down to the next cell and so on.
Thus, knowledge and learning
are handed down through time.
OK, OK, keep calm...
You have to wait, just play for time...
You'll have time to think it through on the plane... just take the flight,
take the flight, get out of here.
That's the main thing right now, just save time.
Don't try anything, keep your cool, you're alive...
you're alive... you're alive, that's all that matters.
Just wait, save time.
Save time.
I'm not in the mood.
Let's imagine for a few moments
what our life would be like if we could access, let's say,
20 % of our brains' capacity.
This first stage would give us access to and control
of our own body.
- Sir.  - Yes?
Has it been proven scientifically?
Oh, for the moment, it's just hypothesis, I confess.
But if you think about it,
it's troubling to realize that the Greeks, the Egyptians and the Indians
had notion of "cells" centuries before the invention of the microscope.
And what to say about Darwin
whom everybody took for a fool when he put forward his Theory of Evolution.
It's up to us to push the rules and laws
and go from "evolution" to "revolution".
100 billion neurons per human,
of which only 15% are activated.
There're more connections in the human body than there're stars in the galaxy.
We possess a gigantic network of information
to which we've almost no access.
- Sir!  - Yes?
And what would be the next stage?
Well, the next stage would probably be control of other people.
But for that, we will need to access at least 40% of our brains' capacity.
And after control of ourselves and others,
come control of matter.
But now we're entering the realm of science fiction.
And we don't know anything more than a dog who watches the moon.
- Excuse me, sir.  - Yes.
But what would happen if for some reason we ignore
somebody unlock 100% of the celebral capacity?
100%?
Yes.
I've no idea.
Hey!
- Hey, you speak English?  - No. No. No.
- You speak English? - Yes. Yes.
- Take me to the hospital now.  - Hospital?
- Hospital.  - Wait for me.
Miss, hello?
Hey, miss!
I need help, it's urgent.
You cannot be in here. We're operating.
Please, get out!
You wouldn't be able to save him anyway.
Tumour already invaded the cortext and right side of his spine.
Somebody put a bag of drug in me. I need you to remove it.
It's leaking.
Do it now.
Right. I'll just administer local anaethestic...
Don't bother.
Right, I... okay.
Calm down, please. Put the gun down.
I'm just going to... examine, OK?
- Do you mind?  - No.
- Hello?  - Mom?
Hey, Lucy.
Baby, it's great to hear from you
but what time is it over there?
I don't know. It's night.
Hold on a sec', let me get rid of the other line.
I'm going to go inside.
I'm back, you're not partying too much, are you?
You promised me you'll look after yourself.
I'm trying to, Mommy, I'm trying to.
Well, thanks for calling out of the blue like this.
Your father is gonna be sad he missed you.
He isn't home from the gym yet. Usually you call us in the morning.
- Mom...  - Yes?
I feel everything.
What do you mean, sweatie?
Space,
the air,
the vibrations,
the people.
I can feel the gravity.
I can feel the rotation of the Earth.
The heat leaving my body,
the blood in my veins,
I can feel my brain.
The deepest parts of my memory.
Sweatie, we've a bad connection, I can't hear you so well.
What did you say about "memory"?
The pain in my mouth, when I had braces, I ...
I can remember the feeling of your hand on my forehead when I ran a fever.
I remember stroking the cat. It was so soft.
A cat? What cat, honey?
Siamese with blue eye and a broken tail.
Sweatie, you can't possibly remember that.
You were barely a year old.
I remember the days of your milk in my mouth,
the room,
the liquid...
Sweatie, what are you talking about?
I just wanna tell you that I love you, Mom and Dad...
Sweatie...
And I wanna thank you for the...
thousand kisses that I can still feel on my face...
I love you, Mom.
I love you too, sweatie,
more than anything in the world.
How much is left?
500 grams?
And how long will it take for my body to eliminate the rest of it?
To answer that, I need to know what it is.
May I?
Go ahead.
CPH4.
Tell me about it.
Pregnant women manufacture CPH4 in the sixth week of pregnancy,
in tiny quantities.
For a baby, it packs the power of an atomic bomb.
It's what gives the foetus the necessary energy to form all the bones in its body.
I've heard they tried to make a synthetic version of it.
Didn't realize that they succeeded.
If it really is CPH4,
in this quantity, I'm amazed you're still alive.
Not for long.
Learning is always a painful process.
Like when you're little, your bones are growing and you ached all over.
Can you believe I can remember the sound of my own bones growing?
Like this grinding under the skin.
Everything is different now.
Like... sound of music that I can understand, like fluids...
It's funny I used to be so concerned with
who I was and what I wanted to be, and...
now I've access to the furthest reaches of my brain, I see things clearly and realize
what make us "us", it's primitive.
They're all obstacles.
Does that make any sense?
Like this pain you're experiencing...
is blocking you from understanding.
All you know now is pain.
That's all you know, pain.
Where are the others?
The others carrying the drugs. I need the rest of it
for medicinal purposes.
Berlin.
Paris.
Rome.
Thank you for sharing.
- Oh, good evening, Professor.  - I sweared I'll be back.
You hadn't forget your dinner tonight?
I'm afraid so. I'm exhausted.
- Have a good rest.  - Thank you.
You scared the shit out of me. You ring that bell like some nut bar!
I missed you!
Me too.
You lose your key or something?
Yeah.
- Can I borrow your laptop?  - Yeah, of course.
So I spent all day at this audition, awesome.
They just have you standing around all day because they don't give a shit about your time, gabbing away in Chinese.
Who understand Chinese? I don't understand Chinese.
And then they say they always gonna call
and they never do. They don't even take your phone number.
You know.Except this one guy, I bet he, uh...he's not Chinese.
He works at the agency and he's cute... Oh my God, he's cute!
You know, like, the cute in kinda way, like he has this thing...
Oh my God, his ass...
Let me get started on that!
And you'll never gonna guess where he take me.
Four Seasons, Royal Suite, and we made love all night.
I'm sorry, I'm talking about myself. What's up? How's Richard?
He's dead.
You guys are crazy. I'm gonna take a shower.
- Yes?  - Profesor Norman, my name is Lucy.
I've just read all your research on the human's brain. We need to meet.
All of my research?
Well, I'm very flattered, young lady. But I find that hard to believe.
I must have written no less than...
6734 pages. I can recite them too all by heart if you wish.
Are you one of Emily's friends?
This sounds like one of her silly jokes. Is she there with you?
No, I'm on my own.
- Who are you?  - I just told you.
Lucy, right? Yes, sorry.
I read your theory on the use of the brain's capacity.
It's a little rudimentary but you're on the right track.
Oh, thank you.
Professor, my cells are reproducing at a phenomenal speed,
several millions per second,
and I'm having trouble precisely evaluating the time of my death
but I doubt it'll last more than 24 hours.
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying is that your theory is not a theory.
I absorbed a large quatity of synthetic CPH4
that would allow me to use 100% of my celebral capacity.
Right now I'm at 28% and which you wrote is true.
Once the brain reaches 20% , it opens up and expands the rest
and there are no more obstacles.
They fall away like dominos. I'm colonizing my own brain.
Uh... well... I don't know... what to... say.
It's true, I've... I've been working on this theory for over 20 years but it's...
it's only... all ever been hypothesis and research ideas.
I... I never thought anyone would...
You can control your own metabolism?
Yes.
And I can start to control other people's bodies.
Also I can control magnetic and electric waves and...
not all of them, just... the most basic.
Television.
Telephone.
Radio.
It's amazing.
I don't feel pain,
fear,
desire.
It's like all things that make us human are fading away.
It's like the less human I feel,
all these knowledge about... everything,
Quantum Physics, Applied Mathemathics,
the infinite capacity of the cell's nucleus,
they're all exploding inside my brain, all these knowledge...
I don't know what to do with it.
If you're asking me... what to do...
You know...
If you think about
the very nature of life...
I mean, from the very begining...
The development of the first cell... divided into two cells.
This whole purpose of life has been
passed on what was learned.
There's no higher purpose.
So if you're asking me what to do with all these knowledge you're accumalating, I'd say...
pass it on.
Just like any simple cell,
going through time.
Time?
Yes, of course.
I'll be at your door in 12 hours.
- You leaving?  - Yes.
- What is this?  - A prescription.
Since when did you start writing Chinese?
- Since an hour ago.  - Lucy, I don't understand any of this.
Your kidneys aren't functioning efficiently. Your liver is failing. You need to make some lifestyle changes.
Take this medication. Work out. Eat organic.
You'll be OK.
Last night, at 11 p.m., a woman shot a patient dead.
Del Rio.
- Hello ?  - Yes, I've important imformation about a group of drug traffickers.
I need to speak with someone in position of authority.
Ah-hah, you're very lucky. There's no one with more authority in this office than me.
But let's start with the begining. What's your name?
Listen up, Pierre Del Rio, get off your desk, sit in your chair,
pick up the red pen to your left and take down everything I say.
There're no cameras, hurry up. I've no time to waste.
Go ahead.
I'm gonna be sending you details of three people about to arrive in Europe.
Each one is carrying a kilo of drugs. I need you to arrest them and collect the substance.
I'll need it later.
What form of these drugs in? Bars? Capsules?
Powder, hidden in plastic pouches inside their intestines.
Excuse me?
Make sure to be careful when you remove them. The product is very powerful.
Believe me.
Got it?
Yeah.
Good.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah, sure.
Del Rio.
Thanks for calling me back.
We got the third guy.
Thanks very much. I'll send you the paper work with the transfer.
Bye.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're now beginning our descend to Paris-Charles de Gaulle.
Miss, I've to ask you to put away your computer now.
You should wipe your nose.
- Excuse me?  - May I have a glass of champagne?
Um, yes, of course.
Miss, your champagne.
Thank you.
I'm very sorry but... uh, you really need to close your table now.
Sure.
To knowledge.
If the habitat is not sufficiently favorable or nurturing...
the cell will choose immortality.
In another word, self-sufficiency and self-management.
No, miss, miss.
You must remain seated.
Miss, stop!
Miss...
Miss, open the door! You really have to go back to your seat! Miss!
We're going to land soon, please, open the door!
Please, say something, are you okay?
Miss?
Miss!
Miss, please open the door!
Do something, help me open!
Answer me! Open the door!
Miss? Are you okay? Say something!
Miss, don't move!
- I need to talk to you alone.  - And I need you to put your hands up, please.
Did you get the packets?
Yes.
- Where're they?  - They're safe.
Here, in Paris.
They'll be safer in my hands.
You know, as a cop, we see some pretty weird shit
but I've to be honest with you.
What you did back there, that freaked me out.
To put everyone to sleep like that,
do I need to be worried?
No.
Good.
Do you mind?
No.
- What's that?  - Korean, I'm going to drive.
Hey! Hey! Hey! No! No! No! This is a police car!
You can't! No, this is not possible, lady.
This is a police car!
OK, OK.
Sir, sir, excuse me, sir.
I need to talk to somebody.
Look, I'm a German citizen and I demand us a lawyer.
Do you always drive like that?
I never driven before.
Great.
- Hey, this is one way!  - We're late.
Hey, I would rather be late than dead.
We never really die.
Sorry, sir, I don't agree...
I'm fine, fine.
I'm going to tell them to stop following us.
Don't bother.
Give me the case.
Open it.
Let's go.
I'm not sure I could be of any help for you.
Yes, you are.
What for?
A reminder.
Shall we go?
Where are we going?
Take the first left.
Okay.
- Professor?  - Thanks.
- Yes?  - Lucy.
It's her, it's her.
Hey you, you're in Paris?
Yes, I'm.
Good, good, excellant.
So, look, I'm no longer at the hotel now, uh, I've come to the university
where I've taken the liberty of calling and gathering a few of my colleagues to discuss your case.
Top men in their field and um... very trustworthy.
I trust you.
Oh, thank you. So, do you think you can meet us here at the university?
I'm, uh...I'm very pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
- Captain Del Rio.  - How do you do?
Let... let me introduce you to my colleagues.
This is Professor Cartier, neuro surgeon.
- Professor...  - I know who everyone is.
Ah, of course.
Uh, gentlemen, this is Lucy, the first woman to...
I mean... like I mentioned earlier...
Ms. Lucy has for reasons, remains a mystery to me,
unlocked certain portion of her brain
that offered access
to... previously unexplored celebral zones.
She has abilities.
Can you give us an example?
Your daughter, Gabriel, aged 6, died in a car accident.
It was a blue car, leather seats...
plastic bird hanging from the rear view mirror.
There're men coming here, can you secure the room?
- I need to stay focus.  - Sure.
Speed it up.
How did you manage to access all these information?
Electrical impulses...
Every cell knows and talks to every other cell.
They exchange a thousand bits of information between them per second.
Cells group together, forming a giant web of communication
which in turn forms matter.
Cells get together, take on one form,
deform, reform,
makes no difference, it's all the same.
Human considers themself unique.
So, they rooted their whole theory of existence on their uniqueness.
"One"... is the unit of measure but it's not.
All social systems we put into place are mere "sketch".
1 + 1 = 2 That's all we learned.
But 1 + 1 has never equalled 2.
They're in fact, no numbers and no letters.
We codify our existence to bring it down to human size
to make it comprehensible.
We created the scale so that we can forget its unfathomable scale.
But if humans are not the unit of measure,
and the world isn't governed by mathemathical laws,
what governs all that?
Form a car speeding down the road...
speed up the image infinitely
and the car disappears.
So, what proof do we have of its existence?
Time gives legitimacy to its existence.
Time is the only true unit of meassure.
It gives proof to the existence of matter.
Without time,
we don't exist.
Time is "unity".
We wouldn't be able to hold them for much longer.
Time to go then.
Are you sure you need such huge doses?
I'm afraid you won't survive.
Some cells inside me will fight and defend their integrity to the very end.
In order to attain the last few percent, I've to force it.
To crack the cells open to their nucleus.
All these knowledge, Lucy...
I'm not even sure that mankind is ready for it.
We're so driven by power and profit.
Given man's nature,
it might bring us only instability and chaos.
Ignorance brings chaos, not knowledge.
I'll build a computer and download all my knowledge in it.
I'll find a way for you to have access to it.
Yeah.
I just hope, we'll be worthy of your sacrifice.
Nobody move!
Do you understand English?
What is she doing?
She's looking for energy and matter.
And she's trying to connect with our computers.
Oh my God, what's happening?
What's she making?
A new generation of computer, I presume.
Hey, you!
Look, the computer, it's moving.
Hey.
Where is she?
Life was given to us a billion years ago.
Now you know what to do with it.