Marvel's Phase 1 & 2 - A Look Back
I should't be alive,
unless it was for a reason.
I will protect Asgard and all the realms.
You're nothing but a boy,
trying to prove himself a man.
You just don't know when to give up,do you?
I can do this all day.
I can not help you if you're gonna start all of this again.
There is nothing except this.
I just finally know what I have to do.
These people are innocent.
Taking their lives will gain you nothing.
So take mine,
and end this.
What made you so special?
Nothing.
I'm just a kid from Brooklyn.
You think you're the only superhero in the world?
You've become part of a bigger universe.
You just don't know it yet.
There was an idea,
to bring together a group of remarkable people.
See if they could work together,
to fight the battles that we never could.
There is no stopping it.
There is only the war.
This is monsters and magic
and nothing we were ever trained for.
You were made to be ruled.
How desperate are you.
You call on such lost creatures to defend you.
There is no version of this where you come out on top.
I have an army.
We have a Hulk.
Puny god.
You start with something pure,
something exciting.
Then,come the mistakes.
No.
The compromises.
The brutality,the sacrifice,
it changes you.
I'd rather be a good man than a great king.
The price of freedom is high.
And it's a price I'm willing to pay.
You can take away my house,
all my tricks and toys.
But I am Iron Man.
Yes,the world is a vulnerable place.
and yes,we help make it that way.
But you need us.
You know why?
Do enlighten us.
Because we're also the ones best qualified to defend it.
Humans,
They are not the cowering wretches we were promised.
To challenge them is to court death.
I don't think you understand what you've started,
letting the Avengers loose on the world.
They're dangerous.
They surely are.
And the whole world knows it.
Every world knows it.
Bala bala bala...
What the hell does that have to do with anything?
The fate of 12 billion people,
is in the hands of these criminals.
I come from a planet of outlaws.
******
Sounds like a place which I would like to visit.
It's not a world of spies any more.
Not even a world of heroes.
This is the age
of miracles.
They've gone their separate ways.
They'll come back.
Because we'll need them to.
Oh,Yeah.
Made by:Jr Logan