Chinese Tea ceremony is an activity that cultivate moral character and develop temperament by making tea ,appreciating  tea and drinking tea .
Now,let me show you how to make a cup of tea.
We should prepare the tea set,it includes the tea tray,tea cup,teapot,tea leaves,the cylinder of teaspoon and the boiling water.
Firstly,burning the teapot and the tea cup with boiling water.
It can clean them and make the musty taste  disappear.
Secondly,using a tea spoon to fill the teapot one fifth to a half full with tea leaves .
Pouring water into the teapot.
The first pass is to be drained of water.
This is washing tea.
Washing tea needs to be finished quickly, because it only needs to wake up the fragrance of tea.
Thirdly,if it has bubbles on the surface of the tea.
don’t stop injecting water
until it nearly overflow,
then we can scrape bubbles  with the lid.
After washing tea , we pour boiling water  highly  on the teapot.
Covering with the lid.
Drenching the teapot with boiling water,
it will be better if we can do it for three times.
Because high temperature inside and outside can make you smell the fragrance of tea .
Finally,we can pour the tea into the tea cup.
Then, we can enjoy the good tea,
After using the teapot, we should wash it and sidelong the lid.
don’t  screw down the lid.
We should put the teapot in the dry place ,but avoiding the chemical agent.
We shouldn't often pour water into the teapot, unless we brew with tea.
This is the simulation of Chinese tea ceremony.Thank you!