[ Intro - Red Warrior ]
"Once I had a dream and this is it"
[ Dark Chest of Wonders ]
"Once there was a child's dream"
One night the clock struck twelve
The window open wide
"Once there was a child's heart"
The age I learned to fly
And took a step outside
"Once I knew all the tales"
It's time to turn back time
Follow the pale moonlight
"Once I wished For this night"
Faith brought me here
It's time to cut the rope and fly
to a dream
Far across the sea
All the burdens gone
Open the chest once more
Dark chest of wonders
Seen through the eyes
Of the one with pure heart
Once so long ago
The one in the big blue
is what the world stole from me
This night will bring him back to me
Fly to a dream
Far across the sea
All the burdens gone
Open the chest once more
Dark chest of wonders
Seen through the eyes
Of the one with pure heart
Once so long ago
Fly to a dream
Far across the sea
All the burdens gone
Open the chest once more
Dark chest of wonders
Seen through the eyes
Of the one with pure heart
Once so long ago
[ Planet Hell ]
Denying the lying
A million children fighting
For lives in strife
For hope beyond the horizon
A dead world
A dark path
Not even crossroads to choose from
All the bloodred carpets before me
Behold this fair creation of god!
My only wish to leave behind
All the days of the earth
An everyday
hell of my kingdom come
The first rock thrown again
Welcome to hell,little saint
Mother Gaia in slaughter
Welcome to paradise,soldier
My first cry never ending
All life is to fear for life
You fool,you wanderer
You challenged the gods and lost
Save yourself a penny for the ferryman
Save yourself and let them suffer
In hope
In love
This world ain't ready for the ark
Save yourself a penny for the ferryman
Save yourself and let them suffer
In hope
In love
Mankind works in mysterious ways
Welcome down
To my planet hell
Save yourself a penny for the ferryman
Save yourself and let them suffer
In hope
In love
This world ain't ready for the ark
Save yourself a penny for the ferryman
Save yourself and let them suffer
In hope
In love
Mankind works in mysterious ways
[ Ever Dream ]
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
Would you do it with me
Heal the scars and change the stars
Turn loose the heaven within
I'd take you away
Castaway on A lonely day
Bosom for A teary cheek
My song can but borrow your grace
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
Come out,come out,wherever you are
So lost In your sea
Give in,give in for my touch
For my taste for my lust
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
Your beauty cascaded on me
In this white night fantasy
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
Ever felt away with me
Just once that all I need
Entwined in finding you one day
Ever felt away without me
My love,it lies so deep
Ever dream of me
[ The Kinslayer ]
For whom the gun tolls
For whom the prey weeps
Bow before a war
Call it religion
Some wounds never heal
Some tears never will
Dry for the unkind
Cry for mankind
Even the dead cry
Their only comfort
Kill your friend,I don't care
Orchid kids,blinded stare
Need to understand
No need to forgive
No truth,no sense left to be followed
Facing this unbearable fear,
like meeting an old friend
"Time to die,poor mates,
You made me what I am!"
In this world of A million religions,
Everyone prays the same way
"Your praying is in vain,
It'll all be over soon"
Father help me,
Save me A place by your side!
"There is no god"
"Our creed is but for ourselves"
"Not a hero,unless you die"
"Our species eat the wounded ones"
Drunk with the blood of your victims I do,
feel your pity-wanting pain
Lust for fame,A deadly game
"Run away with your impeccable kin!"
Good wombs hath borne bad sons
Cursing God,why?
Falling for every lie
Survivors' guilt
In us forevermore
15 candles
Redeemers of this world
Dwell in hypocrisy:
How were we supposed to know?
[ The Phantom of The Opera ]
In sleep he sang to me
In dreams he came
That voice which calls to me
And speaks my name
And do I dream again
For now I find
The phantom of the opera is there
Inside my mind
Sing once again with me
Our strange duet
My power over you
Grows stronger yet
And though you turn from me
To glance behind
The phantom of the opera is there
Inside your mind
Those who have seen your face
Draw back in fear
I am the mask you wear
but it's me they hear
My/your spirit and your/my voice,
In one combined
The phantom of the opera is there
Inside your/my mind
Opera
He's,the phantom of the opera
In all your fantasies
You always knew
That man and mystery
with both in you
And in this labyrinth,
Where night is blind
The phantom of the opera is there
Inside your / my mind
Sing,my angel of music!!!
Sing!!!
My angel!!!
Sing,sing,sing,my angel!!!
[ The Siren ]
A lady with a violin,
playing to the seals
Harken to the sound of calling
Who tied my hands to the wheel?
The zodiac turns over me
"Come to me"
Somewhere there,my fate revealed
I hear but how will I see?
I tied myself to the wheel
The winds talk to my sails,not me
"Come to me"
Somewhere there,my fate revealed
I hear but how will I see?
[ Sleeping Sun ]
The sun is sleeping quietly
Once upon a century
Wistful oceans calm and red
Ardent caresses laid to rest
For my dreams I hold my life
For wishes I behold my night
The truth at the end of time
Losing faith makes A crime
I wish for this night-time
To last for a lifetime
The darkness around me
Shores of a solar sea
Oh,how I wish to go down with the sun
Sleeping
Weeping
With you
Sorrow has a human heart
From my god it will depart
I'd sail before a thousand moons
Never finding where to go
Two hundred twenty-two days of light
Will be desired by A night
A moment for the poet's play
Until there's nothing left to say
I wish for this night-time
To last for a lifetime
The darkness around me
Shores of a solar sea
Oh,how I wish to go down with the sun
Sleeping
Weeping
With you
I wish for this night-time
To last for a lifetime
The darkness around me
Shores of a solar sea
Oh,how I wish to go down with the sun
Sleeping
Weeping
With you
[ High Hopes ]
Beyond the horizon
of the place we lived
when we were young
In a world of magnets and miracles
Our thoughts strayed constantly
And without boundary
The ringing of the division bell
had begun
Along the long road
and on down to the causeway
Do they still meet there by the cut
There was a ragged band that followed in our footsteps
Running before time took our dreams away
Leaving the myriad of small creatures that tried to tie us to the ground
To a life consumed by slow decay
The grass was greener
The light was brighter
With friends surrounded
The nights of wonder
Looking beyond the embers of bridges glowing behind us
To a glimpse of how green it was on the other side
Steps taken forwards but sleepwalking back again
Dragged by the force of some inner tide
At the highest altitude with flag unfurled
We reached the dizzy heights of that dreamed of world
Encumbered forever by desire and ambition
There's a hunger still unsatisfied
Our weary eyes still stray to the horizon
Though down this road we've been so many times
The grass was greener
The light was brighter
With friends surrounded
The nights of wonder
The dawn mist growing
The water flowing
The endless river
Forever and ever
The grass was greener
The light was brighter
The taste was sweeter
The nights of wonder
With friends surrounded
The dawn mist growing
The water flowing
The endless river
Forever and ever
[ Bless The Child ]
"I was born amidst the purple waterfalls"
"I was weak,"
"Yet not unblessed"
"Dead to the world"
"Alive for the journey"
"One night I dreamt"
"A white rose withering,"
"A newborn drowning"
"A lifetime loneliness"
"I dreamt all my future"
"Relived my past"
"And witnessed the beauty"
"of the beast"
Where have all the feelings gone?
Why has all the laughter ceased?
Why am I loved
only when I'm gone?
Gone back in time to bless the child
How can I ever feel again?
Given the chance would I return?
Why am I loved
only when I'm gone?
Gone back in time to bless the child
Think of me long enough
to make a memory
Come bless the child one more time
I've never felt so alone in my life
As I drank from the cup
which was counting my time
There's a poison drop
in this cup of man
To drink it is to follow
the left hand path
Why am I loved
only when I'm gone?
Gone back in time to bless the child
Think of me long enough
to make a memory
Come bless the child one more time
Think of me long enough
to make a memory
Come bless the child one more time
"Where have all the feelings gone?"
"Why is the deadliest sin"
"to love as I loved you?"
"Now unblessed,homesick in time,"
"Soon to be freed from care,"
"From human pain"
"My tale is the most bitter truth"
"Time pays us but"
"with earth,dust,"
"And A dark,silent grave"
"Remember,my child:"
"Without innocence"
"The cross is only iron,"
"Hope is only an illusion"
"and ocean soul's"
"Nothing but a name"
"The child bless thee"
"and keep thee forever"
[ Wishmaster ]
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Elbereth
Lorien
A dreamy-eyed child staring into night
On a journey to storyteller's mind
Whispers A wish speaks with the stars
The words are silent in him
Distant sigh from A lonely heart
I'll be with you soon,my shalafi
Grey havens my destiny
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Silvara
Starbreeze
Sla-mori the one known only by him
To august realms,the sorcery within
If you hear the call of arcane lore,
Your world shall rest on earth no more
A maiden elf calling with her cunning song
Meet me at the inn of last home
Heartborne will find the way!
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Wishmaster
Crusade for your will
A child,dreamfinder
The apprentice becoming
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
Master!
Apprentice!
Heartborne,7th seeker
Warrior!
Disciple!
In me the wishmaster
[ Slayng The Dreamer ]
I'm a priest for the poorest sacrifice
I'm but a raft in a sea
of sorrow,sorrow and greed
You bathed in my wine
Drank from my cup,
Mocked my rhyme
Your slit tongues licked
my aching wounds
Put a stake through my heart!
And drag me into sunlight
So awake for your greed
As you're slaying the dreamer
Swansong for the wish of night
God it hurts,give A name to the pain
Our primrose path
to hell is growing weed
Put a stake through my heart!
And drag me into sunlight
So awake for your greed
As you're slaying the dreamer
Blame me,it's me
Coward,A good for nothing scapegoat
Dumb kid,living a dream
Romantic only on paper
Tell me why
you took all that was mine!
Stay as you lay don't lead me astray!
Tell me why
you took all that was mine!
Stay as you lay don't lead me astray!
Wake up,mow the weed
You'd be nothing without me
Take my life if you have the heart
to die
You bastards tainted my tool
Raped my words,played me a fool
Gather your precious glitter
and leave me be
The great ones are all dead
And I'm tired,too
I truly hate you all!
[ Kuolema Tekee Taiteilijan ]
Only once I could see my dream
Didn't feel the smallness under the stars
Once I got bars in my cradle
As a prisoner I write a letter from there
My lord,to you,let me become what my child thinks I am
In you is the beauty of the world,of which death made me an artist
My own heaven I created here
Let me get away
[ Nemo ]
This is me for forever
One of the lost ones
The one without a name
Without an honest heart as compass
This is me for forever
One without a name
These lines the last endeavor
To find the missing lifeline
Oh how I wish
For soothing rain
All I wish is to dream again
My loving heart
Lost in the dark
For hope I'd give my everything
A flower,withered between
the pages 2 and 3
The once and forever
bloom gone with my sins
Walk the dark path
Sleep with angels
Call the past for help
Touch me with your love
And reveal to me my true name
Oh how I wish
For soothing rain
All I wish is to dream again
My loving heart
Lost in the dark
For hope I'd give my everything
Oh how I wish
For soothing rain
Oh how I wish to dream again
Once and for all
And all for once
Nemo my name forevermore
Nemo sailing home
Nemo letting go
Oh how I wish
For soothing rain
All I wish is to dream again
My loving heart
Lost in the dark
For hope I'd give my everything
Oh how I wish
For soothing rain
Oh how I wish to dream again
Once and for all
And all for once
Nemo my name forevermore
My name forevermore
[ Ghost Love Score ]
We used to swim
the same moonlight waters
Oceans away
from the wakeful day
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"I'll bleed forever"
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"I'll bleed forever"
Scent of the sea
before the waking of the world
Brings me to thee
Into the blue memory
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"I'll bleed forever"
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"I'll bleed forever"
Into the blue memory
A siren from the deep
came to me
He sang my name my longing
Still I write my songs
about that dream of mine
Worth everything I may ever be
The child will be born again
That siren carried him to me
First of them true loves
Singing on the shoulders
of an angel
Without care for love and loss
Bring me home or leave me be
My love in the dark heart of the night
I have lost the path before me
The one behind will lead me
Bring me home or leave me be
My love in the dark heart of the night
I have lost the path before me
The one behind will lead me
"Take me"
"Cure me"
"Kill me"
"Bring me home"
"Every way,every day"
"Just another loop in the hangman's noose"
Take me,cure me,kill me,bring me home
Every way,every day
I keep on watching us sleep
Relive the old sin of adam and eve
Of you and me
Forgive the adoring beast
Redeem me into childhood
Show me myself without the shell
Like the advent of may
I'll be there when you say
Time to never hold our love
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"So I'll bleed forever"
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"So I'll bleed forever"
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"So I'll bleed forever"
"My fall will be for you"
"My love will be in you"
"If you be the one to cut me"
"So I'll bleed forever"
[ Stone People ]
[ Creek Mary's Blood ]
Soon I will be here no more
You'll hear the tale
Through my blood
Through my people
And the eagle's cry
The bear within will never lay to rest
Wandering on horizon road
Following the trail of tears
White man came
Saw the blessed land
We cared,you took
You fought,we lost
Not the war but an unfair fight
Sceneries painted beautiful in blood
Wandering on horizon road
Following the trail of tears
Once we were here
Where we have lived
since the world began
since time itself gave us this land
Our souls
will join again the wild
Our home in peace and war and death
Wandering on horizon road
Following the trail of tears
Once we were here
Where we have lived
since the world began
Since time itself gave us this land
Wandering on horizon road
Following the trail of tears
Once we were here
Where we have lived
since the world began
Since time itself gave us this land
I still dream every night of them wolves,
Them mustangs,
Those endless prairies
The restless winds
over mountaintops
The unspoilt frontier of my kith and kin
The hallowed land of the great spirit
I still believe
In every night
In every day
I am like the caribou
And you like the wolves
that make me stronger
We never owed you anything
Our only debt
is one life for our mother
It was A good day
to chant this song for her
Our spirit was here
long before you
Long before us
And long will it be
after your pride
Brings you to your end
[ Over The Hills and Far Away ]
They came for him one winter's night
Arrested,he was bound
They said there'd been A robbery,
His pistol had been found
They marched him to the station house,
He waited for the dawn
And as they led him to the dock,
He knew that he'd been wronged
"You stand accused of robbery,"
He heard the bailiff say
He knew without an alibi,
Tomorrow's light
would mourn his freedom
Over the hills and far away,
For ten long years
he'll count the days
Over the mountains and the seas,
A prisoner's life for him there'll be
He knew that it would cost him dear,
But yet he dare not say
where he had been
that fateful night,
A secret it must stay
He had to fight back tears of rage
His heart beat like a drum
For with the wife of his best friend,
He spent his final night of freedom
Over the hills and far away,
He swears he will return one day
Far from the mountains and the seas,
Back in her arms he swear he'll be
Over the hills and far away
Over the hills and,
Each night within his prison cell,
He looks out through the bars
He reads the letters that she wrote
One day he'll know
the taste of freedom
Over the hills and far away,
She prays he will return one day
As sure as the rivers reach the seas,
Back in his arms he swears she'll be
Over the hills and far away,
He swears he will return one day
Over the mountains and the seas
Back in her arms he swear he'll be
Over the hills and far away,
She prays he will return one day
As sure as the rivers reach the sea,
Back in his arms he swears she'll be
Over the hills
Over the hills and far away,
Over the hills and far away
[ Wish I Had an Angel ]
I wish I had an angel
For one moment of love
I wish I had your angel tonight
Deep into a dying day
I took A step outside an innocent heart
Prepare to hate me,fall when I may
This night will hurt you like never before
Old loves they die hard
Old lies they die harder
I wish I had an angel
For one moment of love
I wish I had your angel,your
virgin mary undone
I'm in love with my lust
Burning angelwings to dust
I wish I had your angel tonight
I'm going down so frail and cruel
Drunken disguise changes all the rules
Old loves they die hard
Old lies they die harder
I wish I had an angel
For one moment of love
I wish I had your angel your
virgin mary undone
I'm in love with my lust
Burning angelwings to dust
I wish I had your angel tonight
Greatest thrill not to kill!
But to have the prize of the night!
Hypocrite!
Wanna be friend!
13th disciple who betrayed me for nothing!
Last dance,first kiss,your touch,my bliss
Beauty always comes with dark thoughts
I wish I had an angel
For one moment of love
I wish I had your angel
Your virgin mary undone
I'm in love with my lust
Burning angelwings to dust
I wish I had your angel tonight
I wish I had an angel
I wish I had an angel!!!